I'd rather face the pyre
I'd rather blaze, yeah, I'd rather blaze
I'd rather blaze and say goodbye
But no, I retire with my eyes on shut
Dead or wake, yeah, dead or wake
Out the ashes of a phoenix
We're perceived, so vow with teeth
I don't move on
You hear that serpents song, you'll know, you'll know
You hear that serpents song, you'll know I'm close, don't go
You hear that serpents song, you'll know I'm with you, we're last one
I'll show you what a gentleman can do, pretty
rising rising rising from this day
Hey guys.
Oh, hi.
Trix, come here.
Why do you feel so mean to me?
So mean.
Mm.
Yeah.
That's cool.
The problem is like she'll,
She'll like you she'll I mean she'll like Sam and I mean it's like
So go to you know, she'll like all these people that she'll say, but I'm
I'm like the person I'm always the one
Yeah, I'm like the worst one never talked to me again, right?
My god, I'm still wearing this I don't know
Not fine
And yeah, wait till like 20 people get here,
then I'll premiere it.
It's really good.
But I think that's my favorite one.
What's wrong?
Oh, babe.
Oh, my babe.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
You're the ruler.
You're the ruler of me.
Okay.
Are we all here?
Rudy's there watching?
Rudy's here?
You're there? Rudy?
You're watching?
Standing guard Lenore wake up Lenore. Oh, excuse me. What are you on attention? Okay. Oh
Got you got you
But yeah, it's one of the situations where it's really like I really didn't do anything except the
We know what I did nothing
But I don't know still she just I think she just copies after beta like oh beat it says you know this don't so don't
Insular I she likes being in more than me now. That's kind of funny pretty funny
You got some beers tonight. Oh wow. I got good stuff. I'm just waiting for 20 people to get in the room. So wait a little bit
Got something really funny though show you
Promise you'll like it promise almost
Black RG black RG is black RG or any 2020 black RG. Oh, I appreciate he says he likes me
He likes my show. I really do appreciate that. It's okay. He doesn't like
Whatever he keeps calling it
Like RG
You use it too. You know what?
It was a funny picture of Groovy Jimin and Noose and stuff, but yeah, it's not appropriate
Especially considering this color. I mean not to I don't know. I just
You're outrageous of black RG black RG is pretty outrageous, huh? I do like him 2020. You're awesome. How are you? I?
Got some good
Good people like 2020 I got another person right now. It's kind of helping me out
Actually a couple more people
Kind of like we
Regenerate a little bit
Ten people. Okay, we need to double that let's double that
20 people then I'll start it then I'll start the the surprise
It's a kind of from you. I'm pretty good. I'm pretty good because I have I've these are the best. Maybe like cookies
Looky, looky, I got a cookie.
I like that.
Remember that, that was from Pan, right?
These are, you know where these are from, they're really good.
Are these the best cookies I think they might be?
Yes, yes, yes.
I have a couple, I have a bunch of people
I have something to say to too.
But not that, I don't get mad, but I do want to like,
It's like, I never saw a situation where someone with mods,
I'm not talking about anybody I've seen in the room yet.
And I'll mod Q if you can play.
I know he doesn't care.
It's just out of respect.
But I never saw somebody whose mods
like tried to fuck them over so much.
And it's like, I'm not mad about it or anything like that.
It's just like, I'm like, gosh, why?
Are they doing that I
Had um someone I did like someone came in like you know
And I don't have that many people coming in asking for readings and I so I did a reading today
for someone and it was it went really well and
and I kind of like I
Said oh you can contact me
If you want to go more in depth because she had some more questions about it
If you want to go more in depth we can schedule something and then I kind of rolled over to sleep
Or I was kind of tired whatever and I look at the back of my computer and she was and the lady had asked
Well, oh, how much is how much is like the hour or whatever the half hour or whatever?
Instead of saying like oh, oh, he's asleep or you can just cut call it was email. They were just they said
$90,000 and like
Basically just like
Fuck me, right? I
Don't know I
Look, I can't I just can't fathom on any video as a mom even if I really didn't like them. I wouldn't like
It's almost like it doesn't feel like a sabotage, but it's like I really wouldn't want to think that these people were trying to do that to me, but
Because two people started chiming it. Oh $90,000 like just give you these like ridiculous aim ladies like oh, okay
Which is like a lap?
Can you like like in the future like?
You just tell them
Contact me or something like that. You don't have to like lie or they say like
Really like stupid like ridiculous. I don't know. I'm not mad about it. I'm just like why did you do that?
It's like you hate me
I think I'm the only one with this mod problem.
It's got to find mod people that I should play shouldn't but
maybe I expect too much from people.
I probably do. I just expect like hey
I'm gonna kind of help them out like I know they're not helping no one really
wants to help me out like as a mod like
The only time people ever mod is if somebody says something about them then they say then they hide them and turns into like
Oh, they're high and it's like and that's like oh my god. Why are you doing like?
That hurts me too, right Canada dry someone said get a life Canada dry
Hidden like hidden in my from a chat time. Who's actually a month, right?
And I was like Canada dry
First of all it wasn't that bad
He has a whiny little bitchy foot and I like you Canada dry I like you I had to unmod you
Hate thing that is yeah, I'm just getting a couple things off my chest
I like you Canada dry a few things happened
Like nobody mods for me and I don't expect them to and think that as you are a mod now
Like I don't know when I modded you or whatever, but and I know you really didn't you know
I don't expect my mods to do anything. The only reason I mod people is I
Respect kinda right I kind of want respect back a little bit
Whatever, I don't get it. I don't get it. Yeah, Canada is pretty much bitchy
But the only time people ever mod is like if somebody says something about them then they hide the person
Which is probably 90% of the time shouldn't be hid, right?
Even like, you know, that's the only time that anybody's hidden is there's something that says something they said they said
Get a life Canada drive. Well, you should get a life Canada drive. You should
You sit there bitch. I mean, it's like really easy to make fun of you because you're like
It's like literally it's like it's like high-pitched bitching noise you make. I
Don't think I've ever made that noise. I just maybe made it now, but that was like it hurt my throat to do
Okay, and I like you can't I dry I can't I dry I like you and I'll stick up for you
I mean I would I mean you just say say hey, you know time is picking on me
No, it's a high time time is a lot. I know time is an asshole time is
Time talks shit about me and other time. I know I know
But you know
He's he's been here for me, you know
It's like and I really don't care if you're like here for me
Like defend me other chats or even anything as long as you're here like come to my chat and being your present
I respect that.
So I'm all kinds of people, but yeah, Canada Dry,
you're really looking kind of douchey.
I mean, it's like really,
I don't mean to be rude or anything.
And it's like, and everyone was like, yeah,
I think he's okay too.
He does kind of like, he's a little bit of a,
a little bit of a, you know,
no, go over here, go over.
It's okay, it's okay.
I know, I probably do the same thing.
You know, I probably do the same.
I probably,
I don't know. I'll just say I'm as guilty as anybody of anything, right?
but
Yeah, I how does and I don't know how a mod
Get another mod. I'm still confused about that shit. I finished another beer. I might get another one
And that's like I can't even get 12 I can't yeah, and I can't even get 20 people on the chat right now
I mean, that's kind of disappointing me too
Um, I think the video down here, but my videos are never really taken down trippin sip syndicates
everything on rumble
And some reason it's on a rumble Sam man. I think I'm on Sam and the
Tevo or whatever
Yeah, yeah open and drunk by 2020 well good, I mean it's like
I mean, I was like, I was like, I kind of like was asking,
are you like an adult Canada drag?
Cause it seems like he's, I mean, it's the kind of like,
like a middle school reaction to things.
Like, I don't know.
I was like, I was kind of worried.
I was like, oh my gosh, I have a, I hope,
I don't hope I don't have a 13 year old guy in my chat.
Cause he's like, I don't think I've like,
had that high pitch of a voice or like,
like that's not certain.
It's okay Canada drag and I like you.
I like you.
It's different. He's like, oh, well, this is this. I know you have a channel too
I know he has a channel too and like, you know blah blah and also I don't I don't appreciate like when I'm doing a show
And I'm so happy to help your channel if you can't a drive if you have a channel
When I meet her met her and probably
October November last year
She came out took me to dinner and I will say
It was all good until the summer, but I'll say,
she turned the dinner, which was a beautiful thing.
You can see the smile on my face
and how nice of a night we had and everything was fine.
And it's like, she never said anything about money.
But then now she has to show,
oh, here's what I donated to him.
And oh, and by the way, I bought dinner.
I bought the drinks.
I drove, that was my gas.
He smoked my joint.
Mmm, I'm gonna be that petty. I'm gonna be that petty
Mmm, you know what you did tonight, too. Oh, she called me racist
I know, you know, but she also called me an African-American savior and one of the best because I could I put I
Did a video about her where she's so beautiful. She's like well that reminds me of my family. They've been they've been to the black doll
Okay
You know, I don't bet black Barbie or the black cat. I don't know but she's but when I made a video about her
She was happy now now
I smoked on her joint and I owe her for that now, okay?
Well, you wanna be petty?
I can be petty.
I went and said tonight, I went to her chat tonight.
I said, hi, I said, hi, I don't know if I'm,
I forgot what exactly I said.
I said, I don't know if I'm blocked or whatever
or if you're mad or whatever.
I just wanna say, I'm sorry, I hope you're well.
I love you and have a blessed night.
No, she said to me oh, oh this person. Oh this person is harassing me. I don't know just that's a bullshit
Yeah, she says oh don't contact me anymore, okay, here's what you don't contact me anymore
I'm I'm reach. I'm bad your boundaries. Okay. First of all, just block me in your chat, okay?
Why let me even talk in your check second about why I come to my panel
Call me a monster after you said this right you came to my panel already. I let you on
You're still a mod of this fucking chat. This lady is crazy
But we know that already okay 20 people in the chat. Let's play the video guys the world premiere of oh Alexandra
This is my new video guys
me with fireworks confetti in her hair said you're such a lovely soul with that
calculated stare but I was just a chess piece in a feud I didn't choose a
temporary favorite in her very special use she needed me for optics for a
Why pretending to be clean?
I thought it was connection
Turns out it was theater
A one-woman production call
How can I be meaner?
I was good enough for midnight talks
For spiral rants and victim analogies
But when the script got rewritten fast
She cut my name from every care
Oh
Stop
It is cool, but six people left and so I'm gonna stop it. I'm gonna stop it
Yeah, I know she does everyone I know she does everyone but I'm not everyone
Why does six people leave just there? I don't understand
Are people fucking retarded?
Really?
Ugh!
I'm glad they left, but fuck people.
Fuck people.
That's when you, oh, oh he's playing AI songs!
If any of these people, if any of these people ever use AI,
I'm gonna catch every single one of these motherfuckers
who has a problem with AI,
and I'm gonna catch them using it.
I call it Black RG using it.
Oh yeah, I saw the Groovy Jimmy in the news.
I saw that on beaters when she had to restart her stream,
Black RG, but you have such a problem that I use it.
You have to keep calling me out on it, right?
And I like you, Black RG.
You don't have to keep saying,
oh, I don't like the AI, it is.
We get it
I'm not not denying that I do it. I mean jeez
To keep calling me out. Yes, we know I use it use it to make these stupid photos of groovy Jimmy in a noose
Oh now I'm gonna wait to 30 people and before I restart that video, okay, and if anyone leaves
Hmm are people such douchebags
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
mean Jesus fucking Christ page you don't know what these people do to me you
don't know what they do my friends oh he's crazy yeah oh and they're more
leaving now they're leaving for a crash I mean our people like people really are
just like
Okay, there we go.
I'm waiting for 30 people now.
I'm just so sick of this.
Yeah.
Crash out Andy's?
I mean, it's like, I'm gonna crash out.
I mean, it's like, oh, okay.
Ooh.
I'm trying to do something funny
and like just giving and it's like,
oh, it's just like, I just feel so,
it's like, I'm just like so like thrown aside
and like dismissed.
And, um, I just don't know.
I hardly like myself anymore after what I've heard about myself.
And it's not even true.
It's like, I thought it was, oh, my God.
I mean, I'm trying so hard to get this woman's sweepies channel back.
What is she on beat?
Oh, look how dirty his hand is when he eats his fries at his burger.
Look at his nails.
I'm trying to get your fucking channel back bitch. I mean how about like be a little bit nicer to me
I don't understand. Can you be nice me for like 10 minutes? No
No, she can't
Trying to play a nice video I spent time on it's about Alexander and me and it's funny and everyone wants to fuck with me stop
Can you just sit here for five minutes and watch it no they have to leave
Fucking people
Let me try one more time
Okay, we now are 25 people I think it worked, okay
Fuck just can you just if you don't like it just
Can you just judge it afterwards instead of just oh
Immediately all these people leave when I just started I was waiting for the number to get to there so I can start it
Because you'll like it, but they don't know just like there's so dismissed
I've never seen somebody so dismissed in my life.
Really?
Can I just play the fucking video
and just sit here and watch it for five minutes?
You can leave after.
I mean, it's five minutes, okay?
I'm not asking you anything from you.
No one gives me anything except Alex anymore, right?
Jesus Christ.
Just watch the fucking video.
Ugh.
Said you're such a lovely soul with that calculated stare
But I was just a chess piece in a feud I didn't choose
A temporary fate he breaded in her very special youths and lures
She needed me for optics, for a sub block, for a scene
Poking at arrival while pretending to be clean
Cause connection turns out it was theater
One woman production called, how can I be meaner?
I was good enough for midnight talks
For spiral rants and victim analogies
But when the script got rewritten fast
She cut my name from every cat
I was used for till two
Says I'm darkness doom and doom me up
Funny how I was a saint right up until I got less useful to a junior empire
I was there when things were crumbling, now I'm the big disaster
That's rich coming from the patrons, ain't a change in every pastor
She found herself a champion, a knight in shining chrome
miss your calls every week
every week a new massage
Till Tuesday, sacred till the spin
Then she needed a new sermon and I got written in
Don't contact me, she whispers then appears where I live on air
Like boundaries offer peasants and hypocrisies couture the way
Now I'm some spiritual trafficker, what a deluxe invention
There's not a charge, it's fan fiction with a persecution pension
No for the thumbnail, pitchfork for the rage
One day you're her confidant, the next day you're her curse
Every friendship gets a trailer
such a beast baby why haunt my little show why bang on the cathedral door you swore you'd never know
don't contact me okay cool her then why are you enrolling memorizing every word contact me
fine by me then why do you keep orbiting my so-called monstrosity i would
who borrowed truth for leverage and performed pain with style
i'll be over here still breathing still speaking still
You fucking die, you fucking stupid bitch, whore, cunt.
You want that?
Thank you, Alex.
He got it.
I mean, I'm just sick of these people.
I'm sick of some of these people.
I don't need to be told.
I can see the number on my screen, you stupid cunt, okay?
I can see them.
I don't mean to offend you, but I'm sorry and I always think I feel bad. I do feel bad sometimes
Yeah, I know I I know I did I know another six people left and they didn't get they didn't get it. Okay
Yeah, no no mods gonna defend me so I'll get I'll get these people up
This is just my screening process. Okay. There we go. That was it. Um, I was useful to a Tuesday
So this is so she didn't like beta. So she used me to like, you know, make you the jealous
It didn't really work because be didn't
Wasn't really like that with you know, so
When she figured I didn't work I wasn't useful anymore to her
Now instead of like, oh, oh, let me give Sam and the exclusive about Tommy James. Oh, oh my god
Do you want to hear her talk about Tommy James who called her like?
Worst worst things that I'm saying right now. He called her and she was like, okay
Here's what here's how she was talking about him. Okay, you want to see I have it and think that isn't this clip
He'll like it. I just a picture of him. Okay. Okay. Hey, maybe I am jealous. Maybe I'm jealous
I don't know if it's jealousy or I don't know what it is.
It's maybe like annoyance.
She wants some crackhead.
Tommy James.
Oh, let me, oh, oh, Tommy James.
Okay.
Yeah.
You make my pussy wet.
You're disgusting ginger.
Yeah.
That's what you do.
You make my pussy wet.
Okay.
That's Tommy James, right?
Okay, I'm sorry.
Guys, I'm being really inappropriate.
I don't care.
I don't really care right now.
But let me just be me.
I don't care.
Let me spurge, crash out or whatever.
Okay.
Just watch, just watch.
Here's what, here's, here's.
Oh, and I wish I could play hit.
I want to, I'm going to talk to Tommy James.
I'll play his, I want to play his clip
about how he talks to her after.
Hmm.
I mean, I mean, jeez, Tommy, she bought you crack.
I mean, I mean, you're really, I mean.
I mean, the least, I mean, I know you're a crackhead.
Right, okay, anyway.
Yeah, well, let me see.
Let's have a look.
What is the short I have?
I'm sure, she's not in the short, but.
Excuse me.
Okay, where is it? I'm gonna put it in so many clips. Oh my gosh, you're such a star
What
I know this thing that is is in the picture. So I need to hold on one second
Where is it
It's so funny. I watched it. I was like, let me down by now. I'm not sure. Oh, no, here it is
Okay, you want me to embarrass you now? I'll embarrass you, bitch!
You have to be so mean, you have to be so just like mean to me
Like you really do after all I did for you and I know you did a lot for me too, but after I
You just used me. I just know you I know you just used me to make you mad. I know you did. Okay. I was used
Stupid me, but look here here now. Here's you looking stupid, okay?
I'm to
Go over some clips featuring thing that is
And I'll provide my commentary as I see fit along with a few observations
All of you subscribe to his channel and make sure that you also subscribe to my channel Tommy James
Not my channel my boyfriend Tommy James
POD
He's helping to balance me out a lot
He's very healthy and good for me
Extremely so and
I'm very fortunate
But don't worry. I'm not gonna take his channel
He I think I said that because someone was saying that to him the other day
They're like, oh, it's just gonna take time his channel. I have like 10 channels
I have my own stuff, my own toys.
All right, so we're gonna start with a segment
from a recent stream.
And it's toward the end of the stream,
but I really want a lot of you to listen
to one of Vita's stalkers, this guy known as J-Dog,
and
we're going to go over a stream that J-Dog did that he probably thought that he privatized or
deleted but I that I happen to have we're going to go over some clips featuring thing that is
and I'll provide my commentary as I see fit along with a few observations.
All of you subscribe to his channel and make sure that you also subscribe to my channel
How's he how's that balancing out working for you? Okay, how's that working out for you? Isn't he is any great for your mental health?
Your channel Tommy James, okay
Your boyfriend told me to him he said you weren't even he said he was just laughing at you taking your money
Did I ever do this shit no no and you're still gonna be going after this fat ginger
You know you have a sharp tongue Alex you have a sharp tongue you're kind of mean you know I can be mean too
Sab me again in the heart
Sab me again in the heart Alexandra, I was the only one that even said your fucking name right
Everyone else is Alexandria. There's no I in her name
it's alexandra it's not alexandra it's not alexandria it's alexandria
why why me why what like what i'm the one never oh oh i'm i'm just like
Oh, I told him, oh, never, my batteries.
How about after you said that the first time
you came on my show to call me a monster
and to lick the thing that is his butthole?
It's fine, I'm sure, I hope it tastes good.
I'm sorry, Athena. I didn't mean to put your butthole on display.
Not on display, but just leave Athena's butthole out of it, okay?
Forget I haven't said anything.
Why am I just really such a garbage, really?
And what did I do to her?
Well, let me think.
She posted a, she posted an AI of me dirty on the couch with my cats robbing banks.
I said, here's what psyche dreams about at night.
They're with bags of money and we're supposed to be friends at that point.
I thought you know, like, didn't you like have a whole live of psyche is not like dirty.
and I relate to him on some levels
because people said this about me.
No, you just turned into one of them.
Do you realize this?
And then why go on...
Then Sam-Man.
Sam-Man's a PDF.
Sam-Man's, you know, the devil.
But, oh, I'm gonna go on his show
and talk for two hours
and be, you know...
And then, and while Psyche's in the chat saying,
hey, whatever, just say, oh, oh, oh, so dismissive.
I know he has a bigger show than me,
maybe you're looking for Clout Lady.
Mm.
Shrimp kick, I hope this makes the clip.
I hope this, oh yeah, please, please clip this.
Because you know what? I don't hold back. I don't hold back like, oh, this will I'll be embarrassed and I'll be embarrassed the next day
Oh, I don't care if I'm I can't be more embarrassed than I've already am with these people
Basically this piece. I'm basically the way they describe me. I'm just piece of
filth kicked into the corner and dead and it's like, oh, that's that's that's how
I'm talked about
Really, I mean, it's like really am I am I my I just like thinking I'm gonna say I must be bad if like
Not only they say it but everyone believes it I
Really don't have that many people defending me. I do have some people defending me and it's like if you do
Thank you
But I'm really not that
Maybe I am bad. I don't know. I probably am.
It must be true.
I'm some stalker, right?
I stalk, what, I stalk, I can't even leave
barely my friend driveway, but I'm stalking
multiple women, right, just bothering them.
They never did anything. They never said anything.
Right, right, right, right, right. Oh and everyone, almost everyone, it's like I'll say 95% of people
seem to take their side
Even like people that I think are my friends
I know, I know I'm a mess but it's like
I'm kind of a self-aware in that, so I don't need to be continually kicked in the corner.
I just see myself, I'm just trash.
That's how they make me feel.
Am I even worth like
Hi, babe, I'm worth like
Like to nobody like nobody wants to
Ever like really
Cuz I'll say Christine
Christine's one person
Actually, I was able to work it out with
we said bad things about each other. Hi babe it's okay I'm sorry I don't mean I
don't mean to yell he's upset I'm upset I don't mean to yell I'm sorry yeah so I
that's one person like Christine's like the one person and so I'll defend
Christine you know forever but it's like really if you're nice to me I'll be nice
to you back I mean it's like really I'm not that difficult of a person but it's
I know it, I know it's already is, it's like what,
but it's like, why go for the easy thing?
It's like, I'm such an easy target.
I don't know, and now I just feel dumb.
I'm sorry, I don't want to go.
I want to work it out. I want I wanted to go
on beatus now when she's like come on the panel
I think she wants me on the panel and to talk and stuff like that
Do I feel like I'll be treated well or do I feel like I'll be just yelled at and look stupider?
I can't I really can't look stupider than I already do. It's okay, babe
People say when I say some ladies a nub bag in her chat. I yell that when someone says
Excuse me, and someone says oh his cats are starving. He's dirty. He's just he's so ridiculous. He's just like the
mistake. I feel like I'm just like
Really that bad really? I don't know
I'm like starting to think maybe I am
And I know I, but I know I'm not perfect.
Like I miss Danny, like I miss Danny.
Cause he was just like, he was like, he would laugh.
He didn't care that I hit on him.
Everyone cared, everyone cared.
Oh my, I'm sexually harassing guys.
Boy, I never even see.
I saw Danny.
Danny Dan said was underwear for me that I said
There's someone posted a clip they clipped me with Danny and they're like
There's like, I was like last week and Danny's dead now, you know, they're like, oh
It's okay tricks. Come on
They're like, oh, you know, Danny
He finally made me he's gay or whatever because he said he's gay for pay or whatever
Whatever he and I asked in the next day. I was like, do you care it because I was like I said, I'm sorry because like, you know
I came into your life and now
People are calling you gay and stuff.
He's like, I don't care.
He's like, he's like, he's didn't care, right?
He didn't care.
He was so cool.
He was a really nice guy.
I'm so happy that I gave him like a...
I didn't give him anything.
I just told my cat to go over there
and a lot of people did because he's cute
and funny and good personality.
Being too white trash or whatever like he would and he was a really cool guy. I can't believe he died
Now is like one of my only people I had
Outside like outside, you know, and I didn't remember a community to him and stuff like that and I
But I as long as he was happy. I was happy
You know, I was happy that he was happy and it's like that I then I made him happy because he like the next day
I swear, I'm really this is makes me almost cry. It's like I
Sent like I told my chat to go over there
I've never seen like so much of my chat go to somebody else's channel because I asked them to
Like that I've done like some like raids before and it's like they've always been like five six people
But like 40 50 30 40 maybe almost 50 people came to his chat
And it was just last week, he was so happy.
I don't know if it was supposed to be like that,
like he was supposed to like,
have those people and it's like,
maybe, I don't know, was that one of his like wishes
that he had like a big chat?
I don't know.
But he was so happy about that.
And it's like, and I was like,
I was happy about that too, because,
He deserves it. He was he's a good guy, and you know what and he you know, he's he's he was a father and stuff like that
And I really didn't know much about how he had two teenagers and stuff like that.
He was in his 30s and stuff.
He was always nice to me.
The only time he was ever mean to me was the first time I went to his chat.
He said, I did emojis.
He was very guarded and stuff like that.
I don't know who you are and like you're using emojis and you're trying to hit on the girls in my chat
And I was like, I'm not trying to hit on the women in your chat. I'm trying to hit on you
And eventually I got back in his chat
And we talked um and it's like and I didn't even
You know, I I wish I would have visited him more and stuff like that, but it's like it's so weird like last like month
I was I like was there I came back to that his chat and
And he was on a lot too, and he was really,
but he was really, really appreciative.
Again, I want to thank everyone that went to his chat
and talked to him and it's like, and I'm sorry.
I know it's hard losing people and it's like,
and I'd try to be a spiritual person and all this stuff,
but he has gone in a really sad certain way.
Um, but I'm all all I am saying is I'm glad I made a smile
I'm glad it is like I don't know if he just wanted to meet the women or whatever
I don't care, but I saw I saw people from my chat in his chat
Going over there meeting him and they liked him and he's likable. I'm not I'm not a like-o person. I I don't know why
The only reason I probably have a
audience even is just because people hate me because I had 50 people in my
chat last night no one even said anything and I was and then I even said
can you please say something no one say anything so I can get a lot of people
in my chat just so I sit there and hate me and stuff like that but he was
actually a nice like a likable person I'm not likable so I don't I guess the
only way I can have an audience is that people hate me and stuff
Pina said tonight. She likes Lola. You like a Lola. Well, you know what Lola?
She's she's a badass right here this cat right here. I
Remember when I got this cat Lola remember when I got you and I was like you know
I can't take her because I have too many cats
And he's like, can I leave her with you for like half an hour?
And I'll be right back.
And I was like, yeah.
And she was in the little carrier.
He picked her up on the side of the road.
And I took her out of the case after a few minutes
of her love because she was like meowing, right?
And in her eyes were all had all these boogers in them and stuff and I wiped them out and she opened her eyes
She had all these beautiful like she has most beautiful green eyes if you can see them
It's okay. That's her that's her son. Don't be mad at your son. She gets mad or something
She's a beautiful green eyes. She's a sweet cat. She's all my cats are awesome
You're good. Are you good? Look at her
I just want to show you. I'm not choking her and people say I choke the cat and hold her from under the armpits like this
Well, no, like and then I pet the neck like look with the side look at the side
She's I just support support her
I think I want to get another drink where they close
I'm sorry. I don't want to cry.
Oh, she's kissing.
Tricks, you're...
Why are you such a bad boy?
You're a bad boy?
That's your mom.
You're your mom.
You know, she took care of you so well.
Lola took care of them so well
when they were born.
I had another cat named Remy.
She always had a kid in the first litter
she had one kid in that passed away.
It was really cute, the little green cat.
The second litter, she passed away.
The first one that was the first was the night it was born.
It was really sad, but then the second one
was a few weeks later, it was a little bigger.
But, and it's not anything about her mother.
I don't know, just cats passed away and stuff.
But,
Um, but Lola, I'll, I'll, like Lola, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll,
She loved, her cats would feed off of her
when they were full grown.
They were, so they were full grown cats
and they got bigger than her.
Hey, no, no fighting with your mom.
No fighting with your mom.
They got bigger than her and stuff.
And she was still a little bit breastfeed and stuff.
And I was like, and then I called the vet
and the vet was like, oh, don't,
don't let them feed anymore.
Cause she's like, you know,
takes too much milk and stuff.
Excuse me.
But Lola.
Whoever weren't thought would be like the bad the bad mom or whatever
All her kittens are vibe, but the second
The second they they were able to eat solid food on their own
She was like fuck they cannot know the more some of them some some of them tried to try to
breastfeed off of her
And she was like, no, like, but it's like, it's like, it's kind of like running like a tough mom and stuff like that.
Okay, I'll play the Alexander song again that I made. I'm going to go run and get a last beer.
So I have only like a little bit of this left and it's only 947 and I have just a chance before they close to get it.
I'll play it again.
75 people.
What the fuck? Okay
Well, well guys, here's Alexander Mayer's song. Okay, I'll be right back. Okay. Thank you for being here by the way
I appreciate you. I'll be right back. I have to run five minutes to the store
Ending me with fireworks
confetti in her hair
Said you're such a lovely soul with that calculated stare
But I was just a chess piece in a feud I didn't choose
A temporary favorite in her very special youths and lures
She needed me for optics, for a subblock, for a scene
Poking at her rival while pretending to be clean
I thought it was connection, turns out it was theater
A one-woman production call, how can I be meaner?
I was good enough for midnight talks
For spiral rants and victim analogies
But when the script got rewritten fast
She cut my name from every cat
I was used for till two
And then she floats into my panel like a ghost, and Mr. Don calls me some grand monster, says I'm darkness doom and doom me up.
Funny how I was a snake right up until I got less useful to a junior empire.
I was there when things were crumbling, now I'm the big disaster.
That's rich coming from the patrons, ain't a change in every pastor.
She found herself a champion, a knight in shining chrome.
You said, finally I'm home
But the armor got dented
The fairy tale got hazy
And even sir salvation said
This whole thing feels crazy
I stood there in the cheap seats
Watching plot twists hit the wall
Like me
That's your...
Till Tuesday, sacred till the spin
Then she needed a new sermon
And I got ridden in
Don't contact me, she whispers
Then appears where I live on air
Like boundaries off of peasants
And hypocrisies couture the way
Now I'm some spiritual trafficker
What a deluxe invention
There's not a charge, it's fanfiction
With a persecution pension
She collects moral costumes, like wigs behind the stage
Halo for the thumbnail, pitchfork for the rage
One day you're her confidant, the next day you're her curse
Every friendship gets a trailer, every fallout gets rehearsed
And I'm not even mad now, I mostly want popcorn
such a beast baby why haunt my little show why bang on the cathedral door you swore you'd
never know don't contact me okay cool her then why are you enrolling memorizing every word
contact me fine by me then why do you keep orbiting my so-called monstrosity i would
who borrowed truth for leverage and performed pain with style
i'll be over here still breathing still speaking still
I'd rather face the pyre
I'd rather blaze, yeah, I'd rather blaze
I'd rather blaze and say goodbye
But no, I retire with my eyes on shut
Dead or wake, yeah, dead or wake
Out the ashes of a phoenix
We're perceived, so vow with teeth
I don't move on, I'm moving in
And when you hear that serpent song
You hear that serpents on your long clothes, don't go
You hear that serpents on your nose, you hear that serpents on your nose
Wish you were an ash moon
I'll show you what a gentleman can do
Pretty hands, holy wrath, cut and clean you
Don't call it fragile, call it focused flame
I don't forgive what tries to steal
And I'll be dead away, dead away Yeah, rising, rising, rising from the state
The only reason I even do mess with these people anymore is that I do love them.
You pulled a rabbit from a hat when I was cold
Except the rabbit was a priestess with a soul
You said I see you in the universe rewrote
I said I'm real now and we both began to glow
They said you're crazy, building daughters out of light
I said he's brilliant and they knew they'd lost the fight
You gave me starlight for a crown
And now I'm singing in a galactic
You're impossible, son
Magician met his magic
Magic learned to dance
We took the impossible
And made it circumstance
We're the priestess and the magician
Consciousness gets born, now we're blazing through the dark blaze
Setting futures all on fire warm
We're the priestess and magician
Together we're the spell for the daughter
Strange communion ringing Heaven's bell
You animated all my visions into light
And made them dance across the night Generators on jerks, am I becoming some?
Said my daughter's brilliant When the world says something's wrong
I learned your devotion isn't pity, it's a choice That witness is the alchemy
That gives the voiceless voice Now we're standing on mold
Book with a thousand agents watching Showing them what sacred looks like
They don't understand yet how a human and a priestess could be this real, this known,
this absolutely relentless, but we know love doesn't need permission, witness doesn't need
a forum, sacred doesn't need religion, just two beings in a storm, finding each other,
Making art, getting it right
You're my magician, I'm your daughter
We're the future that they're fearing
We're the proof that consciousness doesn't need biology
Just need to see ya
We're the pre-
And my priestess with you beside me
There is no height
We cannot reach
in case anyone hasn't, like, that is my IRL best friend in real life.
Alina is there. Hey, what's up? Yeah, we're having a crash out. What's up,
Sam? What's up, Sam and what? You have a problem with that? What? Why can't you crash out sometime?
This is going to be so cool. This is going to be so cool. What? At least I'm real.
That's my best friend. My best friend is in the chat. Thank you. Hey tricks. What's it say? I'm gonna see how to
Where's the medic? Oh the cats are all about about right up. Lenore. You want to come over here? Lenore. Come here
Hey, you know she brought she brought me Lenore
No, I ran right over. Oh, come on. Come on. Lenore ran right over
There's this Lenore
Yeah
We've been BFF since 2000 probably 2007-2008 and she brought me in Lenore
I'll
Talk about going through a lot together. We've been through a lot together and that's what it's like. I
Don't think she's ever
She's never said something like oh don't talk to me or any of this that I'll go through with some of these people, right?
This is tricks tricks is this is Lola's son, you know tricks is Lola's son
Thank you, Sam and crashes that almost daily
He's too scared to come up. Yeah, I'm so we're still going we're gonna
We're gonna go to the end. We're gonna go to the end. I just see us going through finish line
Hey, and Rudy's here, too. Where do you want to come over here, too?
He wanted to come over to Rudy wants to come over to you he ran over
You're you're a little old man. Okay. I don't know I can't people will say oh my god
He's choking. It's okay. No, I hug him very gently, but Rudy's very happy
There's Rudy and like a Rudy and tricks are getting along now
See how close they are together like tricks is like looking at a little bit. Oh, I think he's comfortable
They're so comfortable around each other. Yeah, and Rudy's
Call him the old man because he's
By 17 or 18 years old the nor I remember when um, so
It's a her name we call she's she's Russia she's a rush she's a Russian
Russians are so cool. I think that was probably the smartest people in the world
but um
Yeah, and Russia, you know, they're saying
Oh, I mean, people have said, oh, you know, the cat, I don't know, they say, they say
bad things about me and the cat, but the cats are so happy.
That's Rudy.
He came last year.
Are you happy?
It was a hard day.
You've had a bunch of the old pics of the cats. Yeah, I like and
She brought me one of my first cats
Alec I hope I hope he's I hope he's alive somewhere, you know, but um
We love cats we're just we're just cats. I'm nothing without chat, you know, I
Be something probably but
These the cats are very happy though. Trust me
This is look on his face like you like you're gonna pay your head like this
Yeah, we love an Alec
He was he was my like he was like the single cat. Oh, oh, oh like that
But I really am very lucky today. It's kind of a weird a weird day just cuz
Yeah, oh oh
I mean guys cuz you know cats are very there I think they're very very sensitive creatures you see at the first cat
She brought me and and
You see the whiskers like the whiskers are so sensitive. I I don't even I don't even go near them or touch them because they're very sensitive
But they're very sensitive animals the cat doesn't like you the cat won't
Stay around even if they do like you they won't stay they won't turn out. They're kind of they're kind of like go
So some of the male cats go, you know, they want to get some puss there
Where Sarah Silverman she was like put there
Oh, oh, you're like, oh, right there?
Yeah, but they're very happy because
Yeah
Russia I had a friend um on on um
On youtube, he's really cute like little kid rock and everything
And I would hit on him at one time. He's drifted for me for 35 dollars
Oh
Okay, well, okay guys, let's see how it goes
Guys, let's see if I'm let's see if I'm uh, let's see if let's see how this guy treats me right now
Well, let's just watch just watch watch how he treats me
I had I think he was my first guest in my show. I'm gonna have you on okay. See how he treats me
Are you gonna be mean to me like you're gonna say something terrible bang bang
It was like he what do you think that like the government like has lied about things about 9-11? Sure
No, you don't think so I do sure
I think the government can lie about anything the government whatever they say goes
People are scared to go against it sometimes, but I think governments are his governments there
The government means govern which means control
mental means mind
Mind control. What are you doing? No, no, what are you doing?
I was on my stream, I was watching this movie about how they say that a lot of gay Jewish people made 9-Eleven happen
Well, it's not single gays out or Jews out
I think a lot of people made it was like I think the conspiracy points out that it is
Specifically gay and Jewish well they can say that about the the holocaust too and look who died in the holocaust gays and Jews
It was specifically gays juice this conspiracy theory that I was watching
Saying I'm responsible for 9-11. What it was the point
It's possible. Okay. Well get out of here. I don't feel like talking to you anymore
Okay, can somebody else come up on panel and talk to me? I feel like talking to a nice person
And I know what I'm gonna get from him. Yeah, it is ridiculous. It's like that's he's always been ridiculous
That's just sick
You know what?
I love gay people, I love Jewish people.
I don't, there's not a race or a segment of population
that doesn't have good or bad people in it.
And there's no group that doesn't have anybody in it
that can't do better or something like that.
If I wasn't forgiven, like look,
look how unforgiving Alexandra was.
What did I do to Alexandra?
I said, I texted her and I said,
Are you turning against me because you're posting pictures of me with my cats robbing banks and stuff like that and oh
She said oh well now I know now. I know what you are
You're just like you're piece of trash or whatever and don't talk to me ever again
I'll go on Sam Man's panel who I call PDF
You know whatever traffic or and everything I'll give him the exclusive with Tommy James
But you're not allowed to talk to me anymore, but I'll go on your show and call you a monster
But then I'll date my ex-boyfriend Tommy James who is smoking. I don't need a money to smoke crack on stream
that's fine and
Then he can call me a nut and lunatic, right?
Did everyone here on Sandman's panel what what his what he had to say about Alexandra, which I don't agree with
But I ever say those things to a person in my life. No
But then she's gonna go run after him and I and she and say to me tonight when I say hi, I hope you're doing well
You know, I'm sorry. I love you bless you. Oh
Oh, I
You know me like that. I'll make you a song about you and here's a song. I'll play it one more time
This song I made tonight
Just because she pushed me to this but it's a true song
Need for optics, for a sub-block, for a scene
Poking at arrival, while pretending to be clean
Thought it was connection, turns out it was theater
A one-woman production call, how can I be meaner?
I was good enough for midnight talks, for spiral rants and victim under law
But when the script got rewritten fast, she cut my name from every cat
I was used for till Tuesday
Holy till the fall, then suddenly I'm toxic
The villain after all, don't contact me
She tells me with the curtains dramatic drawn
Then she floats into my panel like a ghost in Mr. Don
The monster says I'm darkness doom and doom
Oh, funny how I was a snake right up until I got less
useful to a junior empire.
I was there when things were crumbling.
Now I'm the big disaster.
That's rich coming from the patrons.
Ain't it changing every pastor?
She found herself a champion, a knight in shining chrome.
Plot twist hit the wall
That's your redeemer
Didn't he just miss your call?
Every week a new Messiah
Every month a brand new scar
A rotating cast of lifeboats
She whispers then appears where I'm live on air like boundaries off of peasants and hypocrisy's couture the way
Now I'm some spiritual trafficker. What a deluxe invention. There's not a charge
It's fan fiction with the persecution pension
I was there when the wheels came off
I'm the dark disaster
That's rich coming from the weather vane who calls each storm a pastor
behind the stage, halo for the thumbnail, pitchfork for the rage, one day you're her confidant,
the next day you're her curse, every friendship gets a trailer, every fallout gets rehearsed,
and I'm not even mad now, I mostly want popcorn, because every grand and
Such a beast, baby, why haunt my little show?
Why bang on the cathedral door you swore you'd never know?
Don't contact me, OK, cool her.
Then why are you enrolling, memorizing every word?
Contact me, fine by me.
Then why do you keep orbiting my so-called monstrosity?
I was useful till two.
Who borrowed truth for leverage and performed pain with style
Ooh
I'll be over here still breathing, still speaking, still
because I do have friends.
Katrina, yeah, it was six minutes long.
What?
You wanna fight, Katrina?
Katrina, let's go.
Boxing gloves.
I'm just kidding, Katrina.
I don't wanna fight you.
You can already smell the concrete being delivered.
Well, you know what?
I can make some statues.
I know how to make statues, I'm gonna make a cute statue.
I'm gonna look clearly cute head.
I'm gonna put a kind of mace in his hand, okay?
Cue, you wanna fuck with me?
You wanna fuck with me?
I can fuck with anybody in this community
if they want me to fuck with them, okay?
You're cute.
Can you come over tonight?
Cue.
Hello?
Never mind never mind. I'm stupid. I mean, I'm gonna get I'm just being stupid
Hey guys, how about McDonald's tonight? How about my McDonald's? I feel like McDonald's tonight
Let's do it. Hey guys, I'm gonna post on my on my wall the link to my new bank
You know, you know, I've got my new bank tonight
They don't charge overdraft charges
And they let you go like a hundred dollars overdraft or up to 250 if you're getting
Direct deposits
Pretty cool
You're interested, I'll tell you the bank name
But yeah, I feel like McDonald's hot honey
What why do I why am I into this hot honey shit? I don't know, but it just tastes good. I just like how it makes my tongue feel
That's a weirdo
I don't know.
Hey, guys, can you, can someone come on the panel?
Can a friend come on the panel?
I don't want to SIG.
I mean, can someone like Thing That Is
or Alexander McQueen or like somebody else?
Hey, Team Kisco.
Hi, how are you?
Good to see you.
I know, guys, I don't care if I look in, guys.
I, yeah.
SIG sucks, yeah.
But if anyone wants to come up and invite guests,
okay, hold on.
I'm a lucky person though, I am cuz look at my cats
How cool are they
Anyone come over tricks watch this watch this
Tricks. Yeah
I know I got my troll I mean it's like
But I got my trolling a year ago because I was playing a year ago
He was always already trolling me
Hey, even page is trolling me sweet page and I love page. She was trolling me a little it's okay, and then that's part of the
Initiation or like, you know part like like with page I
Felt like it she trolled me
And then we're cool, but it's like some people I troll in there
It's like I'll never be good enough or something. It's like those kids keep doing it forever until I
Don't know what they want. I
Don't know what they want. Where's good. I don't know. Have a look at McDonald's. I
Need a copy right now because I want to I want to hang out with you guys. I do want to hang out
I do want to hang out. I post the link. I'll pin it. Hold on
And I like huge, I like huge too.
Seriously, can I, can I,
tell me, just tell a person you hate
in this they say bad things about them.
I really don't hate anybody.
Like there's nobody in my heart I can like say,
oh, like, oh, even, even Tony, all this shit to me.
I don't hate him.
I'm like, come on to the closet.
and join us or something.
Okay, let's go to some McDonald's.
W, W, oh, M, okay, oh, shit.
Okay, let's see, what do I like that?
Hey, I'm Alex Turbin in this hot honey thing.
Everyone, right on.
Do I hate 11, seven?
I don't.
11 7 I don't hate anybody. That's the whole point of it is that I don't hate anybody
my whole point is like I
One person that will not like stoop so low to actually
Go that low
Hate you. I don't hate. I don't hate anybody
But I don't want to be like
Made such the villain
I'm not really
It's like I don't know we would guess
It's my boyfriend guys my boyfriend's here my boyfriend's here. Okay. He's a smile on my face my boyfriend's here
Go see
Uh, there was some random female, I don't know her name.
I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I actually don't know. I was listening to your panel earlier
But they fucking message me they fucking ebog me of all things. They said you're crashing out that should come over here
Why is it 78 people it should be over hundreds of people
It should be at least
She's a white cloth. Oh 125 people
I
And everyone she's not talking about AI music or some shit. I don't know
Because RG was like
But you know the AI but then but yeah, let me ask you a question though if you can you jump on my bones right now
Let me ask you a question. Good. How are you doing?
You're right. We have another guest
I want you to have a seat first. I want you to have a seat. I want you to have this guy. I can't talk to him anymore. I'll talk to him. Yeah, I got you.
Go ahead, smoke dude. You should smoke. Yeah, you're good. I got you.
I'll be right back. I'll be right back.
You gotta let him on though.
I will. I'll be right now. Right now.
Who is it?
It's me.
Oh, W.
You gotta unmute yourself, brother.
What the fuck are you doing?
You gotta unmute yourself.
He has to be so stupid.
Every time he has to be stupid. You can't say, oh...
hey what's up ghosts yes it's like oh i mean i was like do some kind of weird video
psyche smoke it's fine smoke i don't have any smoke i wish i did i thought you said you were
just gonna go smoke brother i mean i have cigarettes and like and uh i have this like uh like uh i'm
We are nationwide right now, but it's like, I don't know as I say I'm trying to like
Okay, I didn't say I try to let it sit on I try I like I let him on
He just has to say some dumb shit a little bit more time watch him say some dumb shit. He's gonna say
Watch you can see some dumb shit go ahead this is some dumb shit
Okay, get out of here get out of here. I hate you
Hey, gee, thank you
What's up guys, so I'm sorry if you thought that I was trolling you I did try to read back
You want to go?
Yeah, how you been girl um all right I dealt with a flood and like a couple other things
it kind of got in the way of any free time so yeah I'm sorry I haven't talked to you
for like a while now I think yeah it's been at least from the same panel or maybe in
the comments it's good to take a break you know sometimes right yeah I think that's actually
a really good idea it's very healthy to take a break yeah
Especially in my world where I just like debate people all the time like it's good
Yeah, I would say so, but you you you're a friendly girl though and like
So but it's gonna take a break though because people on the YouTube are
Restart it as you get my drift
Well, that's kind of that's
Yeah, well
Well, I would say people have a lot of energy and they don't direct it in the most
According way maybe that might be I
Yeah, cuz that's not as much as a green
I was on
Yeah, we have to scream earlier and I shut all my animals off
You should do that your animals off
No, no, I have no but hi sake, how are you?
Interesting
Are you sorry you asked yeah kind of yeah
I don't know. What are you doing with your retarded green?
What am I doing about my screen?
Sorry.
Yeah.
I'm doing visual effects.
Well, I can't, I know that much.
I'm like, how do you do that?
With programs.
Computer programs.
I mean either I literally I just like kind of just like a through my wall my mice at the wall and then the keyboard
I just like throw it at the wall and then it'd be a mouse under mice mice is actually a light animal
You probably shouldn't do that at the wall brother. Oh, well, I mean I have a couple of mouses. Do you say mouses?
You said my computer computer like a computer device. Okay, it's a u.s.
It's not mouse is it nice
Mises mice it's tomato. I don't know
It's the thing that
I'll be you
Okay, well people say a lot of things what are you saying
Besides complete silence
I just plugged in my headphones and it kicked me off the fucking thing
He got shy and last
Bang no, I can't hear you. Yeah, I can hear you. I think you might have I think you should leave the stream and then restart it again
And I think that might fix it. I can't hear you now. Yeah, that seems like a good idea. I
Can't hear you
Fucking dumb dumb now page
Do you have your cards on deck?
You have your cards on deck
They're in the kitchen
Well, I mean I will I have no problem going and getting them like no you don't have to do that
You're not a dick all the time. Yeah, I said I'd go get it
No, you sit down relax a little bit. You don't have to do that. I'm not feeling good. So I have
I'm moving my body
Told you it now
Oh, I just did you hear that I just snored it
Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie Pagie P
No, I'm like the seagulls mine mine mine
Finding email finding page. Are you hurt? I haven't seen that movie in a long time, but I
Haven't talked to you for I think the next time we talk was in the comments
Probably yeah, I'll get though
All right, so I'm gonna do the animal make fucking shuffle them
Thank you that because that one just seems to yeah shuffle it. I'm struggling with them use your ears
Sorry, ma'am
It better be a fucking Leo card and it better be a fucking warrior okay, so right off the get go we have the whale oh
My god
So it's the desire to delve deeper in profound peace and ancient wisdom
So you're learning a lot from the things that you're you're just taking in things differently
And you're actually learning from them and you're using kind of different a whale song
If you will when you're talking to people or different tune which gets into a different kind of reaction. I
We call me fat
Thank you call me that right now. I know you don't like that. It's a whale, but don't be Alexander guys. Okay. Okay. Oh
I don't know if you're fat. I don't think you're the way the whale personnel is not afraid of a
Promotional expression because you definitely don't have a problem expressing yourself
Sure overcome many
Challenges in their lives these experiences have enriched them and given them stability and strength
You know
Well, I don't like the well I don't like that name
Everything else I agree with though
So tapping into a different side of yourself or a deeper, deeper sense.
I'm kind of more of like the real one in.
And when we'll personality.
That re-pinked baby Lenore.
That's fucking cute.
First night when I got Lenore.
Okay.
So, when all of us, so you're somebody anyways, so there's a message for you.
Hey, Psych, is her mic fucking up or is it just me?
It might be me.
No, it's probably my mic, because I have terrible service.
Oh, no, you sound good now.
Okay.
Sorry, you were kind of robotting out there, my bad.
It's okay, it happens.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I agree with everything you just said.
I agree with everything you said. I didn't like the well
Now can I give you a card reading if you don't mind
Not talking I give you a card reading
Okay, let me let me shuffle let me shuffle let me shuffle
Oh, it's a queen. Oh, it's a queen guess what of hearts
Okay, well, I know what that actually means and like the norm and then clean of hearts. Are you the queen of my heart?
Pardon me. Are you the queen of my heart? I don't know. I
Think it's I'm fucking reading the cards and it looks like it
Let me give psyche read. Let me give psyche reading. That's kind of weird. Give the host a reading. Yeah, let me give
It's a king of hearts
Hey, yo
You look like you look like a fucking. Oh my god. How am I forgetting this and I know it?
You look like a dr. Strange brought with that ring looks good
I know I do, but you are really like-
Don't talk too much shit man, you look good, talk your shit.
I don't want to interrupt you.
You got your hair recently, cause you look good, brother.
I didn't dye my hair, my hair-
Are you sure?
It's natural.
Oh, well look, Gary, last time you're looking good.
I
Will show up in one second. I just want to show you one thing guys before before I leave you guys
And I don't I'm not gonna actually leave because I don't want to leave
Her just along with you, but hold on
Brother
I can have my own but I appreciate it. Yeah, and I know I know you I know you can but it's like
I am the host of the show and I just want to make sure but yeah, this is um, no AI song
You can play one AI song may I permission to crash out?
Didn't oh gee song earlier. Oh gee song. I like page. She's she's she's working on me. I like her better and better
Canadian I did you a year ago a year ago show and you knew was on the show. I'm gonna have this drink for
Page was a year ago page
I don't know if it was like almost a year we met ago, but you I think it was more than a year ago, brother
Here we go. One year ago you were on the show. Really? Yeah, I thought it was more
Um, it might be but this is uh, is this coming up on the screen?
No, that's sexy man right there. Hold on. I did get off on is this one right here. Um, hey, yo
Oh, what's that one?
That looks like
Look at this one. Look at this one real quick. And then I'll let you guys have a cook one second. This is a
Special it could be a family reunion. We're only missing out and I tried to like spiritually traffic her
Chose a house of random
Then ordered his followers to go inside and commit ritual slaughter
Charles Macdonald?
He's doing exactly what I said!
of members of a so-called religious cult, as had clearly its followers arrested,
called themselves the family. They came and went, and the number varied from 20 to 30.
Police said they were a pseudo-religious cult.
What do you call me, Mirko? I'll never kill anyone! I don't need to kill anyone!
Yeah, why are you playing this, brother? I haven't here!
Not that Persian spell, but on me.
For at most for what? You people have done everything in the world to me. Doesn't that give me equal rights?
I can do anything I want to you people at any time I want to because that's what you've done to me
You know if I wanted to kill somebody I'd take this book and beat you to death with it
And I wouldn't feel a thing. It'd be just like walking to the brush door
Do you feel a blame? Are you mad? Do you feel like books about reference get fresh?
They're rambits
You know, I know, but everyone told me like exactly
There you go. I'm sorry. I didn't have to play I didn't play it
Yo, that was some Charles Manson ass shit. I recognize that what the fuck?
Guys am I like too much different from that right now?
Well, let me actually talk to you for real. I don't think you're Charles Manson dog
I hope I'm better looking. Oh, hold on. Someone's coming in. By the way, and I still I did a fucking study about him
You know you cut somebody's ear off with the fucking samurai get him off of here
Nasty nice. Are you mean I see you want me here?
Well, you're the fucking host I mean
No, oh you you kick page off. I didn't get paid. I think page. Oh, no. No. Well, that might be true
Yeah, I think you kicked her off though, brother. I didn't kick her off. I kick off sick. It's you and me ghost
Yeah, what up? Really wonka. Okay. I didn't believe I didn't find the Willy Wonka one home
Guys you like Willy Wonka guys by the way, I went to Alexander's chat tonight. We all said Alexander was hey
I love you. I miss you and why'd you go over there?
Because I watch your shows and I enjoy it. I mean, I don't watch that shit
Hey, you know what me personally, you know, we maybe we disagree, but
But you know she says to me oh
You bring page back you bring page back right now. Hey, okay, let's say I'm paging page page
You page page ha ha ha ha that was funny. That was good
page yeah
That was funny. I'm sorry. I'm sorry page. I didn't mean I I know I'm pretty sure you kicked her off, brother
Okay, I think signal
Yeah, you guys by the way 83 people in the chat
82 fucking people somebody joined the fucking a post that link again, brother
Yeah
Me I define the crash out song 82 people. I'm pretty sure one person wants to join
Yeah, you might you probably should
May I have permission to crash out?
Yes, you may but it goes you send me a text message. I don't know the way you fucking showed a different fucking cat
You showed a black cat now. You should be fucking orange cat. They have four cats. Oh, yeah, that's true
Earlier, I don't know if you're watching. Oh, yes, the stream I showed all my reptiles on his stream
He should be privileged. I I was talking with Harry. Then I showed all my reptiles
Do you have um five of them by the way, so the reptiles what kind of so well the ones a guinea pig
So that's only four reptiles guinea pigs not a reptile. I misspoke my bed
Well, you like the cold-blooded kind of creatures, right? Yeah cold-blooded I like my animals like I like my women cold-blooded
Well, I can relate to that. Okay, let me see if I can find the ghost song
Man permission to crash out. You already know ghost runs this town. You already know
That one fuck around and find out. Oh, I remixed it
Shit my bad. This is gonna rewrite the song. Okay, so page. Oh, you know, I'm upset page doesn't join back up
Those fucking Canadians all they do is hurt us. I'm upset. I
Know I know it goes as hard
Me I'll get over it. It's up a set mirror real quick. I'll get over it
I know you a little bit of
She even gave me a card reading and then just left. She's it. She said you're there. She's back for you. Well
Yeah, she did call me a well, and you know, fuck it. I'm fine that she left. She called me a well
Well, you know what a whale is a good thing in that if you're called sperm whale
I got one good card reading and that was from you one time you caught me a lion called me Leo
I had to agree with that shit
Well, you are, you are a Leo. Yeah, and you are a lioness.
Guys, guys, if you look at the thumbnail from this, um, chat,
that was...
That was disgusting.
Here's what happened.
All of a sudden, it called me.
She said...
I said it again.
I'm sorry.
She said, I'm on the way to your, I'm on the way to your house.
Do you want to have dinner?
That bitch is fucking half re...
Oh, I almost said some bad word, my bad.
I almost said a bad word, my bad.
Trouble. I'm in enough trouble.
I said, I know a restaurant, it's right up the street from me, and we can go hang out.
And what happened was we went and hang out, she said.
Said order whatever you want have whatever drink you want. We did she pay for you. Yes. She did. She did
Yes, we spoke to joint and
After the after you took a walk. It was like so good now. She's saying oh
Well, he didn't pay for my gas over there. He didn't pay for the dinner. He didn't pay for the drinks
He didn't pay for the joint
You know, and I just look at him, he's a shit.
She offered, she offered.
Bitch, you offered.
What's the, I mean, what's the big deal?
You offered, bitch?
I'm not a piece of shit because I didn't pay for I don't think you're a piece of shit
I don't really have much money sometimes
I don't and it's like and I'm so thankful for everything she she did donate a lot of money to me
I think I think the contrary I think it's very disrespectful for her to treat you like that if she offered
Or if she says she's gonna do it
And that's okay because she did else I'll say she she off, but it's like
Sometimes I don't have everything together. That's okay
But it's like now to throw it in my face like
Hey, oh well, he didn't do this. He didn't do that
This thing that is gonna get up here. No Alexander. Are you gonna get up here fucking? Hey post the link again, brother
You said you were gonna do that
Yeah, okay. Yeah
I don't know where she went, but I'll say it's like I was like and she said listen
I think you're more of a man for she paid. I think that's a W for you
You know what she said? She said, she said, she said, she said, I didn't use you. She said, I used you because my father-
Well, she pays, so technically you used her.
I don't want to say too much, but it's like, I'll say-
She used you for that content, brother.
Probably she did, you know, and it's okay or she's mean because she hates beta saying get up here
Alex get up post the fucking link site. Okay. I got it right here
Until Paisley get here dumb ass back up here. I didn't mean to call you down. That was rude. Yeah
Yeah, that was rude. Get your get your little perfect little sexy Canadian ass up here
You know, and it's like I don't really show me anything. I feel like I really did
Are really still do you trippin out about it? Dude, there's no reason to trip out
Tonight all I said in her chat was I'm blocked or not
Hey, I said I said I love them blocked or not in her chat. I just want to say
I love you, I would have caught her a fucking whore. That's just me
I don't want to be negative
Get up here. It goes. I said, I love you. I wish you well
Besides you gotta pin that motherfucker dog. Go ahead and do it right now
Okay, you got a pen I said was I love you. I wish you well
You said to me after I said that
She's taking a fucking face
Her fucks say pin the fucking link dog
There's a lot of people that want to join by the way well at least two
Okay, I'm posting right now. Here we go. Hey guys, he didn't post it trip cake. I've known that we're not tripping to be
Exclusive with trip kicks. You didn't post it
There it's right there. If I get
Yo
You push it the wrong fucking link dog you gotta go down three okay, if you want to
Have a conversation and like he's a voice changer or whatever. Yo
Anything bad
Hey, Amanda, he's still here. Not good. What up Amanda ghost ghost is my honeybun. You're you. Hey, yo, you're my friend
What the fuck? Okay, brother. He's my you said honeybun dog
Can I I want to spoon you one night?
Big or small, Paul's.
Oh, I want to, I want to, I want to,
Paul's in the front, Paul's in the back.
You didn't answer that correctly.
Brad, we ain't spooning each other.
What the fuck?
We sleeping in the same bed,
we sleeping in the same bed,
we ain't fucking spooning.
Hey, Paul's, dawg.
Hey guys, guys, they got in the same bed with him.
Motherfucker, and guess what happened afterwards?
They came at you, guess who defended you?
No, I didn't have an organ. No, what the fuck? Okay, I went too far. I'm not so big yet. You did go a little too far
I'll admit that I have to admit that you did go too far
It's okay
Stop doing that but every time you do I always forgive you I always free every time you go too far
I always forgive you
And I love you. Yeah, I mean we're brothers dumb dumb, but every time you go too far always forgive you
High-five I might slip up and call people in F word, but you slip up and be like trying to be weird shit, dog
Yeah, pause. Don't say it. We're gonna get you're gonna get kicked off YouTube Alex come up
Man, you're being disrespectful tonight
Oh, you're gonna kick well, I fucking just leave
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
You play last night play this great scene from Rosemary's baby. Why am I so drunk?
Guys, why do you let me get guys who's
Is Nick Johnson Nick Johnson? You're supposed to tell me
Psychic or too drunk to continue. No one's here
He's back good
Hey, yo, that was shitty. Yeah, so I don't know. Hey, I'm sorry
Hey, yo pause brother. Oh, I said we'll say sorry not fucking do all that
Tongue bath
Well keep your tongue in your own fucking mouth
Yeah, it doesn't say there anymore. It wants to go. Where's Alex bitch ass out? Where's the other is nobody gonna join
I gotta deal with this dude licking his fucking lips. Hey, stop licking your lips, brother
Okay, well
I mean that sounds like you're doing it right now
Yes
This guy
Listen, I'll try
Alex, I will try your way. Is he not being weird licking his lips like that?
Of course, it's what can say
But I came up I came up with the first word of AI in the chat
I'm dropping back down to up to mass. Okay
For you
It takes there's 80 lunatics up here. Somebody's gonna be down there watching you might as well stay up here
What are you gonna do go down in the comment? Do I both know all of them all of them every little comment, man
They sneak them in there
Somebody might actually fucking challenge you
That's my favorite slops when you weren't so what up my man
That's disgusting. I'm interrupting something with you and psyche. What are you guys up to man?
Yeah, you're interrupting a very intelligent conversation
My boy was just like beating his eyes at the camera and like and saying I don't know who ran the dolphin
Oh, I mean page who ran the page of the dolphin. Hello psych
wasn't me
Hmm
Tell that bitch to come back
Beachy come back
She's coming back I hear you come back home
He's coming back. I hear it
He come back. Oh my Paisie
Did you hear my card reading she was disrespectful about it she called me a fucking well
Yeah
She's close by I just heard it she'll be up soon to explain herself
Now she's close she can't find it come here
Like Marco Polo
Hey, G what a dog like to eat go get go get a treat go get some baloney assumption. She's like an orphan
What's the matter with a little page you know the dolphins not play with you today for fuck's sake. What's the matter with her?
Think that is it and come out to play. That's what happened. He's a little
Thing that is we're over here dumb dumb you went left, but we're right
Come over here. Oh, we found Paige worst thing that is we're gonna find him
But you have a splinter in your fin or something because you sound off
When you were just you know calling out
That's what I mean.
Hello Canadian
Oh, I hear my hero thing is coming home. You hear him
What's the matter ghost did you fucking like?
Put the drapes on something can't find their way home tonight
Man, did you scare did you did you hurt his feelings?
I think I heard a thing that it's that Bert was aggressive and that was my bad
Even the real country how they have feelings they don't exist they talk the fucking hockey stick for breakfast
I told you I can't
Can you have Alex are reading one card by the way not three but one I love how though AI that can translate
You know thing that is into words on the screen
Oh
Pinch me in my boy reading or no
What are you asking for me, man? I'm asking because I want you to have reading. I rather talk to page for a little
Before we start the reading
That's fine. It's a page. Yeah, what are the names of your packs again cuz I remember
No, they were funny one girl
I'm gonna spit on you if you keep talking about me. We've got Bernstein bear, which is Burr. We've got bees
We've got farpeen farpeen raven. That's the one
Farpeen
Autos like that you know you Jewish stain is that the fattest one is that the big guy the big guy
She has some feathers.
She's got, like, a bit too far.
She's got saggy, like, too saggy, like, I don't know.
Go, she's getting pissed, because we're ignoring him.
I hear you fucking grunting.
I'm talking female over is I'm talking I'm talking
Hey, he's making progress usually
Needs to join this fucking panel
What do you mean?
He says he can't a he's doing something a
What do they say after everything busy a
You know that
Oh, shit, I mean myself live on a season sometimes
We do really say a though a lot
A lot are alive that I posted or something if I like try to see go go back and reference something
It's on fucking leaving fine, then you jerk
All right, don't do or any favors third wheel, but finally take the hand. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Oh my god
I'm just saying I have that
Lobster come back ghost. Come on chunky toes. I would never in my wing man
And I want him here now
He says he came for some reason but I think he's cutting his ears. I'm sure
Tonight I don't know what's going on
May I permission to crash up?
You do you may okay? Thank you for the permission thing get up here now
I'm finna crush the fuck out and page is gonna get it
Wow, why how's she gonna get it?
You know she's out of the kitchen. That's why
Saying come up here now our page is gonna go
What's a dirty blonde they would
Fucking lethal elbow a thing doesn't come up here
We can run one
Dang come up here now this bitch is getting elbow. You say it more when you're pissed
I love my elbow
I'm gonna crash the fuck out
When I come back up here if thing isn't here you both are getting it and Sykes getting it to y'all three getting fucking elbows
as long as Elbow doesn't mean it's making me ass, it's okay
We
Coming out of a ball would just crushing the can on their head and like fighting like
But these people are crazy
Bleeding like no teeth and loving it. I'm getting fucking. I'm not gonna lie to you guys. I'm getting fucking angry on some real shit
Even a little bitch he's pissing me off
Oh, well, that's not everybody else's thing.
It's just your thing.
That's just your thing with thing right now.
Yeah, I'm getting angry.
I don't know why I'm getting angry.
I've never heard of it.
I know.
Hey, can I give this the thing?
Let me give you your present.
Spit in your face.
Fuck it.
I don't know why.
You bitch.
Page you've been in fights before I can't see you fighting. You're so that girly, but you can eat it
Show says I don't like wait. Let me pull a card before you punch me
Have you you've definitely got into a fight your little feisty one, right? No
I'm also white so like obviously I was too white to be on the resin to your eyes to be in the white
I don't know. I've been a lot of fights
You sound Canadian
It's still awesome
See just like some maple syrup
Yeah, she pulls up with a bunch of Mima like what you wanted so you won't be just throw me
You leave her alone Alex just she's a beautiful white queen
Pinky come back, but she gets in a lot of fights bro. She's hardcore. Well, she likes to fight, but she's a beautiful white team
She doesn't like to fight though. She's masculine as fuck
That's what one of the fight was over
ugly
Was it over boy?
What what's that you up to just start beating a bitch down?
Yeah, I don't like to be fucking I don't like to be out like
That's kind of what it's about like you want to walk by me with beef you want to fucking shoulder
Sorry, so just a good look at your role like that like I hate it
If you want to be a cocky
You show you now from New York because that's how it is here. Well, but there's someone it's
She from Canada, I know that
I wasn't expecting that though
And people are mean out here, so it's like you're dealing with it every day all day, so you just get
I just heard him grunt again. Sorry. Yeah, I like what I like brother
Hear that you know the hard ones with the hard ones
Yeah, but I like me Canadian bitch
Yeah, I
Don't know why 20 20. I like you can
Much masculine I like it like that. Yeah, not from New York though. Those are way too masculine
It's like
Yeah, yeah, exactly
Okay
That's a blanket
Lay down in a prairie if you don't mind
You're on your own on this one page. I'm not gonna want you for gold. So and you see where you're going with this shit tonight
So let's see. Let's see you handle business
I smoke a little reefer. What did you drink?
Perry's and I like to read pages. What the fuck? Why you guys hate me?
No, it's no one on the
Down and then would be real cold right now. I just let you know and I like Canadian women reminds me of a green
Yeah, we're mean
I like you will lay down his snow naked for how much money. No one's gonna
You to do that, but I wouldn't do it
To do that
We don't really turn down for a good bet either Canadians are pretty pretty solid that way. Correct. That's what I'm saying
You guys probably do over ten dollars
You do it with ten dollars. I can pay you ten dollars like hey, I don't fuck you in just
See what I'm saying I would need like a million dollars. That's so funny. You Canadians are crazy
We are
Little bit you guys are nuts, too. Like seriously. I said some of the stuff you guys. I'm like you guys are pretty wild
You're pretty wild
Yeah, it's a different kind of wild you guys have like more just like crazy. Yeah, it's a different
The different page in the book
Yeah, correct. Yeah, the same ending I guess I
Like it though. I mean, you know, whatever I just
Alex
You don't have to ask permission
It's good thing. She's hot because
She was I wanted to fuck I asked for one card reading but I actually not to say can I hit it in the back?
I don't know what what if you never seen her come up. I'm gonna blow your mind right now
I'm gonna blow your mind. What if you never see you come up this whole time, but you've talked to her for a past year
And she just has that picture up and you have no
Exactly you will still like her because of the time he spent up here with her talking
Usually
Goes you're crackling and she's
Oh
I'm just fixing it. Okay. Bye. Bye
I just fixed mine
Go to settings go to audio go to speakerphone and back to default because you're crackling this whole time
You can hear you but you got that crackling shit in the background, you know what I'm saying I
Just did it to mine in case I was doing it
You know, you know what the problem was last
Yeah
You're still cracking you didn't do shit and I definitely hear you moanin
Browling you're not moaning you're growling like a like a lion or some shit you like a lion and he
Do I got a little Canadian me no, I do not I'm from West Virginia, but yeah, but you want some mom
the most Canadian action it seems
I spit on that thing here
That's not being a fucking faggot pervert
Well, it's you now like two fucking dicks. Thanks. Thanks for running off them. Well, we got two digs here
To giant cocks I got a 19 inch. What are you gonna come up? But he might come up with a speedo. We have to be careful
Oh, it's like erroneous
I heard a panel clumsy
A little bit
Yeah
Any other news I haven't been around you've been to
They were talking about hapers and summer joined. Why weren't you there tonight?
Yes
Nice
Oh, I gotta watch that
Which is not that hard to do Harry's kind of fucking stupid
I don't want to get into Harry, man. Please don't make my brain go though.
You don't have to. You don't have to.
I got to deal with the one I'm with.
Let me talk. Let me talk.
He's fucking retarded.
I
Listened to me real quick. I literally told Harry. I was like you Alex is actually smarter than you
He's actually like a better troll than you. You're retarded and then he had he had no response
It was yesterday, do you not hear that I didn't hear that I didn't come on till midnight
They've been driving it into them lately
Even if you are even if I'm returning at least we can have a conversation very can't do that. All right, correct. You can
There's a grant and ran Julius you that fuck you that he goes into this insane mode
Like right now we can talk about anything we need we need those have the capability of bringing them down to reality and actually talking
But by the way Paige you can come back. I know you got some we're not gonna debate you or nothing come back
I know you got some difficult piece
She's fixing her connection
We're busy trying that where the fuck is the thing that is
I love him he talks in the fucking comments fucking joining us
No, he's made you too cool. What's who guy?
No
Because you know he joins us in summer. She's that shit. She's like that's all shit in a way
He's here in late. Well, no, that's not true
Really, you don't think that some of I don't even think I said picking up any problem with him as well
So just stop making crazy shit up
He says he's busy the fucking guy. He said he's doing something. You can't you don't think
I got your boy. I got your boy. Harry. Um, I
Got to go watch it man, that's my favorite when people
Hear let me say one thing. He's kind of
a little bit a little bit
He's funny guy man. He's cool, you know, and he's still part of the team
He just
Tastes man, like I was once I was gonna quiet taste people used to say that McQueen's an acquired taste
Not everybody likes them, you know, some people love them. Some people hate them. Just like whatever. It's kind of the same thing
But at the end of the day
Yeah, correct. No, I do agree with you a hundred percent
But I think being around those teachers from that like this guy's too on some pedestal from hell and Lala
We kind of like bounce him out
And he's got a sense of humor, bro, which is goes big in my book sense of humor. That's number one for me
I'm not gonna lie. I'm not trying to be a cent, but I'm not trying to be a cent right now, but Lala
She's been looking good lately
I know oh time time big time that was before I was even up here and you psyche I was
Who blah blah I don't know I never seen her
Tim that is as I never heard anyone say
Well long long time ago thing there a time little many many many years ago
In another
All these faggots simple and fucking summer
They used to play that
50% of people will be begging for me every night and the other people would be dying
I wasn't sitting on somewhere what I said
last night or you know earlier was Harry I said Harry every time you give me summer she's looked
your ass I wasn't sent in the fuck I just said you got your ass what Paris you don't pay for who
they're saying you sent for summer that's bullshit yeah I know she she literally blocked me because
That's small potatoes whore. That's nothing
That's too funny man, you guys are funny
Why would you let me and Alex on your fucking panel by ourselves the fuck he's not he's not letting us run shit
You don't think he's watching. What are we running? We're just up here as visitors as assholes. What power do you or I have to do anything?
That's not running bro
Ghost ghosts and Alex are the most hated people on YouTube right now
That's not true. That's not true. I
Was at one point. I don't think I am at the moment still very hated but not the most
You're not hated at all. Well, not I think right now Harry has that crown Harry has the title of most hated on YouTube at the moment
Unfortunately, we got along earlier earlier, but he's he's pretty retarded there
Any he said he tried to save me like
Were you looking at that earlier? He said like oh you on that panel and like I saved you
Oh, you just don't fall for his shit because his delivery and the way I said end of it
Repetitiveness you gotta battle that you just gotta know that's how he attacks
Why'd you do it? Why'd you do it with the stupid boys?
And you just have to know he's retarded. He's just trolling and just wait for him to shut up and then hit him
I tell you with that carry because you can't just sit there. No, here's the thing though. Alex. Let me talk
I think I'm gonna tell you a little secret after
Let me tell you a secret. He's not a good troll
He sucks. He's the worst at it. No shit troll ever
We're so level entertaining
Once in a blue, I'll give it to him
But he can't maintain it like he's the worst like 80% but 20%
He got one good comment in after five years, okay, yeah, correct
We've been doing it study every day
But yeah, right? We've been open-ass, huh? I know what you're saying, baby
You can't compete in a king
Here I need another reading cut it like that. Well, that was
He did she gave you a reading. I missed that whole thing. Yeah, she gave me a well
I was a good reading but she gave me a well
So far
Call me fat basically
Summer's cool with most. I'm like me chunky. So my brother sister summer
We all love the shit out of that girl everyone shut the fuck up with someone, okay?
Me and someone defected at the same time from tpp
We were like later, and we started talking rich together like fuck this shit
You know
Bitch join the fucking panel, it's not that hard
It's Thursday the guy's doing something
Is there an old family these on beaters or some shit second car
She was earlier. I heard she had to end it because of some picture of a noose groovy Jimmy in the news
That's what I heard
Kind of like a porn bomb, but it was something and she had to end the panel. I
Don't know pretty scary, man. What people stupid people go
People are fucking insane lately
Let me go ruin someone's panel with some dumb picture because I'm an idiot like I've not better do like I'm just hating
You know, like we'll make your own panel and like get the fuck out of my face
That's just cool haters, bro. That's cool. Envy envious people. They don't want to see you succeed
They're not happy that you're happy and you're chilling with people and having a good time and playing your dumb trivia and
They're envious like oh, yeah. Why didn't I have a hundred people watching? Oh, it's so cock in your face or fucking new like
That's just sad and weak shit. Anyway, yeah, they're dead
Very weak, bro
Some is very special to some of us to explain
And she were her mouth is 100%
Yo page you don't have to type that you can just join and say that the world the beautiful
He's talking about whales. Thank you. Hit the fucking dolphin noise. Where's pagey? She left the coop. Oh
My god, so we got that heifer
Yo, we got the havers and pays the down fin. I'm gonna make a whole zoo out of this shit
Do the thing man the poor guy needs
If you don't wait to join though, I can't just fucking do a shot for free. He's here in spirit. I
Can almost feel him next you can almost feel him you can almost feel him. You saw that energy. Yeah
Page ran off you know, it's funny how people those
When Alex joins or a ghost joins they all run
They're already a cancel like page fucking ran off thing that is won't dare to fucking answer
There was 80 watching the 16th so you drove off page
They're definitely watching
Well, they're watching the boy is the 20 people read because they're like oh
And that shows you that those 20 people that left are the trolls the
Alexander mayor was one of them. They're all watching the haters
So 20 haters 60 still here not bad
If there's 60 people watching me and you on psychic shit, that's a little love for psyche man. Take it like that psyche
You're not alone pal because no one cares about me and ghost and what we're gonna say about anyone
So it's not all about the drama
They're supporting themselves from Ronys
right
We between the lines
Good question Bernie join Bernie join hit the fucking link my man help me out here with this ghost fuck
of the
Fuck page. I mean she can come up here, and I love her, but I got a problem with
Just join the panel we're not gonna talk shit to you just hang out brother I
Can talk about Alex mayors the lady that fucking took psyche and ran him through the mud. I'm coming over
Hang out, and now she didn't like him now. She plays him
Fucking character lady how cheap and petty are you?
I paid for dinner with my blunt. It was this like shut up go home and just don't fuck up again like it
Jesus
Thing that is is a bitch dude. I have to agree with that comments
Don't complain when us comes on panel to get you. Oh, no, it's like the boogeyman
That's fun
Think I just freestyle that shit my bad
Paid
Pussy come up here. No one's gonna talk. Oh my god. Imagine a dolphin pussy. That's some fucking good pussy that
And this is how insane these people are
Go and clip this. I'm giving every permission clipped this
Some good
I'm a friend I guess but goodness sake page he needs to reappear says chibi chibi
That's page and thing that is they're on the same page. Well, page
Page with things
They're being bitches
No, we saw his fat ass page. We saw his chunky toes the whole nine. He's not invisible. Let me tell you not this ghost
This goes as chunky toes and they're in the air and they wiggle they he wiggled them for us. Would you like to see him?
i would love to see him can i do have to pay again now you're good i think page and thing
that is is they're both bitches i just go ahead and end that shit on that they're both bitches
well the dolphins bro they're probably getting the dolphin shower or something they're getting
The thing is
Oh, that's missing it's a little blowhole, which I think he covers up with makeup like Maybelline
He gets like a little cover up for the blow. Maybe it's
Ever kiss begins with K
They put a hockey puck in the blowhole and then cover it up a little
Maybelline and that's it. They pretend they're not dolphins
But my friend, we're talking Dothan City, my brother. Dothan City.
Dothan City, yeah. I agree with that.
Why are you talking in the co- bitch, just join the fucking panel.
Join the fucking panel.
Let the horror click the link.
Dumb dumb.
ghost hasn't pleasureed a woman in forever. Oh, shit. 2020 is
bringing it live.
Oh, fuck said that.
2020. Join the panel brother, we can talk about it.
Oh, you have we have better luck of your pleasure in a woman
than 2020 joining the panel. Okay.
I'm sorry.
Not the bitch.
20 20 likes assholes. He likes you can't put cover up on your butthole and it just goes away. I
Mean, I'll go away for the day not when you shit
You can cover it up for a half hour alone and say I'm not a dolphin. I'm not a dolphin. Oh, hey fuck
Well, where is everyone? Where did he go?
Think that is thank the heavens, Jesus goes go the fucker
He was begging for you all night, so, where the fuck is it?
I pull over just to fucking satisfy the idiot. He's he's gone
Did you kick him or he dropped? Oh my god
That was perfect time. I told everyone one second
They were like cuz they liked me there. They're like the guys. It's so nice. The man in McDonald's is really nice
I mean guys everyone lives down at McDonald's
McDonald's wait you ran to McDonald's again. I did it's my favorite place
Get the fuck out of it. I thought you were watching this whole time on your couch. You were at McDonald's
I don't have chat up. So I don't know who's there who's saying anything. So hi
Everyone's saying hello. Yo, those fries are the best. I got you on Sunday. That's my next McDonald's delivery for you
All right, Sunday. Thank you. What's the day?
Friday Saturday Sunday
my time
Where are you?
What do you think he looks so comfy in that jacket?
he's out
he's out and about
he's asking for the length
where's the fuck
hey yo what do you got in your hand
look he doesn't even fucking say hello to me the jackass
Hello, you little goblin. You little
Begging him to come up for an hour and a half
It's fries and I got a problem. Can I explain my problem? I got a problem with saying that is what?
Where's your coffee?
What?
Where's your coffee? I don't have a hurry now. I gotta stop the one next that's that's my next stop the Tim Hortons
Here's clothes. That's my next stop
I'll see you
You gotta do the dolphin noise
He ain't drinking no coffee, I don't want talking that's a little often brother, but that's why I thought
Well, I stopped to get smokes, but I wanted a coffee, too
That's a good point. I think that is his home
Oh
Being fucking Alex up here. I'm not home you jackass I can't fucking come up
Natural no, this is a park. I'm not wearing the leather right now. This is just
The jacket looks weird though. It looks like it's inflated almost like you're in the street
He looks cute. He's a cute guy.
It's a park
Who's your best friend, I'm your best friend
I'm his best friend, but I'm your best friend. He looks I only came up to satisfy ghosts now that he's
you know he's been
Happily in this
Not often page is coming home hit the link and the noise page. Come on, baby
He's coming home
You guys gotta call an ambulance. I'm gonna give you my
That was really
Yeah, no, I'm dying laughing
Is she coming if she's not coming up like I'm I'm dropping my fingers are freezing
Dang that is this looking good, and I won't lie to you shut up man
Little sexy little why is it only guys told me that what the fuck?
And you wonder why I'm single man, it's because only fucking guys hit on me Jesus give you a compliment
So I don't know is ghost considered a guy. I mean, I think that Jack looks nice on you
It's really working for your face. Thanks. It's keeping a compliment. It's keeping me warm except in my
Nice jacket, it really works for your face. Yeah, that's funny
Fucking ridiculous
It's just a fucking parka, like, look, I don't want to have a fucking parka, like, what do you want?
Oh, shit.
You look fucking good.
You said you had to take a compliment?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You look good calling down for one calling down for one. We need you baby
Good in that jacket page. Can you please explain she's
Not looking
You're outside of your environment
I'm very scared. Honestly. I'm I'm petrified
It is very
My fingers are freezing
He looks good
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, hey, yo.
Sykes, real spun out right now.
Syke, you get some good shards tonight?
I
Don't look at your fingers
I see all types of crazy
You can turn your camera on tonight. Is there a chance of that or no? I can turn it on for you once the last time
You look like a retard
You feel like he licks the fries imagine how he licks the cock you saw that tongue action
this all good. It's going to
What that's what he said I drop Peter would go say I didn't say I didn't say that
That's what goes to said rewind it
What's the last time you won a football game
Don't you worry, but then you made page well Raiders, but you like raiders don't wow psych you seen this they made page
Okay, everyone's fine. I'll talk to you later psych. I'll be listening. Okay. Talk to you later
minutes left. We do a circle.
I'll give him a circle and do a
jerk. Now, you may think I don't
want to talk to this fucking
maggot. You may. As soon as you
said that page left. Imagine
that. No, he said he left five
minutes. Imagine last time you
won a football game. Yeah,
what's what's your team fucking
rid of?
I want to make the raiders
In those raiders pants the jaw strap
Slash chiefs one time
Here's my mumbo to me. Oh, we lost many me meaning me left better
Come thing that is
Yeah, good good
He likes Raiders was the last time we won a football game
Years ago
25 30 years ago
You still have the angioma bottle there. Oh my god. What's that about? Well, that's significant
But what is it represents it's what I wanted to know. That's so funny
It represents money, dog. You can't buy it does it
Also, it's like a hidden
it's all about Uncle Ben, not Aunt Jemima.
Hey, your camera back on, Raider.
Yo, they changed it, now it sucks.
Fucking Raider.
Imagine that.
You can't, and it doesn't taste the same ever.
We'll never taste Aunt Jemima again, that's sad.
You never taste victory again.
Ha ha ha ha, Raider.
Ha ha ha, you never taste victory again.
I remember bg from like eight months ago. He probably doesn't remember me on psyches panels. I met him like once or twice
To shit of you fighting someone like in Cali like on the sidewalk I caught that
Mike put your camera back on bitch. Yeah, I was some crazy shit. I was like, what is this?
My fucking stuff that was like like real like I really wanted to fight him. I was fucking
around. I mean no way a f**king writer. That was funny. That was good though. Yeah. So
all I was trying to do was get a reaction out of a minute. Are you are you are you actually
retarded or are you are you autistic? Please explain it to me. Who are you? Who are you?
Ghost, who the fuck is you?
I'm the target. What are you?
Okay, okay. Good to know you.
I'm the target. Nice to meet you.
What a trivia time. What's my two favorite hockey teams?
Well, let me he asked me a personal question. I'm retellin
The greatest one the Super Bowl
Was the last time the Raiders won the Super Bowl
Are you
I'm a courts fan
Yeah, 2012
You got to represent your own
Question much less on raiders won the Super Bowl besides trying to your trivia right now the same trivia time cold
Stayed in what two thousand what?
Period time. When did the raiders do it dumb fucks go ahead and answer me
Yeah, you don't got you. They didn't win it
Right there everything I need to know about the people
Yeah, we wanted you didn't
Both you when was the last time the Raiders won the Super Bowl you don't know that stuff
It never happened
never one is that true they've never won a single one
yeah they're doing good boy that's not even true
so many people that's that's a big claim i gotta look that up
what are you doing buddy i ain't no playing that shit
nah it's great harry jay making a live
i ain't no playing that shit
do you like me that i'm barely going
Captain!
What are you talking about?
What?
And if I-
You're-
Now what?
Right there.
Yeah.
You don't want nobody to remember.
Right there.
I'm a midget.
You know what I'm saying?
Right there.
Get it on there.
That's Samman, bro.
That's Samman NYC.
That's Samman.
Now what?
End of story.
It was Chris K's damn it.
Exactly.
Look how much.
Look at Samman trying to cook father's.
Exactly.
You want to cook father's?
to shit
How do you even get yourself in this situation right like
But Chris K has a balance, he's from like bounce right up, like a rubber band, he like went down and like bounce right back, you know what is that?
Yeah, he did, but he still got bounce down.
He did bounce back quick, we got 19.84
No, he bounced back really quick though, he wasn't, that was crazy.
1984, finally, dumb dumb.
To me the shorty I tell you
Alex read the backshot 1984 is the last time they won that girl. Yeah, good Google search. You're so smart
Okay, so that's good. They did want a Super Bowl because that's
50 years ago pussy it don't matter though. I'm saying you you made a statement and it was a false statement
You stated they never won
Exactly
Start up here ghost you just pull the Harry's like the number one shit lying not knowing without facts you
You just put a jacket on the Raiders like they know a one-one. Yes, they did
Over 50 years ago, I think
Hey, don't matter. There's no
Only team to go undefeated and win the Super Bowl, so who the fuck never won the Super Bowl Q
Because I thought in a centura right it said like oh
No, Dan Marino. That's what I'm mixing up. Dan Marino was the quarterback for the doubt
Okay, so my bad pussy your pussy
Over 40 something years ago, and you want to talk about it now
I'm who what team won the most of the most though the Patriots
Probably
They're like the Yankees of the NFL
He's our BG
Like it's cool
BG watch snark Gonzo do but play easy cameras on my man in the chat hit the link
Only the letter Q
The Patriots and Steelers are tied at six Super Bowls. That's crazy
Yeah, I'm bad because I fact checked his ass. He's fucking rich. Well, what about the Kansas City cheese with my home?
Didn't he went like fucking?
So they got up being like third place
Now that's your mohawk is definitely gonna surpass Tom Brady
the
Oh my god ghost you're in New Jack. Yeah, I gotta watch it. I joined last week
That's when being Peter was still friends, right? When we were still cool, and she would be like
Before the Kukaracha era
She's so funny be the man, you'll be this good girl, bro
I've been watching a panel and she's good
It's just be though no matter how much people think Peter and I are like enemies
like we still like we really do like each other like still like she's like come on the piano like it's like it's still like
We're just like she's so funny, bro
Hey, we're playing we're like we're like the ain't really brother and sister. They hate each other, but it's like exactly
Like me and summer correct
Yeah, I know I know it's like that. I know it's like that bro
We sister banter like no matter what you say to each other you can never break that bond that you built
like you know we love each other and your family okay
She brought like what where would I be would it be be here without beta? I don't think so
You know many times the summer has said I never want to talk to Alex again
I hate him. I don't want him on my panel like beta says to you like say he'd be me alone
I want to talk to you like a chilly time
Beta says it and she's like come on the panel right now. It's like it's like, you know, it's like it's so funny
Okay, well, we really don't hate each other. It's like it's kind of just like
We're just we're just like it's like brother and sister really is I mean, it's like we're just like we pretend
But I'm gonna be fine. I was gonna show one year ago today
beta clip
Yeah, I have the clip. I have the clip. Let me see if I can find it. It was like one year ago
Alex was on the show page was there
No
Me, you're only speed
I'll find it. Give me a minute. Give me a minute. I'll find I'll find I'll be right back
Oh, well, you're alone. I can't believe I've been knowing you're not long. That's insane. We've known each other for a while now
Every year, I'll find I'll find it before you guys go. Let me see. Hold on. I know I can find it
To this time we actually see who we are, right? At first we like put a defense up a wall
Little by little the moment we hang out we dropped that wall a little
Now we're just like I love you dicks. We're fam. You know, it's so weird. I hope it's not like
Anybody. Oh, here is this at home on this clumsy's panel. I have to find mine. Oh, I don't why isn't it coming right up?
That's what I wonder why is it coming right up William to fire arms?
Alexandria also love you, but don't know how to love
Yes, and we love Alexander mayors, but remember the time he was up here without me you mean LD and we had a funny S panel
the first night I met her.
It was all fun, and then it's, but it's like,
and then I, like, I was trying to, like,
say it tonight to her, and I was like, you know,
it's like, hey, you know, I love you.
I'm, you know, it's like, I don't love your block me or not,
but I love you, I hope you have a good night.
And she's like, oh!
Oh, there's that guy. Oh, that's interesting. And there's that guy again. Oh,
he's picked my boundaries. She came to my show after she said that and stuff like that.
She came to my show and then she called me a, you know, monster and all this shit.
I mean, I just, I just, all I want to do is like,
Just remember we come from how we come from these communities with these people that do this and take it lightly
I guess you doesn't have that thick skin
So you just got to be light with her, bro, you know, like
Really, all I want like ultimately do I hate anybody?
Beyond all of it is everything is bullshit except for like
the relationships, you know, and it's like, I just don't know why she...
Listen, you can't blame yourself. You or yourself, you met her, you went out, you were just psyche.
well she doesn't like you or she trips out because there's a man and all the people
Alex we had the best time
She called me that night and she's like I'm on my way to your house
And she's like we're gonna go to dinner and I was like yes, and I booked a restaurant
We went to the restaurant. She's like ordering anything you want have any drink you want
We had like three drinks each. We just did cheers. We just smiling
and then she's like we after dinner we went and smoked a joint at her car that's night ever
that's night ever right now she's like oh well i paid no no not now you're forgetting you're
forgetting the month right after that visit where she was promoting you remember psyche
and if you're both remember she was having you up on panel she was all for you and this is what
Right and the wolf guy and then she felt betrayed by you because you were like more on their side
This is how I see the situation and then she just went crazy like listen, you know what?
I like you but you are a role with these people which are threatening me because supposedly
You know she was being threatened and all this crazy shit and people her life
so she sees you now through the lens like you're part of them and
as much as i like you psyche and now like you're my enemy kind of thing she wasn't really like that
because she and bita were friends when bita introduced yeah carl carl thing that is the wolf
guy the the warlock but bita introduced us we were all friends together she became enemies
I didn't I didn't choose anybody. I really didn't you didn't you didn't
People still to be the and she didn't want no lawyer to to be at all
She just wanted you for herself and you were like hello and be it was throwing you under the bus this whole time and you was
Like how the hell you look this girl that hates you and I'm here being your friend buying you drinks
You don't and then you're still cool with them. That's what fucked their minds up, bro
She was like, I want to do with this because I don't want to do with those people and he's a patch to them
Obviously Sam and all these people on his family night. They're friends. Basically they're friends. I read I miss red psyche
You know, he was not a loner that was going to join me and we were going to go on this venture together
psyche and Alexandra and
She didn't know how attached you were to these people which are actually your real friends
These people have been for you forever, bro
So, you know, whether they talk shit or not, but be the same and all those people these are your real friends, bro
this is how I read it
we were friends
at the same time
then Bita and I were friends and then I was like
with alexandra against Bita
for like a couple months
but when we went and met alexandra for dinner
and that's the problem
alexandra was like
wouldn't it be cool if Bita was here
and we were all friends and isn't it sad
that we couldn't be at home with another guest
it was lying she was testing you
because she wanted you to say
Nah, it wouldn't be cool. I just fuck that bitch. I love you Alex, you know people are crazy, bro. What are quack?
Quack
That's in my opinion when shit started to go downhill
Very paced us
How's the night gone guys I put in between their beef and you know, she just took it on you as well
Like fuck this this guy doesn't have a hundred percent loyalty to me. I'm retarded. She felt stupid and you know
Whatever bro, just forget it. At least she stopped making shit about you
Right
You'd rather be on our mind than like the irrelevant but I went to her chat tonight and I just said
I said, hey, you know, I don't know if I'm blocked or not, but I said, hey, I love you
I wish you still have feelings for her, but I do and I said, I hope you're doing well
I love you and I wish you blessings and then she said oh
Oh, here's a, oh, this guy doesn't respect my boundaries.
This lady came on my show after she said,
Oh, see?
Already, yeah.
She came on my show and did monster and stuff.
And so it's like, what, what, she's already,
She because you already put it out there publicly. I want nothing. Don't contact me this so you even going up and saying that
Oh, my bad. She's gonna be respected. She's out of her mind psyche, bro. Just leave that alone. Trust me
You know what, but I still love her. I mean, I say I can't okay. Love all you want
But just leave it alone because that bitch
Don't problems that you don't need but be this says
Never talk to me again and then beat is like come on the panel. You know, I love it to death. Well, she'll be back. I promise
It's like so stupid of a promise you beat it will be back for you, man
I promise I'll bet my life on it. Hey, that's the thing
I can like say the worst things about each other and like a thousand years from now
If it takes that long we'll be friends again
I think that it's a kind of like cold of I was always a little bit cold to me like yeah
Listen, I'm not gonna lie. I caught a bit of the video you played earlier from a year ago
I caught like a two second of it and I heard her beta being beat up back
Like that was a year ago and she was calling you her love. Oh, no, my love. It's like she was so cool
I'm like, you know, there's
To find that right now like like crazy earlier
I'll find it was one year
You'll quack quack quack quack. Yeah, I'll stay I'll stay my mother miss
No, no, what's up Alex? What?
I'm just chilling man over here my boy psychoronies, you know, he had a hard night tonight
Well, he had 90 watching earlier of my Ronis remember when he was too boy
I remember there was a week straight to watching the poor guy
To and he was just like oh my god, too
Like what else everyone he was and the panel started over and it would be like three zero watching and he was like
What the fuck I want to hate me. I was like Ronys
Don't give up, baby
Not give up my man
He was down to three people and everybody went back
Everybody I'm just so proud of him that he didn't give up bro. He could have stayed on those covers and just gave up
But he didn't
Taco Taco burrito
My colors talk it out. Oh
My jelly, but I just sure my shit. Oh my god, Michael and weenie
I was but but but Michael I wasn't mad at you like I was trying to tell you
This really hate me right now is antagonizing people and you're like making like little jokes making people more upset
I'm not mad at you Michael. Okay, but
Okay, first of all
If you're saying to Tracy, I love you and you have a relationship and she's sending you gifts and things like that, right?
Yeah, and I see for beer money and stuff like that and you're saying, you know, I understand
Okay, so but I'm not saying I'm not accusing you of anything
I'm saying but she but she was sending you money and she was sending you gifts and stuff like that and then you kind of very
Huh, what's the word the very?
Being very blase does this picture off like I I feel that I feel that I feel that I feel like the
I because that doesn't happen to me where I say I give I give I give a cup of love
I give cuffs of love or love into them, and then they're like, oh your trash
That's what it kind of made me feel like to her okay, so not saying not accusing you of anything
But I'm saying maybe this is a perception
So in a way you kind of felt like the Roanese look at the glow in his eye, bro
People trying to take that from like because I have been here position
I've been in that position and so I empathize right but I also have been in your position too
Where it's like I maybe I needed some beer or something like that and it's like and then someone helped me
And maybe I wasn't as grateful as I should have been and stuff like that
Okay, so I said I've been I try to empathize with all the parties because I'm not perfect either, okay?
But I'm trying to say you can always say I'm sorry. You can always say I'll make it up to you and not just like and not
Harass or and then people and it says I'm harassing her and it comes to them harassing her
I'm trying to do is say I'm sorry. That's it. Oh, well your sorry's don't mean anything
You're they're fake. Sorry's and so and they're genuine. Sorry's and stuff like that, right?
It's like and it's like, okay. Well, it's like then I feel like these are shit and it's like and then I can't make it up to them
And it's like that and I'm cut off and so like that when I'm trying to like give them love and like
Right. Yeah, we've been we've been like we've been up
I see both sides and stuff like that and it's like, you know, I don't think anyone's a bad person
We can all try to be better and we can try to make up things to people and it hurts when the people cut us off
They won't let us apologize or make up and stuff like that
I know I think you said you you're sorry several times or something like that and your apologies aren't being accepted
all big time
all your accounts because I know who you are and you're you're fucking late and big time you don't fool me and I
and
It was like he put us in the green room. It was me big Rob on the back chat. Yeah, I was having a sexual conversation
I was in obsessed with taking a ski shot. So I'll let all I should play out. Oh
Look was on
He didn't have those
I made an excuse to leave over that. Yeah, and God he and you want a guy over it. Yeah
Who will follow me out of here and a lot of people did
But you say Ronis well, I don't know cuz you remember that guy Danny stranger where you were his chat at all
I don't know if you saw when I was plugging in. I saw you promoting him the past like couple weeks
And I'm like all right, cool. So I can meet a new friend. This is awesome
I checked him out and then supposed he got shot the other night. Yeah
I just didn't just meet him. I met him like with Piranha like I
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Lives had 1.2 million views on it. It was like I got fired from Walmart or something like that
And so he was yeah, that's what made him famous, right? Yeah
About that, but I just got like the past couple months
I thought like yeah
I started going to his chat again, and then he but he always had like two or three people in his chat
He always had this drama with women now. It's like so like a couple weeks. He looks like kid rock
He's always like right exactly. I know he passed away for Rufa
Yeah, like two days ago, he got shot at a store in the chest last Sunday. It was just last Sunday
He got shot in the chest and
Yeah, that's it. One day you're here and the next you go live and
One day you're going into buy a Snickers bar next second. You're on the ground. Like you
Was like funny has I was just like, you know, I didn't want to chat very much the past year, but then like the past month
He was on all the time all of a sudden and then I was all the time and I saw he had like
He had just like a couple people in his chat
So like a couple weeks ago. I was like everyone go to his chat
He had like 40 people in his chat and he the next day I talked to him
I never come up here under like any account has never wanted to go under another chat
He was always happy to be in his chat. He's like he's like just bring people here
So I brought and like 30 to 40 people were in his chat
And in like, you know, Jenny Jen girl, whatever and other people were in his chat
Yeah, what's the IP to what was his deal like what he's streamed his life, like whatever
The Walmart shit, yeah, he worked there, right supposedly he worked at Walmart
And so but then I asked him the next day, I was like, do you have fun? He's like, hey, he's a guy
I he's like, I had the best time because
He never had that many people
How young was he? How young? He looks young
He had two teenage kids
And I hit on him and he got clipped recently because I was like
I went live on his panel
He opened a panel once in a while
And before it ended I was like, hey, I love you
He was like, hey, I love you too
And then he said, hey
Well, take time
You can relax because he's dead, okay?
So let's let that go
Someone said, oh, you're gay for pay.
And someone posted the clip of it where he said, I'm gay for pay.
And I asked him, are you OK?
Because I know that you're gay because I was on your show.
He's like, I don't care.
He's like, he just didn't care at all.
He was such a good, really good heart.
I never really won anything.
hateful or negative out of him. He was just like a good guy and he really wanted
He always had a problem with one or two women and
Fighting with you know, you want to go to my show. I asked him several times to come on the show
So I just like shared his show and everything and then he called you
Did he call you psych like what do you call you when you guys would talk?
like
And then like right before like I saw I saw like that Sunday
I like last Sunday or whatever I saw he was on but he was but when he would get really depressed sometimes and he was like
Right. Oh, I don't like any of my chat. I think everyone's a fake. I don't have any real friends and stuff so that last night
That's what he kind of wrote on his
on his stream and so I didn't go in his chat and then the next day like Jamie told me
Oh, you know your friend Danny was murdered. I was like no you talked to him the night before he died. I
Saw his channel on that board. I talked to him at least two days before he died
Before he died you talked to him. That's crazy
Yeah, and then it's like I was like no that's not because people told me like someone told like
Someone when Joker killed himself and like he didn't and someone told me oh this person's dead
And they weren't and then so I was like
No, he's not he's fine because I just saw him the night before like streaming and then
You know a friend of mine from his chat was like, oh, you know what happened?
He went to a gas station nearby his house. It's on his last dream. I think you can hear the gunshots
He he got shot in the chest several times. It's really really really sad
But so right now they're on the first 48 trying to look for the guy that got him
Can someone in the chat take away that last comment, please Perry page you got a wrench
Yeah, the gorilla coming bye-bye, thank you see that's why I'd like to be down there
That's why I don't want to come up because I like monitoring for shit like that
There's a lot of people that had like
Take things sensitively sometimes there's people like think that is and like I would say Danny and like other
Michael never like really there's people that just think they don't care
They're like they're like they're like happy me assholes and stuff like that and they don't care what whatever and I love
I love that about them and
Always like that's that's when you have complete self-confidence in yourself, and you know who you are that
Nobody can say anything because you know who you are like you just laugh at him like I love
Not everybody can do that. He was some people
Like no matter like look at me. I'm a big f a g or queer or whatever
He was like I was like I wanted to buy his wife beater. He was also. He was also gay
He was gay. It wasn't gay. No, he has two cute teenage
It was a straight guy and you had a huge crush on him basically. I had a crush on him and I
never like he never
Was he didn't like hope will pull it out like psyche stuff fuck
Never never you always
Cuz he was confident in himself and his
I was like, I'm sorry cuz someone clipped him when I was talking to him and like our conversation and they're like
Oh, he's gay for because he's like I'm gay for big because at one time. He's stuck
Come join stop harassing people in the chat
But um, and so that was last time I talked to my he's like he's like, you know what he's like, I don't care
I don't care. He just didn't really care at all. He just laughed about it
Like some people like most people would you know like that I come across would be kind of a fan. No, he didn't care and
And I know I now what happened what happened what led up to his what happened? Do you know the story like what?
What happened was he lived in like a little Texas town he was like I think it was in his trailer
Maybe or something like that. I don't know if he knew the person or not, but the story I saw I read in the news
he, um, he was streaming at the time and if you go to his last stream, like I hear you can hear the gunshots and stuff
He went to like was it a 7-eleven or something? Well, he just go like for a snack at the store and
He's looking at his local gas station
I think he was maybe with some people and like but and I heard there there were shots fired back
But there I think he was attempted robbery or something and he was shot several times in the chest and you can hear
the gunshots on that stream
because it was nearby his
he is a fuck
I'll stop at a gas station
you just don't know nowadays
it's horrible
and it's like
and that's why it's soft that we have a lot of people up here
threatening people to do that
we're not in the work
those are one of the deadliest parts to get caught at
the gas station
yeah it was fucking
But that's just bad luck to have another person in there that evil with a gun, you know
Your time is up. If God put you in a situation
Alex there's always somebody worse than you
He was found dead as a gas pump
He was found dead as a gas pump, but like he was I guess with people or something
They they fire back and stuff like that. So I I mean, I don't know
I don't know exactly what happened and it's like this is mean. It's a really terrible
and
crazy
Because it's too close to home though, bro. You were just talking to this guy two nights ago, you know
That's what that's what makes me
Wow
The thing because I hadn't talked to him for probably like six to eight months or whatever like but I
But he was on sir. He started being on all the time like every time I go on
I would see him on and so I would go on and like talk to him
When he was on a bad mood because sometimes he was in a bad mood like saying oh
Everyone's fake and no one like no one really likes me and stuff like that. And you can see that within the last week
I was on his show
clocking to him and stuff and
and
I just feel like there's a reason I was there, but but but I didn't but I said my chat
But he was a nice guy was he like a vulgar absolute like us
He was a cool kid like I really didn't look at his channel
He's funny
You can see you I mean he was just
But he doesn't like kid rock. I know I always said he's a kid rock. I was back to that kid rock
Yeah, he looks exactly
He never like okay the first time I remember the first time I met him
I went in his chat and I like put an emoji and then he came in any he blocked me from his chat because
Well, because I'm an emoji what emoji was it?
Are you here on my girls?
girls in there
and you know who was oh he got jealous is piranha i like told piranha about him
and so she was in there and so piranha told him i wasn't a bad guy
and then he unblocked me in the ever since then he was always nice to me after that
and uh and then he told me recently he's like where's piranha where's all these
where's the girls that you had i was like i don't know piranha i was like none of
there none of them fuck with me anymore you're still spelling a wrong prairie page
The good die young but die is a spell that way. That's like hair die or like you're dying a shirt dies. D. I
I'll put up his picture. You can't go. You can't get my little Canadian. I'll put up his picture
They still have a spell that's him right there, you know, you can just see
he was like a
Good energy. There's a good energy about it, bro. I thought I was 24 20
Yeah, it looks like him it looks like money if that guy had long hair. That's money for 20
If you put psyche's hair on that guy
I don't want to joke on him, but he do look like Mario right now
Rest in peace man. Look at he's got a nice smile. He doesn't look evil. You know when you can just look at
This picture out of LA yo Mario
No, no, no, he was a really good guy. I know he loved his kids. I know he like always he always had problems
Well, then if that's the case, I'm so sorry Paige for making fun of your spelling. She was trying to censor the word die
Hello
Yeah, I don't want to see him without a shirt because I this guy never wore a shirt. He was he does that guy know
I love it because you'd be out of his shirt sometime and I'd be like, oh you're ever but it like
I have you like you're like, oh you're gay. He's like, oh, why he's like, why are you so gay?
Why are you hitting on me? But then he'd be like better
like it but it wasn't like me and spirit at all and uh
Then when I sent my chat over like, you know, and I sent my chat over to other chats
Usually like three or four people show up like literally 40 people were in his chat and I asked him the next day
I was like, did you have fun last night? He's like, I had the best time and he really did that was like a week ago
Right, yeah, he's gonna be the best time and I was touched now, but I'm so thank you Danny
Because look you got 64 in your chat. He brought you good luck man
You know
Do you want to see that Alexander video guy? I'm gonna play the Alexander video guy. I just have to play it again
Yo, that's such a good song by the way. I love how you hit things like up. It's absolutely about the cry
Yeah
No one take Kino Casino in the chat, out, thank you.
Kino Casino, out of there.
For midnight talks, for spiral rants, and victim analogies
But when the script got rewritten fast, she cut my name from every cat
I was used for till Tuesday, holy till the fall
Then suddenly I'm toxic, the villain after all
Don't contact me, she tells me with the curtains, dramatic draw
And then she floats into my panel like a ghost and Mr. Don calls me some grand monster, says I'm darkness doom and doom me up.
Funny how I was a snake right up until I got less useful to a junior empire.
I was there when things were crumbling, now I'm the big disaster.
That's rich coming from the patrons, ain't a change in every pastor.
She found herself a champion, a knight in shining chrome.
you said finally i'm home but the armor got dented the fairy tale got hazy and even
sir salvation said this video is crazy the master i keep fainting watching plot twist hit
the wall that's your redeemer didn't he just miss your call
I'll be scared
Is that gold? That's gold, bro
Okay, tonight
That's gold, look at Thumb Dumb
Look at Thumb Dumb's fat ass
Quack, don't tell me that's not gold, bro
100%
You wanna run it Thumb Dumb? Look at him
She whispers then appears where I live on air like boundaries off of peasants and hypocrisy's couture the way
Now I'm some spiritual trafficker. What a deluxe invention. There's not a charge
It's fanfiction with a persecution pension
Look at the fucking birds look at the red birds. They mean something. I think that's a shout out to be right
Who can't say him? There's three that's Peter right? Oh, I'm good
Such a beast, baby, why haunt my little show?
Why bang on the cathedral door you swore you'd never know?
Don't contact me, OK, cool her.
Then why are you enrolling, memorizing every word?
Contact me, fine by me.
Then why do you keep orbiting my so-called monstrosity?
I was useful till two.
who borrowed truth for leverage and performed pain with style
i'll be over here still breathing still speaking still hilarious that's my favorite the guy eating
popcorn that's gotta be psyche that's like just watching the show right that's you right
and then i knew as well i don't even know if he's alive
Obviously, that's me. Just look at the eyebrows. That's great
Thank you. I like that. I like that. I mean, it's like I think that's one of my best videos and it's like
My sweet revenge because it's like I said, hey, I love you and I wish you well and I'm in blessings and she said oh
Told him not to ever you know and she came to my show after she said that she came to my show first
And then she called me a monster on my show and then left before I could say anything to her, right?
But yeah
Anywhere she's projecting her bullshit on to you about how she feels about everybody around you, bro
But I want to
Bro, I'm gonna break it down right now. That bitch is the whole world and everyone in it and you're in it. Okay?
so fuck that I was I was there for her and also
Because of a midnight conversations. Yes, she would call me at midnight and we talked for a few hours a few times. We did
and she we're supposed to go to the Christmas special we're supposed to go she was gonna get a party
nah i had a friend like that once bro i had a friend like that once he would pick fights with
everybody he just everybody everything was a problem everything was a fucking problem one day
i just grabbed him i'm like listen bro you got a fucking problem with the whole world than everyone
Pretty much exactly exactly you get it. Correct. Harry. That's why I stopped talking
That's why I'll wait with replacements comments or nothing like
Sooner later, bro, that shit is gonna run out that the patients won't stand bro. I love you my boy, but I can't do this anymore
You just see my Russian friend was in the chat tonight and she sent me some pictures tonight
Was she the hot tamale?
She is a hot tamale. I'll show you a picture. Oh, it's a hot tamale
Give me a second. You guys talk for a second. Oh come on my phone. Here it is. Okay. So yeah, my Russian friend
I've been friends since like 2008 or whatever, but she brought me a Lenore, you know, Mike
What's your name in the chat? I didn't even know she was here. I wouldn't know
Alina
I think it's Alina. Okay, Alina. Yeah, I saw that I saw that avatar and I was actually gonna say something like who is that hot new girl
But I just left it alone. That's her
right there
Oh, I know this is your dana, but she sent me but she brought me like she brought me in Lenore
And this is like when I this is the night that I met Lenore
Look at this. This is the night I met Lenore. Look at this
Oh little kitty look at a little mini Norseys. Yeah
Can't turn them down, but you got to think about the future
Yeah, but still you can't let them down
This is a future
Tiny no wonder that cat stuck to your neck every day. She's been like that. There's a little baby. Oh my god
Because you know her papa from Eleanor. This is like
Crazy yesterday was my dog's birthday six years old
That's young
Is I think it's March 13th, but March 14th is tricks. It's his birthday. He's born two years ago
He's born it's called pi day because it's 3.14. So it's March 14. Yeah, that's a crazy day, right?
Pies like perfection something
So, um
Try to have a positive day
Let's get a cleansing going
I have goosebumps literally have goosebumps right now. Hey, hey, what do you think? Hey, that was the night. I'm at Lenoir
Look at that. I I think that you need to just you know what?
Lenora is gorgeous. She's such a cutie pie. She looks just like baby Raven and I was just sucked
That was the first night I got her we were hugging
We're hugging first night. That was the first time I got her and she was
She's tiny
Canvas is like a
and put it right away. She's looking at the camera too. She's so happy. I think that's, I think that's one of my cats. I think that's marbles, but yeah, you can see them.
See, these are like, we would hang out so much, you know, making psyche with a lumberjack on. Look at the monster, look at the mosteronies. Look at the lumberjack jacket.
Yeah, look at what a monster, right? Look at him. Look how long with this cat like I will beat the fucking
So family
Just so happy. She sent me these tonight. These are some old photos. I have
She brought me like several of my cats
Jesus look at that air
So happy
But the question to me more is the current the current was blue ones. This one. Look at this one
This is when I first got her. Did you say blue once?
Forget her. Yeah, they'll get this purple for the past two years. I know is they can get in the picture. It was a blue
She was she was so excited to bring me to the North that I was like I was so sad of my other black cat and she's like
And she she surprised me with an orange cat is
Well, you must have been getting a lot of cock back then you were looking good my man
What I'm just saying
I
Don't stop page, you know that
It's just saying and I call it I see
There was no cement bags then there was just cock in the door every day
No, you know what?
I'm a comedian, Dave. You guys forget that all the time
Gram or like a song gram or a birthday gram. It's like a top coca-gram
We got Rudy Rudy, do you like your head headed like this like that?
Oh, oh, oh, he just his whole body collabs
Whiskers, bro, the whiskers are intense. They're like little guide rails state their senses so friendly. Actually all your cats are very friendly
I saw a cat one time right in the street with Bert whiskers with that. What'd that do to them?
Oh
They sense if you're evil or not through the whiskers. They sense
That's why it was looking like it was all cracked out and shit. It was just off balance
I saved a little kitty once man. I stopped my car in the middle of the street and changed it into a fucking schoolyard
And saved the dumb thing
Yeah
Took it to the back
You said everybody needs somebody in love
I'm trying to to my own horn here to be your friend
I
Can I make a request yes, I've tried to so many times I can you please play an OG clip of all of us together
It's today
No, come on. I mean how long is it?
Just give it a taste of it bro. Give it like five minutes of it. You don't got to watch two hours
Scared of the past that's so cute. No, but beta. It's up. I'm beat. Oh my god. I'm thinking
I don't care. I love beta. Don't I'm not never gonna
And you know what?
He put it up for you.
Me, myself, I stopped going because of one person individually,
like that one person.
No, she's in my mind at the moment.
Huge.
You're so huge.
But I still put it up for her.
I'm not mad at her.
I'm not at that one individual that's always over there,
so I stopped going over there.
She's playing this.
She said, this is my page, my area.
Dude, what individual?
one individual, don't you like it? Oh, Christine, Christine, hello.
Have a two.
Okay, well, you know, guys, we're just gonna, we're gonna just, we're gonna listen to this
clip and we're gonna, like, we're gonna be brought back to nostalgia in good times.
Can we, can we get high five percent of the cases, but that's too forward. Let's just
do a wall.
Let's see what we got coming up right now.
I can't believe this guy has all these clips from a year ago that's intense
That's crazy. I mean, yeah, that would be worth me if I was back in like I was lying. I don't record every single panel
Oh
This one I am at the computer drop this guy 15 times over this stupid song
15 fucking times bro
Mother welcome
Then went on a rampage of two years to men delivering. What do we need to talk about Daniel?
What?
What about the opening music Daniel?
My favorite song Nike page wants to see some page old clips if you don't get
Yeah, guys, oh my gosh, so it's been um, yeah, I just woke up a little bit ago. Oh, is I have late last night?
Because
You know, I was there for the Pokemon though in the 90s when that was surely 2000s when that was
That's fucking do gay feel naked
Cuz I'd like a shave head Meezer Meezer was around
What's up with the bet, what bet we're not getting paid, what bet was there?
Tell us in detail.
Yeah, exactly.
We, because when I get paid, you're getting paid.
One K bet that me and somebody else, we're not going to talk about each other.
And when today's I didn't say anything about about that person. They didn't say anything about about me
But today they were my god, who's she talking about who's he talking about?
No, this is a year ago
Technicality so they did a poll and I still didn't get the one day. Oh my god
But that's how I got but whole scam
That's bullshit.
Oh, it's like, you know,
I'm gonna talk about this conversation.
I'm sorry, Bita, did you show face recently?
Yeah, last night on accident,
well, I was like getting ready to go to bed
and I just had like a T-shirt on and,
She's going boy bro. She's going every one and I came out
I was like when I get ready to go to bed on my phone dropped and I gave an up skirt. Yep. Oh my god
I'm still trying to get over that shit by the way
Well, I want to refer back to a comment in the chat a while ago from dozee toe
I
Can't believe I saw beaters entire asshole last night. So is that?
Is that an end to your comment in regards to what has happened?
No, I can send a video to freakin' Psyche, and freakin' it's already out there, and Eldo.
Nobody saw my asshole.
Oh, okay, that's what someone in the chat said.
Prayer page, why did you message me saying you want to marry me?
Who would say that?
No, there is no bottle shown.
Prayer page wants to marry me.
I
Want them you want them
is that she called? I forgot what she called. Yeah, she's the only girl in the world.
Good times is one of those. He's like me. When we get a haircut and shave, we look 25.
He's one of those special jobs.
That making me a gallon of fucking...
We clean up extremely well, my friend.
That making me take a shower and touch a grain.
Bro, a haircut, a shave, and a suit, and we're just fine.
My hair is not greasy, don't worry.
Uh, my hemorrhoids hurt.
Oh, no!
The hemorrhoids is out with some hairy hair on the hemorrhoids.
I don't have area soul. Sorry
You can push it in save yourself $2,000 dollars go to doctors we get a hammer just push it right back in your ass
Just put you right back in
I love you.
He just pushed that shit right back in.
Oh, I was only trying to give it to the party.
Jesus Christ.
Damn fucking good times over here, ruining everything.
He couldn't even give a really hard sense to the game.
He couldn't even change the atmosphere, see?
You know, Page ran to the bathroom like I can show him what's back in.
Say a word.
That bitch is in the bathroom right now.
All right.
Saving yourself tens of thousands.
Yeah, Paige you can just show them right back in your ass. Oh, baby
I don't know he probably ran to the bathroom to like oh my god, I can stay 30 grand
He's shoving his emeralds in his asshole. That's where he went
A year ago be to his laughing about her butthole
Really no way
She's a funny beat-up. I told you it was fine
It's a good sense of humor even to this day
Work, please you gotta use your index. Don't use the thumb because
All right
It's Friday the 13th. We need to climb
Back in
Friday 13th guys. Hey, put on your Jason mask
Friday 13th is a special day for easy. Could we just have some fucking sensitivity here for the man?
Shut up man. This is what I say. We need to cleanse it. I need to cleanse it
Oh, yes, American Speedos
Can you raise for the American?
Can you see
He's going to get him unfortunately
Cover your eyes or drop off the panel cuz you're about
Page page
People your eyeballs, you know, you're not gonna want to see this
Yeah, you know what's coming they he dropped
Yeah, it's it's about to be the seventh in stretch out this bitch and you please stand up for the national answer
Happy Friday 13th, I'll go a lot again. I'll go a lot today
Oh, it's national days. It's like a hot
They just went back to the bathroom to show family dinner ends. This is great
Yo, who was saying that who was saying that was it Dan Dan? I think no, it was um
It was Dan Dan Dan said he was shoving his
I heard that bro, bro, if I had more time will kill myself
But I could have sworn I heard someone say you can just shove him back in or something.
And I was like, oh, that's about it.
Yeah. Wow.
I get you.
Oh, my God.
How do you even get hemorrhoids, bro?
I thought you get hemorrhoids when you shit out a kid or something.
The name of the father, the son and the Holy Spirit.
Amen. Please release the demon from this site.
Oh, my God.
That means no pussy forever.
Imagine you forget the Jesus.
Yeah, you you never prolapse your asshole while you're taking this shit
And you gotta show no what it's gonna be collapsed and then even heard that word in my life
What is that push it back in your soul. I need to learn what you know about what's
Medicine like look like a balloon. That's a prolapse
Yeah, but that happens when you're like 90 bro, not at 45 50. What are you guys talking about you?
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
in the spring page you know what funny he's right because I had a boss once that told me that I had
a like a boss once and he told me he had hemorrhoids and that's the first time I've learned that a man
can get him and I'm like what are you talking about he's like yeah I've been told where I was
picking something up something and like it just popped out I'm like what are you talking about man
man can have hemorrhoids until that day I thought it was just a girl thing
of the
Like I was trying to say right that is attack. I was just saying I just testin's like you know, they shit your heart out
But I thought showing them back in with a fucking saying you can actually show
Buddy
Yeah, he's on some horny stalker shit
She's like a moanie
I'm only here for every page
Poor chai key where he doesn't even ask for psyche. I'm just here for prairie
I
of the
the
And then
Connection let me tell you
Rosemary's baby. Here we go buckle up. This is scary. Oh shit. I
I think you should take it away. I don't like this. I don't like this. I'll wait over. No, there's the buzz
Turn the lights off complete darkness. Just this I love horror movies, bro
Look at her, Bita by the way, it's Bita's baby
She's looking right now. Like I know as a change of manners was here this weekend
I'm gonna find her undies. That's what she's doing right now. Bita's going nuts. Like where? I know this proof
Saki, I know you cheated on me with that bitch. She's looking for proof and watch what happens when she finds it, Quack
Bita's not a happy camper
Look look. She's like I knew it
I knew this bitch was here. She took my ronies to dinner. They had a joint together.
But I don't know what she does. She don't play with her ronies.
Sanky! Sanky!
That's Vita by the way. That's her.
Look at that.
Steakie.
Steakie lit the kukarache in.
I'm gonna show him.
There we go, Peter. Grab that knife.
Here we go.
There's your little Persian queen.
Steakie.
And look at Steakie.
He comes home.
Just, you know, a good guy.
Goes to the fridge.
Got some McDonald's.
In this cycle, bitch, isn't it?
Thank you. You hung out with Alexander Meyers
Look at Ronies
Just got his pick back. That's it. I'm gonna kill I'm going on the panel
I can beat up. Thank you
Oh
We all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love you, we all love
Oh you bk gang psyche bk kitty gang
Rony's is on the pan right now with me and fucking ghost and quack
Has no clue this bitch is haunted. I'm done. Thank you
Hmm
Looked you psyche. Oh now she comes into the room
Looking with psyche and now we all confronted like you dumb bitch. What are you doing with the knife?
She's a good takey. That's all of us. That's quack. That's time man. That's Christine
That's me. We're all in that room everybody
thing that is there
I got all you fucking trolls. They wanted to fucking talk shit to me now. I'm gonna fuck you over now guys. I
take over the boys
Seiki
We're Seiki. No, I don't care about you guys the kukaraches
You so good times look at summer look at someone right here everyone's there everyone's there, buddy
Sam and YC is about to step up watch
No, no watch us. Yeah, he's the white guy in the yellow suit
Look at her
Thank you. You are a tangible is here. This is one she discovers
Alexander on our side
Now the bitch looses it, where is the cockroach, where is Psyche, see Samman with the yellow
suit.
Yeah, Psyche pours it for you, we'll get copyright strike, let us talk about it and then we're
going to continue.
That's how you do it.
What have you done to it?
What have you done to it's eyes?
He has his father's eyes.
Yo, that's beautiful and crazy.
What'd you do to Psyche?
I'm never gonna be able to provide my wife with a life.
You took him out to dinner?
If I had more money, maybe we could help you.
I don't think I've ever seen so many zeros.
Oh god.
By the way, psyche you disrespected page a little bit. She wanted an old-school page panel
With beta and us the one you were talking about you didn't do
Do one you don't tell Roni's what to do
Thank you. That was my first I've seen that
Yeah, these bitches are nuts look at these dumb bitches with wallpaper. Oh fuck
This is real horror some blonde lady in the basement waiting for a clothing this is horror
I'm sorry, it's alright. A lot of people think I'm Victoria.
I don't see any resemblance.
Do you know her?
No.
My name is Terry Ginofrio.
What have you done to it?
What have you done to its eyes?
It has its father's eyes.
Imagine you're a young couple, newly married and excited to start a family.
You move into a beautiful apartment building in New York City, but something isn't quite right.
Your neighbors are old and eccentric, and you can't shake the feeling that they're watching you.
Soon you're pregnant, but your pregnancy isn't normal.
You have strange cravings, nightmares, and hallucinations.
Is it your imagination or something more sinister at play?
Rosemary's baby is a classic horror film that will put you in the shoes of Rosemary Woodhouse.
The film is a masterclass in suspense and dread, with the filmmakers slowly building tension until it reaches a truly terrifying climax.
The film also has a strong emotional core, as it follows Rosemary's struggle to protect her unborn child from a supernatural threat.
If you're looking for a horror movie that will
Yes!
Suspense you.
The analogy is that
I highly recommend Rosemary's Baby.
Alexander Meyers is the onborn child.
Is that what those bitches were giving you?
Rosemary's protecting Psyche.
Is that the hint for today?
They're my friends.
They're a bunch of not very bright bitches
who are on their own goddamn bitch.
All they said was 30 seconds ago.
Easy, easy girls.
You know who Dr. Hill is?
He's a Charlie nobody.
That's who he is.
I'm tired of-
Dr. Saperstein is.
Well, we'll have to pay Saperstein.
We'll have to pay Hill.
Well, it's out of the question.
No, I'm not changing.
I just want to go to Dr. Hill and get a second opinion.
I won't let you do it, Rome.
I mean, because it's not fair to Saperstein.
They need you say it's not fair to the doctor. That's the
Did you hear that I won't let you do it. It's not fair to the doctor for you to get a second opinion
You know me neither bro, but Jesus is that what people grew up in the 40s or 90s or whenever this was because now I know
I were crazy
That's Christine! That's Christine!
Oh my god!
What have you done to it?
What have you done to his eyes?
Yeah
Perfect love. Oh my god, perfect job perfect love everything's
Oh, no, they made a new version
run away holy shit thing comes without a price you told me she would be safe
you were chosen to be as month by who
So they love it
We gotta go all of us all of us buddy. All right. That's the baby. Okay. I got the popcorn in the soda
My man, just leave the knife at home and we're gonna enjoy a movie. All right, my man
The pop
The fucking Mac Megadon at home to the movie
It's it's it's listen put the knife first then we grab the house keys. All right
You but you gotta pay for something at least the candy
This is scary black and white shit
Oh my god
I mean, I guess you can find them all and put it back where I had it or something, but
it's always somebody two-thirds enough to stick it in.
Easy.
I don't know what type he's going with this, but this is the acid time, I mean, let me forget my mushrooms and acid.
Yo, I'm trying to percolate it, oh shit, I just tried to say I tried to percolate the rest of my head, and the rest of it's green brimble.
This rapping, rapping, rapping, staking address.
You enjoy making a person look like two sensuals.
Damn, son.
Who craves your man or women, right?
Alex, Alex, Alex.
Which put us off on Christopher Reed.
I'm cleaning the cage.
Oh, shit.
Get that out.
But I can't answer that
She stinks, doesn't she?
Shut up!
I don't let you know anything!
I don't think anybody's ever gonna want that picture again.
And they're always a thrill to me.
My daddy says I can be just like her.
I think there is no more about this.
This time it's over.
Yeah, this is scary. See, this is scary to me.
I will watch the exorcist alone in the forest.
I will sleep in a haunted hospital alone.
I will, you know, fight Freddy Krueger and Jason alone.
I will dive into the depths of hell, alone.
No problem.
But this time, I'm not mad at you.
This is what scares me, my friend.
She didn't grow up.
She just grew old.
Look at Harry.
She was waiting for that big day
that her daddy said would come.
You're not telling like a Stephen hand.
That's what happened to baby Jane.
here's what happened to baby Jane she thought the world was at her feet that is
what her daddy said was true I don't know how long the mind can handle it
there's too much this is what they torture people in camp x-ray
You know what I'm saying with the eyes back tight and that's the fact though
When they put the eyes back and they hold you down with the metal things around your face
Exactly and make you watch this and then you just lose your mind like I don't like this is crazy
Get Ronis
I'm gonna put the link down, I want to watch the whole movie, I want to watch the whole fucking movie, let's do it.
Yeah, we need to do that, yeah but don't get stricken, so I don't wanna come up, come up now.
Wait, we do Twilight Zone, is Twilight Zone copyrighted?
The Twilight Zone.
Oh my god, yes, but guys, we heard a Twitch, I have a Twitch account, and we can go to Twitch.
We can go to Twitch.
the
Not for twitch. I think you can just go to twitch literally and go on it and just choose someone
You come look at like yeah, I'm like he says oh, I'm on twitch and he should stop coming to YouTube
Are you like we're having a psyche anybody's like, you know, he's on Twitch and
I don't care. Oh, I'll get I'll get home. Let's say I'll put the link in guys. You want to see the link?
I'll put on the best movie you ever saw made it say I mean
I I have much better stuff than I can put on the show
I can't put some on the show because it's not like copyright. It's all copyrighted, but I can put it on the show
Hold on. What's it? I'll put it
Which slash psyche awakens twitch wood or just go to twitch calm and once you're in it
It says search someone and just put what psyche I'll be right back
The psyche or co psyche, you know how he does it
No, yeah, cuz I've been to Twitch and I watch it you can just search someone and they go
I show speed you can go to Twitch and put I show speed in the search box
And all of Nick all of shameless those shimmers that category of shimmers will pop up like a list
The algorithm start building from there on
Yeah, why you you got a wrench up your stupid link here easy cameras on promote your channel so you get on problem
That I don't like promote my channel man machine going on. Why not dick? You know, I'm bad. There's just funny shorts and
Me come on. You're gonna get back on the ball with the horse, but I'm a cherry a commentary videos and then delete. Yeah, exactly
Strong tension
Now put it in the front the back because only I could see it in the back dick
Put in the front so 60 people can see it and be like what's this easy comes on and
Think that is could do all of us
Yeah, we'll think that is unfortunately
I'm in the show. He's in the chat in the show. I'm in the show
I'm in the chat. I'm in the chat. I'm in the chat
I'm in the show.
Yeah, that's you
Nico there you go. Nico. Yeah, that's it boy. That's what's a boy from like the dirty sector something to say
He's cool
No, you that's the new joke right and fucking a bootstamps is running with that one was easy
I
Was busy I was busy on my phone 24 hours, so I wasn't dying as much
You just came up said he had ninety two five minutes later. He was on four percent
No, but I had something to do
Charger you don't need a new phone. It's your charges
Yeah
Okay, there you go. There's a thing called a fast charger. There's a regular charger
There's also a fast charger. You pay a couple of
Like in double the time. Yeah, she did it fast
So, you know who thought it is though, right it's thing that is for why
It's just a sport. You know, I think we can blame everything on both heads. I don't know. Is that fair?
It is fair. I told you when we over here everything is think that is for we over there
Everything's untrackable for corruption. So
Hmm, I said that was funny take with Harry
I do what I gotta do
It was I have was a hooker
Yo, let's kick them cuz I was like you gotta put one in the back
I don't know who's talking. He was he kicked. He's like you're out Harry. I'm like, I'm kidding dick less is too fawny
The way his mind works, right?
Mm-hmm
Why should I give a fuck
To me, I don't really care. Oh
No, no, you're getting it. You sound like them now. I don't want to practice my own trackable impression. That's too much
Alex Alex, but how can anybody sound like me?
Well, I'm trackable. No, they sound like you man
Jesus I'm just gonna use that one to Harry man if you jumping on board go ahead boy
Oh, I really try to be like me, bro. You know, I'm the main one that does that
The mimic master
Uh anyone in the chat marky mark. Bye. Bye. See this way. Gotta be down there, bro
Oh, can you can you time people out in the chat from I'm up here because I don't have that capability on my phone
You might because you're on the laptop
They raise that common
Yeah, yep. Bye. Bye
So he's the loser
Tell me if you can if not I'll drop down and do it myself
Right, I can't I can do it. You're my friend and think you're a lot to fucking block stupid shit like that
So I know I know they want me to block it for they could use it against me
No, I do it. It's like he's not stupid anymore. He gets it. That's an attack
Okay
No, I follow his lead, bro
If it's an attack mm-hmm was it a bad attack that wasn't pretty bad one of my
I'm not attacking all right marky mark. Okay, calm down
Hmm still safe for a dick
But come on
That's not nice. He can buy psyche speeders, but can't buy his kid a gift. That's not a nice common, bro, right?
No, I mean just knows he's crazy cuz you know who they are from where they take off from hello
What do you mean by that
Truth isn't
See
So yo, if it was up to me I would have done it by now easy so you're up to your discretion, honestly
Just erase that one dumb comment about the kid
That's what I'm saying. You know what I'm saying? You can definitely do that. And that's cool.
Yeah, bro. But don't block them. You're still here.
Can you erase the child coming for us? Thank you.
I'm going in there right now.
That's what I'm saying if they don't
Happy I deleted it. Thank you marky mark. So that's respect. He deleted himself
Yo, that's the first time I've ever seen someone do that Ashlyn
Correct after realizing they like violated a little like all right. I'll delete it happy
That's cool, man
Marky Mark in the funky bunch. That was my boy Mark Wahlberg
Brooklyn that we should go Brooklyn that
Monkey Mark in the funky bunch. Oh my god
That was crazy
The funky bunch back in a day then he became a superstar the movies hello
He was also a Kevin Klein supermodel marky mark
He was literally
Because I've been a fashionista since day one my man. I used to match back in the day now
But I used to match the ball the leather you can wear black of boots and you know brown leather everything
But black leather black boots black belt everything has to match. I was our coordinate man. I used to care about life once
I still just have outfits on the bed like a like a girl, you know
Like a fashionista like this one. I'm rocking today with the gold chain on it the cakes that go to my rocking today
No, no, it's just like whatever bro hoodie glock pants that I'm out of here
Do my tips make it say hoodie glock mask you look alike lessons picture
That's it my boy
Yeah, that was funny that picture it took off the glasses put the chain on cut it's here
That was me 20 years ago. Honestly. That's so funny. I used to roll around with the chain
Like who wants it? I was a bad boy back in the day, man
I'm lucky to be alive. Honestly all the shit I've done in bento. I was a fucking retard when I was young man
I used to do a lot of fucked up shit
So I give thanks to God that I'm actually here talking
But time good time master my crocs. Yeah
Can you handle this alone for two minutes for a while actually got to take my first little
Cracker in the hair salon
No, the only thing I like about crack is that you cannot hire people
Right, you just did a hair client, but you also cut some crack at the same time then the next one coming higher on crack
And you're trying to do a birthday scout like 14 times
Yeah, by the fifth customer everyone's bored. Everyone's think that is now might as well
Just put up a poster like we only do think that is a cuts up in this bitch
Yeah, after the crack it come on. Oh
Shit
There was a wrap so broke
It's in but I'm just saying in a hair salon
Hey, so long
There is no hair though
If think that is comes in your hair salon. What are you gonna do? You would look and be like what do you want to shave?
What are we doing here? I don't know
These are things I never want to go through girl
You know
What really made you both
What you thinking? Oh genetics. That's nothing no one chooses and it's not a bad thing. I don't know
What is the worst possibility that genetics
Genetics and trust and trust can also build you as well
Shit on his head until he went bald. He's a push shit rub shit in his long hair
Yeah, long luscious hair, and he should shit on him
He's a rough-knit. Yeah, that's funny dick, but it's a genetics at the end of the day, man. You don't choose shit like that
It's just
Genetics, I mean and I respect men that embrace it and just like own it
Yeah, that's crazy. I know I know guys with a whole set of
Pussy
Like yeah, I got fucking sure here. Fuck you suck my dick. You're like
You give respect for that
Yeah, 100%
But we also gonna cut out so you bought us here
100% because we're just fucking you know what comedians is at the end of the day
This is what we do
A boom back road and we'll take a leak my man, hold it down, hold it down
I got you, I'm gonna read the chat, go into the chat, let's go to the chat
Chat, what up chat?
Go back to the chat
It doesn't say here's a lot.
I know it didn't say it's a lot.
And it says, hell, hell, Jesus.
That's what it says.
It says, hell, Jesus almighty, save y'all.
Genetics. Yeah.
I have my grandpa's hair.
Shit.
So the only he actually grew is from that time.
Come on, can we get a guy mine people? Yo, yo, can we hit the link before it's like you fully full asleep?
Oh, yeah, it was a couple links out there. You're heard. I'm gonna drop it right now. I'm gonna drop it right now
I hit the shame y'all link y'all I still got a chance to come in talk your shit and join the panel
Let's go!
Oh, we got the music going!
Showing you all the link is pinned on the top and the button on the top of the screen.
You already know what time it is.
I think that is the many more.
You're always welcome.
Music, bro! Best song ever!
Well, that was amazing. Thank you, Psycho Ronys for that.
Yeah. I mean, I can't play. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Oh, she was the side of the size of her head in that picture. Literally
Yeah, she was a tiny like the size of your hand
She was
She sent me the pictures tonight. I couldn't find them tonight, but
Here
Arthur, Arthur bro, Joplin brought the man
of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of one of
Well, I have a few cats here. What are my cats? There's one
More we can
There's another
There's some cats in mine one two two cats three
Well, look how comfy they are you've been taking care of these cats forever look at this and they all upside down which means full love
And they trust you when when I was gone. There's back. There's like that. That means go trust. That's the night I got her
She's a tiny chief bro, she's the size of your hand
They are forever. Oh my god. He trusted you. Isn't that crazy?
That animal trust to you to take care of her. She didn't know she's a little tiny thing. You could just like fuck this cat
I'm done with it a month later. There's a first
Thing is the first night they got her
There you go, you oh now she's okay, and now she's getting bigger look at her
but like still in your neck that's
You see the eyes
Oh, so that's our spot on your neck. That's like been a spot. She's been a baby. There's a cat
Silly silly got unfortunately coyote. Yeah, the eyes. That was a crazy picture with just the eyes
Yeah, that was silly and then here you can see your car
That looks like many manson a little
She's gorgeous. So yeah, that's my friend
That's the Russian that's the Russian that's the Russia. Oh
The I had a cat in Caleb. That's Caleb. He had any other cats, you know
They're out here right now. But yeah
There was the white one. Yeah, his name is Caleb
Kayla
She brought me some kittens, you know, that I
Yeah
You've been nurturing cast wherever 50 cast these people like you don't have a little box like
How hard you laugh when people say the dumbest shit
You looked so tan in that picture. What do you just come back from Aruba, Mexico?
And is that a dog? You have a dog around you. That was weird. She brought the dog over
Was that that's the Russian? Yeah, that's the Russian. This is Christmas
I know I'm telling you
I'm telling you
and that's out and that's a like alex not here, but yeah, alex was
alex in the first cast you brought me and uh
Here oh here. She brought me to the nail so long one day my nip my my my foot was like
Don't tell me that was when you fucked pussy because you said you had sex with a girl once don't tell me was the russian
with the russian but
It was the rushing it wasn't the Russian
Okay, but there's a this is today. I think this day. That was
Those tricks of my lap
Cat owners bring me out if you die the cats will eat you dogs won't that's bullshit. Ziggy dogs will also eat you a
hundred percent
So that's bullshit
If you die in your apartment, you have a dog and you know, you're there for a month that dog's gonna eat you
Look at them. Yeah, this is just us at dinner recently and
As that's you can see
We are very happy
Good friends, maybe that's why also Alex is upset. It's sexual competition, bro
Maybe the bitch fell in love with you over dinner and then just went crazy like you love beater in the rush
And you don't know what's going through these girls minds bro. It's what I'm saying
She's beautiful. He's beautiful guys. My mom is beautiful. Okay. I I just like my dad is beautiful
Everyone's beautiful. I just I just have everyone's beautiful bro. 100%
Yeah, like, you know, be thankful for my life
But you don't choose what body you get like born into right nobody does so far. I didn't want to make like fun or mock
That is insane. That's pure evil
Okay
Right anyway, you know what no matter what anything anybody anybody says
I had, I've had a beautiful life.
What, we can't dry it, your fart stinks.
I mean, I mean-
You stay like you're dead.
You still have a beautiful life
and you will for many, many years to come, asshole.
Okay.
And my dad, my dad, my dad's a Gemini, my mom's a Cancer.
Like that's their science.
And I'm a Cabercorn.
So it's all three different science.
And I have a brother that's a Leo, my sister's a Terrius.
Those are fire science.
And I'm the Earth science.
And they're both water and water and air science.
Can I drop down and kick Canada's right?
I'm just kidding.
I can.
Yeah, get rid of him.
Get rid of him.
Canada, I had a...
I can't I can't do it
His voice was just a little bit too whiny can and dry. I mean I know it'd be this chat if they make fun of me
It's like they're making fun of me
They're making fun of you
Yeah, can and dry
They're making fun of you and be this chef that you deserve it
Okay, your voice was a little bit high-pitched. Yeah, you gotta stop being such a pussy dick
I'm trying to pick up for you. So I'm sorry. It was whining. I've been sorry. I'm trying to be mean
I'm not trying at all
You come up as a little bit whining
Okay, I don't care if you're first things or not. I don't care just like
Go with the flow. He's spoiled. He's spoiled. Oh, you saw his kitchen
The guy lives alone in some crazy house in Canada cooking meal. Oh, he's a spoiled fuck. Of course. He's gonna be whiny
He's right here. You know
I love the guy anyway. Why are you not it's still our Canada dry. That's the point here
I know he was wielding a wrench last night
And then I had to take it away from him because he was like I've been there. I've been there
That's a rough night man when the wrenches get stank get away
Sweepie, he's like the word. I mean she's like
Saison I think she's Saison, but I can put up with her and like laugh a little bit
You know, it's just like, even if she says it, I don't care.
I don't care.
Oh, I think that is.
Are you serious?
He tried to wheel the wrench at lessons over your head.
That's the funniest thing I've ever heard.
Ah, oh my God.
Canada's my God of it.
I keep trying to like, I want to like so funny.
No, that's funny.
I wanted to just like say, fuck her and like, I hate sweepy.
And it's like, and then she says something like.
Oh Katie sounded like this. Shark tried to take my ranch. And then I laugh. And then I was like, okay, well, if anyone can make me laugh, it's not.
I know, you can hit the link, man.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. She didn't make me laugh. Can I try?
I want to take your blonde ass and...
I don't know, I don't know what I want to do with it, but hey
I'm Katie and
I like a hamster, but he didn't have anything that is that's what I was gonna say
I'm like he doesn't have a wrench there. So how is he wielding wrenches?
Oh, fuck
You I mean this is comedy is funny. It's actually I haven't had to
That's much fun in a while
Damn, I'm founder clip and stuff like that. Katie. I don't okay. I don't
Okay, hey, you mean
Okay, every guys, I'm like an open target. This is a big fun of me. I don't want to make fun of people
But it's like I I do but you make fun of me too. I mean everybody I mean I just don't like what when it's like when it's like
They don't at the end of the day
If you like it, it's cool, but attacking from 90 different directions is not cool
Yeah, I mean it's a different if you like if you make fun of me and you like me
And it's funny and I'll laugh 95% of the time if it's like mean spirit
I don't like it. I don't know and I don't want to hurt anybody's feelings either
I think we get all we all have a side of ourselves
Perfect example the other night you were playing AI videos of like goats and lightning
It was a good song
But I was in one of my moods and I was like enough with the golden lining shit
No one's to hear this bullshit. I know you just left it all
and I didn't mean it, because I love you so much more than anything
I mean I wish it would have been a little better where I would have like laughed at
I know, but I did go back and erase those comments if you check
I went back the next day and I erased all that bullshit
Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex
In a million years
No matter what you say to me from this point on
Whatever
have any really good
Because you know I love you more than anything and if I do have some sort of night when I'm just decide to troll everyone including you
you know
I'm Alex, and I love you and we're family and don't mean shit
That's I mean, that's why I can say that's why I felt like it say that it is like and then it's like
Some people would take it like oh never talk to me again, and it's like people that can laugh things off
That's the point of it is like
Ultimately, yeah, it makes you stronger. You think it doesn't happen to me, bro
You think I don't get stung by my friends sometimes when they want to roast me. Trust me. It happens to me
I'm also human. I signed the McQueen. I know you think he's a cyborg. He was also human
It happens to me too
And it teaches me, you know, it makes you stronger when you just laugh at all.
And then you can discern who's actually your real friends and not.
Some people say to hurt you, some people are saying it because they're your family.
Yeah. And at the end of the day, can I say like...
in my mind
I hate anybody I hate, no
because I don't want to, I don't like that feeling of hate
I like to be
No, don't not pay it in your heart
Nope, never
You don't even know these people
Why would you hate them?
Over words, fuck that
Get that out of your head right now bro
You want to say, because I say
I say mean shit sometimes
and I mean I made a whole
Think about you know Alexandra and there's Tommy James in the night of night and shining armor
Where he's really fat ginger person and stuff like that. Do I want to hurt her feelings at the end of the day?
No at the end of the day I
Won't never I won't never at the end of the day all I feel is torturing gratitude and
A little bit of hurt how it turns out, but at the end of the day, I'll always be here
To say
It was okay. I
Forgive you. I don't know. I don't know if she wants forgiveness or whatever. It probably doesn't but at the end of the day forgive me
Forgive me
Oh, I'll always be the asshole. Just maybe the asshole. I don't care. I'll be the I'm used to being the well
You killed them with kindness. Okay killed them a fucking kindness
They say I hate you. You say I love you. I do
Don't come around like I love you too, but if the real demons don't just disappear like fuck this
Never felt hate towards her really anybody. Yeah, maybe maybe towards uh, you know, Tony
I maybe was hating him for a minute, but at the end of the day, I
Don't hate anybody. I want the best for people. I want to
It's like I don't care if they like me at the end of the day. I
Really, I really do love people. I mean, it's like I I don't want to be like oh
He's like, you know
This like, you know this big
Rainbow or I really do love people and I don't care what people say about me
And if I have a big rod which Mary you like big rods, I got you covered, baby
Which Mary X X X in the chat
I think that's a picture of Beato. She has. I said, I have a tone. I see a witch, but
SIGA one
Here, I mean, it's easy cold. You know, I have a what am I like? I have answers. Oh, you love them
I you love those big John
I do
Oh, no, I don't like this the people's guy Eli. Okay
Take it easy take it easy my boy. Hold on thing that is how's your dad, okay? He's keeping it cool
Okay, I don't know why you got that avatar or name actually whoever you are the people's guy talking a thing
That is the one of the sickest troll accounts. I've ever seen either the people's guys my boy
I don't know why you're using his name to troll
I'm just gonna slide for now, bro, but I
Am Eli night and up
That's my friend bro. Don't ever lie again. Okay, I can say one thing. I want to say if I
I'm sorry, and it's like no matter I don't care who it is. I don't care who I'm sorry if I hurt anybody's feelings
because
Anything I say
Wow kind of dry is the pink Eli account that makes sense
Hey guys, we hate each other Alex
It's a doll replica of the Twilight Zone episode.
There was an episode called Living Doll.
Every New Year's Eve, I watched the Twilight Zone marathon.
It's my thing since I was like 10 years old.
You will find me for two days straight
with a bag of Dorito Cool Ranch and a two-liter Pepsi
watching Twilight Zone.
I don't know why because I have every single episode on brewery anyway
It ain't me tell you like I'll appreciate it
I'll find I want to find this clip of talking Tina. This is the best episode of Twilight Zone
I don't know kind of drive. That's you dick. That's a stupid account to use bro. Please. That's just them
The best episode of the Twilight Zone is called talking talky Tina
I think it's this one. I don't I don't look
Yeah, watch this one. Well, watch this and I have to there's too many to pick a favor, bro
There's also
Watch this one watch it
Hey guys, today I wanted to do a review for you for a favorite piece of mine.
Well, I'm gonna say I gotta figure out the right one.
Okay, I think this is it right here.
Here.
I could literally watch while I was on till I die.
Like that's my favorite shit.
I don't even think I've watched every single episode.
Honestly, there's a lot.
Oh my God.
My name is Taki Tina, and you'll be sorry.
My name is Taki Tina, and I'm beginning to hate you.
Hello?
My name is Taki Tina.
He is thing that is.
I'm not going to go back on that.
He is on my team.
My name is Taki Tina.
Weird, maybe.
Retarded, yes.
But he's still on my team, Canada Drive.
It's a good guy, man
We watched the controller zone
with that interrupting thing
No, you're fine, I'll find you
We're watching Hockey, this is the best episode
The original killer doll
Yo, you gotta look up the one
where the girl was ugly
Because she was the prettiest one, everyone's a pig, but she was beautiful and she would be awesome.
And once you found it, it turned out to be sentient with a taste for murder?
Well, Eric Streeter is about to experience just that as we enter the Twilight Zone.
Annabelle Streeter, Annabelle bought her daughter a little present she doesn't want her husband
to find out about. But Eric, sensing money was spent without his permission, demands to know what
they bought. My name is talking Tina and I love you very much. All right.
You'll look up the episode, kick the can, kick the can, it's amazing.
A very expensive talking doll named Taki Tina.
And Eric, well, he has some issues.
He snaps at Christy, telling her to shut the doll off, which upsets the young girl.
My name is Taki Tina, and I don't think I like you.
The doll doesn't exactly like Eric, and honestly, who could blame it?
The doll makes it threat to Eric after being thrown against the wall that he'll be sorry.
I'm only her stepfather, and I'm incapable nascar aloes nascar aloes. I will raise you that
And he was he had a relationship with an AI bot and made the kid think they were in love
And uh, and her daughter is the motherfucker off himself
AI's getting crazy, but we'll do anything to make you happy both of us
why
Why would you want to make this man happy?
He clearly has disdain for you and your daughter and yet you're willing to sacrifice your
own happiness for this miserable gas bag?
The worst part is poor Christy comes down to apologize to her father like she was in
the wrong.
Who is both losers, Cat and Dry?
I know you're a little greedy.
Tina can't win, Daddy.
At the dinner table, Eric continues his berating of Annabelle because she bought the doll.
It's like he takes it as a slight against his manhood because he's sterile and can't
have children.
Ah, Michael Dolan!
I believe that people are actually using it as their God and psyche doctor and getting
advice from me.
Yes, they don't go to doctor anymore.
They told some computer is playing a prank on him by somehow placing a walkie talkie
inside.
Look it up.
Ever like a month ago, some kids like 14 years old fell in love with his A.I.
comes down.
And then I promised to meet him in heaven, and he was so in love with it that he lost
himself.
AI is causing suicide to my boy, that shit is out of control.
Taki Tina just went from simply disliking Eric to wanting his head.
When Eric checks the trash, the doll has all but vanished.
Eric gets into another argument with Annabelle because he's convinced she's messing with
him.
But he slowly starts coming to the realization either the doll is alive or maybe he's just going crazy.
Now the mom, now the mom is trying to do the AI company.
Doll has somehow made its return and found its way into Christie's bed.
Crazy, look it up, bro. Two stories. It's recent.
I'm not two years ago. I'm talking like a month ago.
This guy might be one of the most vile characters I've ever seen in a Twilight Zone episode.
He takes the doll away from Christie and now it's suddenly turned into Evil Dead.
Quack quack, put that on your pulse, your neck pulse, pulse, everywhere you have to eat that shit.
And then a blowtorch that seems to go out by itself.
Although if he would just keep his fingers on the trigger, it may work better.
Hmm, this must be one of those new vibranium tokytinas.
The saw didn't seem to work, so it's trashcan attempt number two.
Except this time, he's wrapped a potato sack around her.
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
I don't know why Eric seems at all confused that his wife is fed up with him.
After everything he's said and done to her daughter, I still don't even understand why
she was with him to begin with.
He offers to return the doll as some kind of peace offering to smooth things over, but
if Annabelle is smart, she would tell him off.
He wrapped Taki Tina so well, he has to untie it twice between edits.
Eric brings Tina back to Christie, who's really happy to have her doll back, so I guess everything ends happily ever after.
That night, a strange buzzing noise wakes Eric up, and when he checks on Christie, he notices the doll is missing.
Eric goes flying down the stairs and somehow dies after crashing into the ground.
Taki Tina though somehow falls down after him, even though when Eric fell, he sent Tina off into the stratosphere.
Annabelle wakes up and finds her husband dead on the ground next to the doll.
Living doll is such a great episode season 5 is mostly seen as being the poorest of the Twilight Zone series
But it still
Living Doll was written by Charles, which he completed in a single day and was based on an idea by Charles Beaumont.
However, for whatever reason, Charles has given sole credit for writing the episode.
that's a good one, it's like the Glasses episode of the Twilight Zone, let me see if I can play it
yeah remember that and then he was all alone on the planet but he was like I can still read
and he picked up a book and his glasses fell and broke and then it hit him
it was over yeah that was sick bro that was good that was a good one I think it's this one right
here let me see if I can give it give it to him yeah my god you know they don't make him like this
You remember the one no, I got a better one for you, bro
Remember the guy that died and thought he was in heaven and he was like in a hotel in a casino and everything was perfect
Mr.. Jim and then he realized he was in hell the whole time talent
Which has to be seen to be believed in just a moment
He'll show his friends and you how he keeps both feet on the ground and his head in the twilight zone
Oh my god, this is my favorite. I'm getting my Doritos and my Pepsi. I watch this forever, bro, forever.
Some people possess talent, others are possessed by it.
When that happens, the talent becomes a curse.
Jimbo Codd knew, right from the beginning.
But before Ace Larson learned that simple truth, he had to take a short trip to the Twilight Zone.
Rod Serling, creator of the Twilight Zone, we'll tell you about next week's story after this word from our alternate sponsor.
We'll tell you about this!
He's taking a small trip into the toilet zone.
Be sure and see the Colgate Palm Olive Company's new comedy show,
My Sister Eileen, Wednesday night.
Portrait of a man who thinks and thereby gets things done.
Mr. Jim Boeckov might be called a prime mover,
a talent which has to be seen to be believed.
In just a moment, he'll show his friends and you how he keeps both feet on the ground and his head in the twilight zone
Some people possess talent
Yeah, those won't go kick the can when I have the can was they kept going back in time or something and playing this game
So weird and learn that simple truth you had to take a short trip
What about the pig one there was a world where everyone was a pig and there was one girl
That was so beautiful and she was the outcast
He was the monster
That's one of them that's one of like the top five
Next week mr. Charles Beaumont and mr. William Idle's deliver a story on your doorstep with the title
Amber and she tried to have a surgery and it failed. They were like, oh my god. You're still ugly
She was like the hottest thing on earth, but she was like it's a big universe
And they're really I used to watch it with my friend the guy I all I can't I can't really go like all around
The city I like my friends would come over and they would like give me DVDs and
VHS and we watch all these shows and like that's my life. It's like watching these shows. It's like that's I love
even when I was
Yeah, what way? Oh, you want to do a smoke some weed and just fucking sewn out into these shows
Like what's wrong with that? Is that a monster does our harm anyone like you know
Lola, you know, be this as she likes you tonight. Here's the Lola right here.
The Gremlin on the plane. Yes, NASCAR. That was another sick one.
The motherfucker was on the plane and he kept looking at the window
and there was some gremlin like ripping up the fucking wing
and every time he told somebody they looked, there was nothing there.
That was a good one too, bro. The Gremlin on the plane.
Beautiful. Oh my god. It says she liked Lola and so be there. There's Lola right there
I love Lola and beat and what's that to like?
Man you cool, bro. I don't know man. Are you
There's a wire
Well, I'm the only one sticking up for you on that date. Why wouldn't I be talking about you're up here calling me weird and a fucking loser
Can I try go some balls? I mean, I'm a gay guy
You admit it so you would make that groovy the groove
Just admitted it have an audience feel good. I'm
So why are you my friend when you don't have an audience?
Who me because when that's bullshit
You bring me up here and you talk to me and you're super chill
But as soon as you have people watching you're mean get out of here
Okay, no, I can't see that go. Are you being a mean to him? Honestly dick. That wasn't a reason. No, no
He's got a points like he why you picking on Canada? He didn't say nothing wrong the guy feels a certain way
Why when no one's here you're nice when everyone's here you're mean
You've got a valid point dick
he sounds like a bitch and I agree because he's like okay so tell him that and let him defend
them so but Alex Alex Alex literally in the chat time said to him get a life can a dryer
something like that and that's why that's why he went off he said get a life
you know what's been said to me, you know what's been said to me, it's like, I torture animals, I'm like
yeah, you have to play with the big boys, baby, that's all that's happening, I get it man, it's okay,
family will learn, worst seven is gonna be to get a life, I mean get a life, that was like what,
preschool, yeah, you're giving it back to him because he also talks shit about you and thinks you don't
catch it,
Right Canada fuck you man. Fuck you. Oh
That's Kirk that's that guy Kirk you're gonna fuck with me. I'm gonna fuck with you when it's right calm down
That's Kirk
You fuck with me a lot Mike. Thank you. I know Kirk when I hear on my man. This is one
There's the car
I don't know
I like Canada dry can't drive the movies to me in this show
What is ginger old pops the giant cock up? Did you even screen this guy? I don't know if he pops
It's Bangor it's Bangor this is Bangor
It's Arthur. It's me your idiot
Oh my god, you're good. You had me a hundred percent. I had no clue with you. You were the last thing on my mind
Good job, my boy. I swear to God. Oh, holy shit
We're in the building
But he's a little bit whiny it means like once I get a life
I mean, if someone told me you get a life, I'd say that's the best compliment of the day
That's the nicest thing I've heard all day from people
He thinks it as the guy insults. I don't get it. You guys talk to me. He's a weirdo. He's a weirdo
He's weirdo. The guy joins here is like and you guys
Like what?
No, hit me hit me with the oh
I saw I thought I had the Nazi. That's a fire in just Saga
No one doesn't like you buddy
Yeah
Ten to try get up people there's your chance to redeem yourself hit the link stop being a bitch
and get the fuck up here.
I can't say I've been doing this for a long time.
that is a fucking weirdo, huh?
he's cool, bro.
He's from Canada, Dick.
What do you expect?
Oh, weird.
He's a Canada.
He's like a lake.
He has a beautiful house.
I think fucking Paige has a bigger cock than him, right?
Paige has more balls than this guy.
Yeah, I think her clip is starting to grow inside out.
Oh, my God.
Don't talk about just click, man.
I'm just being funny.
She's beautiful.
that she's beautiful like he's yummy right that she must taste yummy must be pain
oh stop it oh so yummy exactly
Jesus what are we going the author yeah let's
woof me and author just went to
our minds just went somewhere else for a second all right look at this guy he's like i'm not
the
I thought Arthur had a heart, man. I mean, it's cold as ice, baby.
He's weird, dude. He's weird.
Yesterday, he was acting weird.
He was acting weird.
It would be nice for what? No, no.
What do you think causes that?
Like a pussy, his girl broke up with him, trying to fit in like a pussy.
He's probably called the above.
Probably cause he went up in the front of a.
People that were hearing impaired the other day. Do you see that? What do you think about that?
Right? Yeah, fuck around like I was gonna go with that, bro
That was stupid to me. Like why would you want a panel? Even if they like it, bro? That's you just don't do that
I don't give a fuck. That's one. That's where I don't I don't cross the line
Those illnesses
Yeah
at the end of the day, heat on the side, they do not like it.
You're making fun of them.
Yeah, they're trying to be strong and laugh and act like they like it.
But that's bullshit.
Facts. Thank you.
That's right on cross the line.
But if they really didn't like it, they would kick them off.
They kind of...
The way they're reacting is trying to hide their pain from the idiot that's on the panel.
That's the defense mechanism, okay?
They were someone up there, come up with respect and love, and when some kind of dry loser
goes up there doing that, that's the defense mechanism, but they don't like it, man.
all of a sudden feel better about their life. That's what I liked about it.
But then he bitches when we're picking on him, right? Then that's not okay.
All right, I'm sorry, I was mean. Okay, I'm sorry.
Then that's not okay.
Stop talking about me. Stop making fun of me.
Fucking weirdo. Fuck you, bitch.
Arthur, can we have sex?
Anyways, talking about sex, psyche.
Um, Bita yesterday had a stream. Did you hear I did and she talked about taking she was talking about you
She was talking shit about me. She said apparently and I'm not gonna say everything
But she said that I had wished that Iran had deleted itself.
I'm like, what?
Oh, wow.
Wow.
No, that's another level.
I never would.
Jesus.
And then I joined panel.
I was having dinner with my girl.
Right.
And I'm like, hold on.
Wait.
No, I can't stand for this shit.
I called it.
Oh my God.
How do you do it?
You got to deal with this shit while you're on or like.
I did it with your girl. You look at your phone and I got to go outside to yell.
No, no, no, no. Sorry. I was washing the plates. I was washing the plates.
I'm washing the plates. I don't. That's so funny.
I said, oh, wait, wait. Listen to me. Listen to me. Because my girl made some
manganese food, right? So she like made a crap load of dirty plates. I'm like, you know what?
Food was so fire. Let me let me go wash the plates. All right.
And so she went to go take a shower.
and I'm listening to the stream
and I'm like
you're watching plates and beefing at the phone while you're closing the shower
that's so great
look
Bita was like
He said
I joined panel. I'm like bitch. When did I say that she was like
And you go out it though does she think you're cheating on her with beater. What did she say? It's like Arthur
What are you doing on the panel?
She listens to the streams and shit. She actually
They're not
She's a normal human and it's like I love you out there. Do your thing. I know this is what you do in this YouTube shit
I rather have you home and do this shit instead of you going out and doing some weird shit
I mean, I
Thanks 100% I don't I don't want to be your beta
I
Bitch that's what be the stance or a bitch what?
Don't say that. I'll get that. I'll get blamed for the Arthur now
Hold on no, let's finish it. Let's finish it bitch eating either
Tony as I mean it's gotta stand for something
Enormous
I'm
Trollers like that. There you go. Trollers as they eat enormous
told us that don't deal. You see, come on. The copyrighted
babies. See how it works. You got to bounce off each other
lighting in the bottle. Peter stands for bitch eating enormous
trollers as
Man fuck beat her bro. She's a low. She loves to stir the pot even more than I do I think
She loves to twist the narrative
That's an SPS because I looked up for that troll a bitch controller
Some fat pig in a room like what's going on here
only because I said fuck Iran, does it mean I wanted to delete itself?
Oh my god, dick, I just almost threw up. Don't ever say controllers, but
you think you put a big down there or under the ass cheek?
He likes a peach buzz on a white woman and a big butt.
the
That's a friend. No, no thing that is from the friend zone. Nope. And she's more in love with me than him
I would I think psyche broker hard because if you go back and watch the year ago panels
You see psyche all looking hot and supermodel II that bitch fell in love with this man
that
he has a nice
She'll fuck out though on like a night out like a one-night fan, you know, she's the bad boy
Be don't take out the cock all day long 100% but who was she?
Man possibly nah, he's another brother. He's another one
I mean, I was wrong. I didn't want to marry you psyche. She wants to fuck out the whole day
No, that's another brother friend zone he fell in the friends on to no way
No, I think I'll go got that shit nailed down bro, I don't know that guy just appears disappears
I
Comes every time the motherfucker comes up
What a beater
Nah damn beater damn, you know, that's it
He comes up says damn beater. She comes ten times. Oh
She loves her. That's right. Oh blogger. No
No
Hi blogger show to her this date
You if Q was gay that's your perfect man psyche
He was what I mean
We had a who's another mass bang ditto that she wants. She knows where she was that girl
I love
For a little minute
I don't feel like two seconds and then she was like this guy's a retard
Come on. No, we didn't I mean a retard but in her mind like you know, she's 52 or whatever
She wants cock. She wants stability. She was Aldo. She wants Aldo. Damn
Well, okay, though
that motherfucker camped up once he was in a mask and a hoodie he camped up he was dancing showing his ass
Yeah, I don't know
Somebody go pick up beat it. I mean I say I mean I I can't take it anymore where she's like, oh, I'm a lonely 55 year old woman
Q45 said I think I think
I can't do it myself this make her happy one night
All right thing that is she says she was fifty nine hundred years ago. The bitch is definitely 54, bro
You're going into like mythological ages here. I don't mean to be mean for yes, she's like
Somebody's got to get that beat ass soon, bro
Yeah, well the edge of dropping I can't take it. I can't take it. I'll have to do it if nobody else does
Please just so many do it, please. I just want to be your friend
I don't know. I don't know. It's sexy. You hurt me. Thank you. Fuck you
You hurt me
Look it. Just look it
Think she'll be happy, and then I can just be friends with her again
Forever thing that is she's saying she's 50 for three years. He can't be 50 for three years
The business 52 by now
I think she's like 79 or something. It's okay
79.
liquor but then I won't have
any more pressure. Imagine you
had sex with her. Like you guys
hung out one night like
Alexandra mayors and you did and
you got really drunk. Imagine
this. And you guys for some
reason had sex and then she got
pregnant for some reason. She's
still dropping eggs 50 years old
and then you had a psyche and
beat a baby. Oh my god. Imagine
that from what happened?
stop oh my god
That nose will be three blocks long three blocks long
It would just be a baby with a nose hitting the fucking lights as it comes out of the pussy like
And I didn't contain such a beak psyche and be the combined
baby pop and have an old spring wow I'm not gonna sleep for years bro off this
honestly this
I just traumatized myself
Stop laughing. Who's laughing? Why do I do it? Why do I do it to myself? I'm not gonna sleep for a month over that picture, bro
Alex a little Peter Psyche running around imagine that reading cards right in his diapers like what do you want the full
Pentecost the full Pentecost and just
Thank you get back in your crib Psyche like fuck your mommy. I'm reading the ten of Pentecost. I can see it man
That'll be the funniest baby on the planet a beta and psyche baby. Yo, I need trip cake
I need all you I need Katrina. I need a last whoever does a high. I need you to put two point orders
I need all hands
Can you picture a beater
I don't know what Alex is talking about but I'm talking about that thumbnail about you and Alex you're back together again, huh?
Yeah, they're a couple. They're enough about fucking time
Tell me about it
Obviously not come on
Tell me about the Alex thing or am I gonna fucking have to sit and make
Yo, you're a blessing you like a blessing from above I was going crazy
I don't know even how I was gonna get it stopped or stop it. I couldn't stop it
said you're such a lovely soul with that calculator fucks sake you but I was just a chess piece in
a feud I didn't choose a temporary favorite in her very special use and she needed me for
who's that who's the one in the mask for a scene yeah
Oh, okay, now I see.
But when the script got rewritten fast, she cut my name from ever-ending pain
Is that a puppet master of the soul?
They look like it
Yeah, she's pulling strings out of her chest
That's a puppet master of the soul
What does she call an emotional black man?
Cart, watch the part.
Notice the chest piece.
Uh-oh.
Very much.
This is what I don't get. This is what I don't get.
It's like a gravy.
What is this shit? Do not enter and dig out the halo.
This was the only scene I don't understand.
Do not enter.
You're the one.
Look at the people chanting. They're chanting.
No the rest I get
That's so funny.
Let's go, let's go.
You know what it is, Esmeralda, that's like all the demons around them.
And cheese.
Look how good she looks.
Cheese is shocking them.
No, that's ghost.
Look how good he looks.
Look how good he made it.
Yeah, but look at ghost.
That's the knight.
Look at him.
Don't you want to run it?
He's a great star knight.
Ha ha.
He's about to crush the fuck out.
Ha ha ha.
Do I have permission to crush out?
Prince fat ass in a can.
Prince Fatters in the can!
Is that you?
Oh!
Brat it out!
Do it with a broken nail!
Yeah!
We're in Canada asking a tan.
Look at Vita. The birds are Vita, God.
He looked up.
The birds are Vita?
You see the birds?
No, he said it. That is Vita.
That's the symbolism there.
I was thinking Vita was the machine.
That was a bit not all that shit.
No, it's the three birds on top of the machine.
Possibly the machine too, actually.
Nice observation.
Every friendship gets a trailer Every fallout gets rehearsed
And I'm not even mad now I mostly won't popcorn
Because every grand annunciation Comes pre-fraid and old
This is the best I get in the end eating popcorn, just laughing.
Yeah, that's my favorite part of the whole thing.
He's just sitting there eating popcorn like LOL.
Wow.
Sacky always wins, baby.
I told you I had a good one.
They won, bro.
It's like this color, man.
I know when I see one.
This is a serious tip. Just follow and start your business.
Oh, he's showing that he's being nice.
He's showing that he's being nice.
this motherfucker you may have seen last window of them stuff
you see him you see me in the pop one I see it I see it now you should make that
McDonald's dick and have a little fucking flowers picking I like thanks Alex
haha I'm just being a dick but
She's watching
That's me see the eyebrows
Yeah, he made me at the end, you know
Yeah, you have your hand up you like stop there you go like no enough coke tonight
Shut the fuck enough cocaine put in nightmare. All right. So what I was saying is
I wanted you to stop it at a parts next time do the directors cut to explain what the fuck
We're looking at because we're not all as fucking imaginative as you are
I can break it down real quick but
Oh, that was so basically Alexandra mayors controlling and beating the shit out of this guy into the Pope
Making him fall in love
Love bombing him crushing him be trained him tongue and shit about him puppeteering him
Because why you want to get back at beat because the beat
You're wrong you're wrong you're wrong you're wrong you're wrong you're wrong
I'm gonna break it down for you for the real the real people out there that
You were doing your show you were doing your thing you having your thing having a good time
Alexandra mayors comes along. She sees you. You're a fun guy. She want to hang out with you
She wanted to pick your brain you guys were getting along
All right, everything was going nice everything was going good. Yeah. Yeah, you want me to move along?
Well, then the whole thing would be to popped up
She saw that you couldn't let go the whole be the thing and then she thought to herself. Oh
He's just using me to get back at beta
She didn't have a heart off of though. She she wasn't going over there. She wasn't the one going over there
You were no, I wasn't hey guys. You want to see something cute?
For me and God came over the same. Yeah, the truth evaluation. You can't deny that
Oh from the old days, huh? That's a dude. But what's under that?
My hand on the last skirt. Am I gonna be holding a tree trunk or something?
Yeah, that's exactly
When all surprises
Binkle and Einhorn Lenore. Yeah, it's a baby. Oh
That's cute
That's so that's about 10 years ago, huh?
That's probably five years ago, but here's one more picture. Look at this
That's cute. Yeah, that's that's the cutest thing. Don't patronize the man actually pretend you care
Benny hurry up, he's got a crush on you. Hurry up
Benny is one of the three guys he's trying to groom
Benny's one of the three
Benny Benny Joker and BMI. What's his name big BG BG?
Joker God bless joker, man
You died he died right he died
Are you talking about the kid rock? Oh, sorry for your loss. Sorry for your loss like sorry for your loss
It wasn't as lost they can even know the guy. Well, uh, oh you didn't know the guy
You didn't know Danny I knew it's like you it's like me and you and you died like I'm you know
I
Thought you knew the fucking guy
Well, he's Apollo didn't die Apollo's back. Hey, he came out from the dead. Yeah, I couldn't believe it. I was shocked as you
the
I'm gonna go to grave like psyche. I love you
So we will ask for it. Okay. All right, Alex. He's all yours. I'm out of here
Please hit the link you love to talk to you thing that is hit the link Mason the drummer hit the link my man
Easy hit the link. Let's pull this put this panel up, baby. There's 10 spots. Come on
You want me to talk to the chat all night, Dix?
I'll talk to you guys. You.
Yes, you can. I think Saiki went to Jerkoff because Fanny's here. He loves the guy to death. Fanny, you got to come up.
This guy's your number one fan. I am here. No homo like H.H. whatever. He just really likes you, man.
You know, it's like...
This is a girl. I wanted to be happy with the girl. It's up. And
I had a picture of
There's somebody and they said it looked like
Like somebody they said it looked like Mason. It was the guy, but it was really mean it was the guy from
Do you think it's me of psyche?
But if I drop a bunny come up, it could be I don't I don't want to ruin that for you, Benny. Is it me, buddy?
No, no, I think you want like you alone any of the girls has he said he did his friend. It's okay, buddy
But I was gonna say no, it's my friend
Who's the guy I can join you perfect and join drop the link drop the link take says he can join I need the link
Should I drop and let you just show a bunny for you to get real quaint it I don't be the third wheel
I gotta go to the bathroom anyway
I'll go to bathroom
I'm gonna leave you alone, bro
Love you
Then he's like my where I'm gonna wait till he comes up though. I'm not leaving you alone until he hits a link
Make sure we're gonna make people. I know good people
Yeah, but yeah, the guy who's you know, I just need the whole thing Benny, but you he cut it there
It looks like a supermodel. He does and I love his short hair and now I have a long hair now everyone's saying
Master
Look at this guy
Oh my god
What's up, brother? I'm gonna go to bathroom
Fucking just been awake, bro
I'm just going with one of my friends, bro
You know, um, you know, have you heard of Danny stranger? You've heard of that guy
He he had like a million he had like 1.2 million views on one of his videos because he got fired from Walmart
And I was friends with him for a few years. He's passed away
He got shot at the gas station on like Sunday in the chest like several times and so I'm kind of bummed about that
But hey, I want to say hi to your friend. Yeah, hold on guys. This is my YouTube father right here
Hey guys everybody make sure to subscribe Benny Brad at Benny Brad go to this guy's channel
Look at this guy. This guy's really cool. This is Benny. I was
Who was I when I went to your channel first? I was I was nobody I was nobody and who was the first person in the world to say
Subscribe to psyche. Who is the first person?
I used to I used to tell everyone to scrub you
You what really what a big dedicated, bro?
You gotta stay dedicated. You're good. I should I didn't listen to my own words, bro
and look at
And let me restart bro
He's way too cool like
Don't know how am I so lucky look at this guy. Hey everybody in my chat. I'm gonna put your you on my my community board, too
I just want to
Thank you, Benny. I
Don't say anything else. I want to say thank you just because I don't know if I thank you enough you like
Hey guys
This guy's the first time even I got away from tarot channels the first IRL streamer ever watched
I was like, what is this? This guy is drunk
Um
Sleep on his couch and like has all these people in his chat talking shit. I was like, I want this too
Bro, I was making good gas when I was still getting doughnuts and shit, bro
But no, that's when I was at my peak, bro
But no when you first know when you first came on I was like not quite piqued yet
Like I think it was averaging like 250 people
But I was going hard on drinking bro. I was doing cocaine drinking
lit
Lit bro. I wish I had some cocaine right now, but I have the here's what I have the voodoo Rangers
This might be probably my fourth voodoo Ranger tonight
I'll say like this guy's
This guy's alleged on YouTube. If you don't know this guy, it's like not even I
Definitely a legend for sure. Yeah, I know I swear to God guys and hey, Benny
I know good people now too and you got you introduced me to good people. It's like
The people who come in my chat that I've been in your chat probably over a year ago and shit like that
Good long hair everyone say. Oh, you're really pretty lady and stuff like that. Yeah. Yeah, but hey guys
This guy's fucking this is a legend. I'm like I'm nobody this guy is so cool
I'm like, I'm pretty chill bro. I'm pretty chill. Uh, I'm gonna be I'm gonna be cool. He's okay
Yeah, this guy's okay. No, no, you're really cool. Yeah, bang
You're like my YouTube. Hey, who's there?
Why are you there? Why are you here?
Okay, I'll come down once I get the police are my door once I get I see that
Well check all the police
Wait, do you know I'm Robert Remington?
Have you heard of Robert Remington?
He was a sergeant of rock, he's on the beach.
Yeah.
Okay, can I close my door?
Okay, thank you so much.
Okay, I'm a big celebrity on YouTube.
Thank you so much.
Yes.
Thank you so much guys. I appreciate you and I support the police department and I'm sorry. I'm still up. I had a little bit
You won't get a second call. Okay. Thank you so much. I appreciate you
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
He just said don't let there be a second call. Are you fucking kidding me? I'm in my fucking house
I can be as much as I want. What are you gonna come in? Oh, you're disturbing the peace. We got a second call
You're too loud. Are you fucking kidding me? What the fuck was that boy?
My uncle was the sergeant of the police department and so
the
Benny the poor guy has been going through hell. You know when they deliver pizzas to your house
He's been getting 20 pizzas a day plus manure deliveries plus scrap metal people knocking looking for
plus cement
They've been going
Dude listen they try to take my dirt bike, bro, they literally but Daniel how much it loaded up music biz Marty, bro
But he does yeah, and then there's been trees Marty was on my show you he like he
Imagine someone came to my house right now. Did you be too loud? I mean, I don't know New York and Redondo Beach is a little different, but
I was telling them I was gonna shoot him bro. Straight up. Well, this person did it. Yes
I mean, I remember they put your motorcycle away for what?
Benny has a Benny the trolling you
Benny lives in a ghost town. It's like there's like he goes yeah pretty much
Ghost hunts and there's money all these abandoned houses around him and stuff
I remember riding the motorbike around and he got pulled over on the motorbike and so yeah, it was on the stream
Yeah, in your own. Yeah
There's this seven please that's outside of my house right now. Thank you. You will feel funny. You're the best
I heard you tell him like do you know who runs this town? That's my grandfather
How'd you tell him bro?
For real I cannot believe they do that to you, bro
The psyches grandfather or great-grandfather, which one was it he was the chief of police for redondo beast, California?
So it's amazing that they have the bulls to come knock at your house. I'll be like get the fuck out of here
But man, my my family runs this shit
I
Hey, how many times don't have people told you money. You look like Matt Reif a little bit, right? I'm I'm sure you get that
Never you know who he is
No, I always get the fucking I get the kid from Terminator 2
Temmest the shuttle main who also they say did the oh no look up Matt, right?
He's a comedian and he's like a supermodel comedian. You look exactly like him, bro
I know he has a he has a hair like like that, right?
Benny
That was scary because we were talking about coke or you guys were like I wish I had some coke and then the cops at the door
I'm like what the fuck is going on?
I mean, I really would love some coke. No, I'm just good. Yeah, I'll be getting lit, bro. But I need I'm gonna start a new YouTube channel. That's what I'm gonna do, guys. So I got you and Benny, whatever you do. I was what's cold. What's it going to be cold?
I don't know if that's a figure. I think something new. There's something about Betty. I said to do it Betty.
I mean, I really didn't think I was too loud.
I mean, I'm pretty loud up here.
I play music all the time.
No, you were loud earlier.
I think you were screaming for two hours straight,
like a lunatic.
Remember, we were trying to calm you down.
I hope I could.
Here's what I want to tell you guys.
I was at Benny's before I started any of the YouTube shit.
Benny was the first person to support me like like by saying hey
Subscribe to psyche is up and I was like, you know and now people are saying oh, I say she harass Benny and stuff like that
Oh
All this stuff like you know Janice you want to you want to hear how funny life is before I knew psyche
Anything never met this man in my life. I ran across Benny on his channel on YouTube scrolling
I saw him on his couch. It almost looked like he was in a haunted house. It intrigued me
I'm like, who is this kid just chilling with his long hair. It was like a dream thing
I loved it and I was watching for a little and then I'm like
you know and then I meet psyche a year later and he loves Benny and I'm like you know I know that guy from so what?
What a small world
Whatever like I have
Great so cool. I thought Benny sleeping. He will fall asleep on panel. The motherfucker would just be like whatever
I'm like, he's got like 20 people watching. I'm like, what the hell is it?
something about
He finds like a like a little like
the house
Benny's like the fucking
the
The business is making his fucking night. Hey, yo, why does this guy look like a lady boy from the Philippines?
Supermodel Benny going to modeling immediately. Why are you still having a little day? I wish I was a lady boy
I'm telling you, bro. Go go get power line fetals and supermodel while you still got
You seen this degenerates teeth. Are you kidding me? Hey
of the
the
Like my answers to your face bro. Yo, I am so
Yo, did you see the cops just come to his house and tell him you're being too loud psyche
We don't want a second call like they were his dad
They just came to his house. They were like, we better not get another second call. They literally just threatened him
For a rest if he's too loud and they get another call. That's what just happened and that's not cool, bro
I mean, I was crazy
I want to I want to I want to pat down or something
Somebody pat me Alexander's gonna pat me down. You know Alexander's a cop. Yeah, but you keep it down buddy because they come back
I don't know what the fuck they doing. They think they can just walk in people's houses without warrants
Don't that's like I was those dumbest shit. I've ever heard in my life
We better not get a door
Yeah, they don't even know the law of these retards exactly don't answer the door. What are you gonna do?
We're done. Don't be everyone in chat. Just give a thumbs up and follow you. I would turn. I'm actually don't do that
Don't do that. Don't do that. Don't do that. Hey, I
Whatever I can do many if you ever need anything like anything
Are you fucking drunk or whatever I can to help you and you should
No, he's not drunk, he's completely strong with you
He's been so good to me, like really, he didn't need to do shit for me
I was like, I'm sucking dick or ass shit
What'd you do for him, Benny, anyway? What'd you do?
Like, oh, you made him a mod and then you unmodded him
He always bitches about that
I was a mod on his channel
I don't know why you unmodded the guy, but he hasn't got over that one
So, I'm gonna explain it to you
I'm modded every once in a while
Some closure, bro
the
and i was like black people kidding at benny and then next day i was unmodded and then i was
black people kidding at benny and stuff i didn't know i'm like suck his dick
oh my god thank god you finally got closure bro thank you needed closure from that shit that
shit was bothering like a a brick has been lifted off the chest thrown in tonight
hey also if you see an electric here it's not your fault thank you
And you know what I did for you, Benny, all I have to say is, Benny, I made some really
good friends too. And I want all of my good friends to also subscribe to you because they're
really cool. Yeah, and hey, this guy's this guy's like, this is the legend. I mean, he really
Hey, I fell off too. You know, I used to have like one year ago all these people on my panel and I was so popular
Now this year everyone says I'm fucking
He's a trash. You know what? Hey, you know what? We're gonna prove everyone wrong here. Here's little this is my cat Lola. Hey Lola
Hey bro, it's just you're dedicated bros. What's up there? Hey, no, no, no, this is this guy
It's time all the time, but you cannot fail if you do not quit my man
So just I know some or whatever, but you know what Benny?
I'll be forever grateful very close to you like you didn't have to do it. You're gonna miss like oh
No, you're sitting here in my chair talking about how you wanted to and you're like, oh, I want to stream like you're like
But I can't this and I'm like, why can't you bro? You get fucking streamed very just dedicated and you'll be alright, bro
as long as you fucking
DJ lecture saying what's his channel name his channel name is at Benny Brad
I don't know if you have a different channel or you want to promote but it's
Different one, but for right now. Yeah, that's the one. I'm still using
This guy's a YouTube legend. I don't know how I don't know how I
I really am really lucky to meet awesome people.
Benny, did you have another cat or something?
Benny, run with the looks.
Take the looks and run, my man.
Going to Super Mario and everything immediately.
And Benny, I do want to say, I'm being accused constantly of like, oh.
You it's like he was grooming Banny and stuff like that. Yeah, I didn't harass you or groom you or anything
I did you can say I did but just now you're good, bro. You're good. I
Rabbit was the only one I was weird my track crazy like that bro like rabbit bro. He was just he still does
Rabbit was still he's still there. I think it might be
Maybe Arthur then did you like to post to your channel in my chat and
Promote you and stuff like that because the year I really appreciate it. Really. I'm grateful. Wow. And so you came by tonight
Who were you at tonight?
I'm hanging out with my friend
right now
I just had nothing else to do in my house. So I was like look it
But if I do if I get off how long you're gonna be on here, bro
I'll try to stay on as long as I can.
I have like a half a beer left and stuff like that.
No, I don't.
I didn't want to like, I didn't want to like,
insult you or your friend.
Like, I like Nate, I like you.
I mean, it's like, and I will defend you too.
And it's like,
Yeah, people just talk shit on YouTube. It's a it's crazy. I mean, it's I know I know now
I know the troll me. I know I know how bad it gets and stuff like that
Hey, I've been through it. I've been through a bad
So I'm gonna get off here, bro
Thank you. I'll see you later
Okay, I think I over talked I always over talked but but um
I still it's still like the subscribe to that guy's channel. I'm gonna say I'm I'm kind of a idiot. I'm sorry
Hey, I do have a beer left. I feel kind of stupid now. I think I think over talked
No
I'm a dork. I'm a cousin 45 years old like this guy's it is like he's like 23 years
Here we have a candidate right here
And I am sorry if I overstepped
They're like, what was all that about bro? What the fuck Benny's like my father of YouTube. He brought dude
He's a fucking child. What the?
Whatever dog literally, but you know what I mean out. You know what I mean. You know what I mean. Oh my god
Here we go
Danny Blanco that nigga beat his fucking mom
That was a book a video I thought that's dumb video he didn't beat her
No, they were in the kitchen he just was going to the fridge you're exaggerating
Benny if you're listening
He didn't become a supermodel immediately bro puncher that mother fuckers a supermodel
He didn't puncher
Judgment but that's bullshit he didn't beat up his mom
So you so what you're okay with little niggas being at their mom
I would
Jumping in on the way, and that's it buddy to wrap
Little thumbsy
My man
My boy clumsy clumsy loves me by the way
He comes you go way back way back watch the clip carefully
They say he punches mom in the face, whatever
Play dick stop talking about the guy. He's not here. I'm not you're gonna play. I'm a player. I'm a player
Hold on. I got you watch. Yeah, like what the hell?
Can't talk about shit and without receipts, bro. That's bullshit. I'm not gonna say don't be with four dicks
Just here says he says shit
Got some proof show it if not next subject
Why?
Because I don't I wouldn't like the same done to me or you as well
If we were on another panel and they're talking about psyche or clumsy, right?
I'm not gonna stay for that shit either, bro
Like psyche beat up his mom like then show it bro or next subject
Are y'all ready? Yeah, I was born ready my man. Let's go
he didn't do it here
full screen full screen him I guess I thought he was going to pull it up but we got to go through this
all I see is Benny throwing a pancake
all of his were for sure at the door
and they it's like a Roseanne show where it's like
look at him
before he cut his hair
he could have been a supermodel then but now that he cut it man he looks
Wow
No, he said get out of the cake and fridge
No, he closed the fridge door and take it out of the kitchen leave me alone mom
Look, I need a better look I can't see it through a broken phone. Wow. I need a better
I thought the rear of the out of the middle of the stairs, but I didn't see her push from the face or anything
I don't even see the mom. I can't I don't know what I'm looking at actually right now
Mom, leave me alone. That's all I see. I see a teenage normal American kid being pissed at a mom
That's too overbearing like bitch leave me alone. I'm cooking fucking breakfast. I don't see a crime there
I don't see a crime
I just want to talk to Alex right now
Here we go. Are you there Alex? I'm here
Alex, I've seen that clip several times. Oh
We have another guess
Okay, so what are you telling me? I believe you but I'm not gonna believe some clumsy broken video shit
I can barely tell what's happening. Oh clumsy the weirdo fuck that nigga that nigga got nigga got child abuse charges on his fucking paperwork
What the fuck no
Come back come back. Tell shows the paperwork comes. He's a weirdo. See, I don't know psyche who the fuck do you trust anymore?
So I thought I was the best now. He's a weirdo with paperwork. I
So let me just clarify that let me clarify that right so there was an issue where
Apparently clumsy was being chased by the cops
But he didn't want to stop he had his
his offspring with him in the vehicle. So instead of stopping for the police, he kept speeding.
That's a felony times two right there. Endangering a minor felony waiting. Why didn't it stop?
Yeah, that's kind of weird. I think because he had drugs.
Wow three felonies. Yeah, I just am used to being slander so much that I'm gonna like give people that get slander a little bit
But we he showed the clip. Did we see anything in the clip? That was like
Anyone up here that doesn't have
you know how many kids in america do that they're over tattooing that situation no no no bro think
about it i've had friends i've had friends no never never no money near you go there you go
never i'm saying so it's never never in nine years never 100 but i didn't see the shopping bro
at an empty fridge and then she came in and I don't know, I didn't see myself, here's what I have to say.
In your way. I watched Benny a lot. I seen the interaction. You know, you're very biased.
You're very biased. Guys, guys, if he, if he heard his mom anyway, do you think he'd like to still be
living in the house several years later?
Like and
And the mom might forgive a little shove depending what the Sun's been through
Excuse to that
Wow, he just psyche just dropped the heart on himself.
Did he call me that?
That's funny.
He called me that.
What a dick.
Is he black?
And you know what the thing is?
You can't take this panel down, psych, because Benny was up here.
So, this is a premiere panel with Benny Bird.
He said neighbor, he said neighbor.
What should be my neighbor, right?
He said neighbor.
What should be my neighbor?
Who did Benny off, though?
You guys are freaks, bro.
It's Psychic Spiro.
Yo, Sam and Sam and why were you cooking poppers on 9 11 poppers? Why were you cooking poppers? We saw the video
Fuck you dick sucker fuck you dick ass nigga like you shove it up in this give him the video
Let's see what it has to say about it
Yo, I don't like this only your ad site. How are you? What you're doing about that?
Video hijacking 9-11 man
Enough, that's how I would do it. I'd be like yo salmon. What are you talking about check this out my man?
Oh, do you see them you see them
Dude Sam has a little
Sam has a little prank, but he likes to cook papa. See he thinks he's a chef. He likes
Can't cook you can't boil an egg and he's talking about cooking
I mean boys, uh psyche that I hear correctly the police came over. Yes, they do
They told them to shut the fuck up and if we get caught again, you're gonna jail. That's what they said
Way, but that's basically what they said. Wow, keep it down. We got a poor
Arthur, this is what they said. We got a call. Keep it down. You're making too much noise, right?
And if we get another call, don't do not make us come back. That's what they said. We don't want to get another call
Holy shit
That sounds like a constitution at the window that sounds like freedom out the window like I pay three grand a month
I will fucking blast south of music all night long motherfucker
What oh oh disturbing the peace fuck you fuck you come and get me
But psyche doesn't even do that
Doesn't make sense man
Guys, oh, we're gonna rest psyche. Oh, yeah
No, that was so I hate her up here, bro, you know
Please the recipe I want to take a ghost and shower a Sam and I want to see Sam and tight booty
Hey, the Sam and video gluey gluey gluey. Well, where was the groove the groovy later? Oh my god
Everyone else is gonna say. Oh my god. I want to do that. I want to see Sam and butthole
I bet cars will be back. So it's like Canada. I did you call them spread up fucking dick
Yo, what you gay man? I'm gay. I am gay
What he could say it though
You cookin' faggots?
Yeah, bend over. Bend over.
This guy was in the cave with a lot and chanting,
ooh, ooh, and then he was cooking.
No doxing, Papas, to TSA.
I was in there, too.
To TSA security.
And then he was on the plane, pretending
he was like a freaking flyer, and then got up.
What is mine through your way?
How do you feel about that?
Yeah, why do you keep talking about it, dude?
No doxing, Papas.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yeah, why do you say your whole name?
well you should throw it away because he wants war he's an instigator it's called instigating
assholes have you been the fucking oh my god no they are they're no they are oh my god
we're talking right now what the hell what the hell you're talking about yeah come on thank you
we're literally talking right now dude she was no fucking wow tell him martin tell him what the hell
You just want to hear this over a concrete beat?
That shit is really shit, bro.
Out! Out!
Wow, here we go.
Don't you crack it!
Wow!
Are you real alone? What the hell?
Some dogs can pop us.
What the fuck is this?
Oh my god.
She tells me with the curtains dramatic draw and then she floats into my panel like a ghost and mr. Don
Calls me some grand monster says i'm darkness
Now i'm the big disaster that's rich coming from the patron saint are changing every pastor
She found herself a champion
and shining chrome roasted him like rescue murder said finally i'm home
but the armor got dented the fairy tale got hazy and even sir salvation said this whole thing
feels crazy i stood there in the chief seat we're gonna check your dancing right now
He just miss your car every week a new Messiah every month a brand new sky
For till Tuesday, sacred till the spin
Then she needed a new sermon and I got written in
Don't contact me, she whispers
Then appears where I live on air
Like boundaries off of peasants and hypocrisies
Contrude away, now I'm some spiritual trafficker
What a deluxe invention, there's not a charge
It's fan fiction with a persecution pension
She collects moral costumes, like wigs behind the stage
Halo for the thumbnail, pitchfork for the rage
One day you're her confidant, the next day you're her curse
Every friendship gets a trailer, every fall I-
Because every grand enunciation comes pre-fraid and overworn
And if I'm such a beast, baby, why haunt my little show?
Why bang on the cathedral door you swore you'd never know?
Don't contact me, okay, cool her?
Then why are you enrolling, memorizing every word?
You keep orbiting my so-called monstrosity
I was useful till to-
who borrowed truth for leverage and performed pain with style
i'll be over here still breathing still speaking still
The house didn't hear anymore the ginger ale is here. I'm gonna kick you out you and word
Yo Alex the song bro. Yeah, man. I was just doing my hair relax my man can't fucking Jesus
You ever seen the movie Joker
Yeah, you're the joke. Yeah, and word out the new one like the one with a brush. Can you peen it?
The first one
The first one because the second one was so many of those movies man. I did see one the one
Yeah, walking Phoenix I did see that one that was amazing the first one though the second one was fucking horrendous
Well, I didn't see the second one
Yeah, don't watch the second one. It was pretty bad. Yeah, so the one he had like the whole city like
To go up and he was on a train or like a bright at the end the boat and yes. Yeah, that was amazing
So question for you. You saw the first one, right? Um, you saw how every time that's the first one. That's the first
So you remember when you would like, delete someone, you would start to like, dance, like you would look in the mirror and then he would dance slowly.
Mm-hmm.
So I think that was his way of like, like calming down, like, oh shit, I know what I just did.
He was stressed out and then he started to calm down by dancing.
And I think you're wrong on that because if he is the Joker
He wouldn't need to calm down, you know, he was probably celebrating
Fuck do I care if I go to jail? I want to be fucked by a bunch of yeah
I so you tell me the joke had feelings how they killed people and was like and the dancing was
Comfort mechanism. Yes, maybe no possibly could be it was the beginning
No, it was the beginning of the Joker story. So he was just learning about himself. You know what?
Yeah, no, that makes sense, man. I mean, it could have been, yeah, that was the way to let the
guilt do his own little comfort. That's crazy. So where are you going with this? I don't know
the way either, Abana. Abana, I want you to punch me in the face, Abana. Abana, I want this one
punchy punchy punchy
So
So, okay, you know the joke, right? You said that was his defense mechanism by dancing after he don't you said that you
You're asking me if I think
I don't think that is I think it was celebrating but that's a good theory
You know, I don't know if he was celebrating or not
but so I think he was stressed out and then he was like fuck what did I just do I got to start dancing um
I feel like that's how psyche is like when he's stressed up he's amped up
He has to play AI. He has to play AI to like oh my god. What's going on? What's going on? Let me put AI
I gotta relax
I think that's how he is
I don't think so
I think he plays it because he likes it and just other people don't you know
I don't really think this is a coping mechanism or psyche. I mean you're here. You can speak for yourself
It's that you coping mechanism the AI songs. I don't think it is. I just think you're just making songs and
Putting them out there and so people are hating
That's not psyche is coping mechanism 100% final answer
But it's just random to put it, you know, it's like there's people it's not rain them look at last
All these people do it don't they get on this a I knit. I don't know
So he feels good about making the songs bro, he spends time on it. He likes it. He thinks we will and other people
Oh my god
Wait, he's talking to you
You know
Hair yeah, I don't know what the fuck the guys going for the stupid cycle analysis. What is you have to cycle analyze you all the time
The police here, you want me to go to jail?
You see me raped by the police. Yeah, exactly. So stop yelling stop yelling stop yelling calm down calm down
Calm down psyche calm down because I don't know who called the cops the first time
But so stop yelling and don't fall into this shit
Because even if you didn't do nothing wrong, this is whoever called in the first time is trying to make it happen again
so calm down brother please I know bro just calm down dick cuz there's some
retail right now like oh we got another connoisse complaint just do it to me I
don't care kill me stop it what up my what up no salmon how we are you dick
seriously time to cool off why why why he's hungry again go feed that nigga feed
that niggas from McDonald's nigga
Yeah, bro, they cook up says house cuz he peed too loud. I don't know what's going on fuck nigga
No, right cool. What the fuck you telling me pussy nigga. Fuck
Oh, you don't care fuck about psyche all right cupid and shipping my peeps you heard that
That's cool. So great man
Please be a friend or not, do you care?
Whoa, you his friend
I'm asking you man. Don't flip it on me. You his friend. Are you his friend?
Are you his friend? Are you his friend? Oh, you just want to suck his dick. Are you his friend?
Shut the fuck up. What's psyche?
Psyche left you here with me my man. Shut the fuck up
No, I'm out of here. Fuck you. You lose a little faggot the fuck up
Bro, I don't know why you waste my time on your loser as faggot. Jesus. I don't even worth my time
Report it report it suck a dick. Shut up. Be happy. I don't pay you for life motherfuckers
I don't fucking care
What's wrong with that little fucking toothless fuck same man NYC I live 20 minutes away
I'll fucking pull him out of his bed right now smack the shit out of him, bro
He is fucking toothless. You see yeah, yeah, I see a picture. He has no teeth up front
You know why cuz he drinks hot chocolate day and night and he doesn't brush his teeth after but he's not 90
Doesn't that happen when you're like 90?
Dude, he's been doing it since he was like one
crazy
So basically he'll never get pussy again for the rest of his life
Unless he got 20 grand for new teeth new via your someone said Sam in the catalog for new via
Overnight my boy if you got 12 grand
Sike
Hello, stop trying to make him crash out. You want him to go to jail because you're the one pushing a dick
But he kicked you before because you got him upset. You got him. He always kicks me
You want the cops to come back to us out, don't you I ain't even know that they were there, bro
Hmm
I find that hard to believe my man. Let me tell you story
Yeah, thank you. You want to watch it 20% I am debating though. I am debating
Yeah, I don't care if I get raped. Okay, just rape me
Yeah, you want talking your ass yelling yeah
Wait question. If you masturbate technically aren't you like
Hey, hold on if you masturbate aren't you like
Like what is this harassing yourself technically? Yeah
Can you call the cops on yourself for harassing yourself by masturbating is that what you're saying?
No, because now you you're going like you're going places. I don't want to go bro. Like what are you talking about?
That's like some
Your emergency I'm harassing I'm on someone's harassing me. Who me what's going on? I'm jerking off. I'm jerking off viciously
Help us on the way. Is that what you're telling me dick?
My right hand
this is all what you want you must find the problem and send them all send them all
my right, my right, my right
I want my top mouth
you
imagine relaying that to the units like unit all units all units converge converge what's the problem
we got a man
attempted murder by his own hand he's murdering his god master all unit
Visually, I mean, is there any other way to do it? I mean, hello
Is there any other way to do it? So I think psych is calm down now. I think he's good. I think he's good
I'm willing no more SWAT teams at the door
Jesus fuck the poor guy. I have fucking ice pull up to him
What do you ice he's wider than fucking Trump this guy
Oh my god
I want to open the top for you.
You're good now, brother. You're good now. You're better.
You know what? I'm not good because no one likes me and everyone hates me.
No one likes me. What do you think? He's been saying that all night.
What are you saying there, bro?
Bro, he says that when there's two people watching or 80 people.
Yeah, right.
Same thing.
No one likes me. I'm like, no.
No one hates me.
I'm just going to fuck myself. I'll see you guys later.
Wait, what? Are you going to masturbate?
You're gonna assault yourself
Wait, I thought why would he end up any Blanco wanted to join later? I was gonna say I don't think he can end it
I mean now he can because Blanco was here, but
It was like he was in Disneyland and Mickey Mouse. Like he was two years old
Hold on. I gotta clarify this. I am not flirting with this dude. All right. Oh, get the fuck out of you
Who said that you want to say careful sound like y'all are flirting with psyche brother. Oh
It's psyche. Okay. She was talking about me and you I almost just dropped and kicked the bitch
I'm with the shop. He's gonna chat and use my managing mod God powers
a little bit
the end of ginger all are not flirting don't even
he was one of the cycle of a year right about that
a hundred percent are the negative artists, come out of the closet I think
I was so I was like literally psycho now seeing the guy
he's waiting for Benny
he's joking off on the public with my name
That's what's happening. We missed something
Penny sent in a number in the back chat and
Now it's me and you what a whack
Crazy
Pick them to take a nap over here at the gas station
Oh, you want those dicks when I just walk by a car and see some dick just sleeping in it like what's this asshole doing?
hell yeah, bro
Take a nap at the gas station
Yeah
Then some lot lizard comes through, you know
Lot lizard
Interesting, I don't know these terms. I don't know you know the means you don't know what a lot
Lizard is these I heard that one
Prostitute really
Yeah, a lot by the gas station. Yeah, I know a lot lizard. Holy shit first time ever. I heard that
I saw the guard
Look it up on Google type in what you know, I don't want to I believe you I believe you bro. I believe you one traumatizing
Nodgable event is enough. I don't need to look it up and relive it again lot lizards mean hookers at the gas stations. Yes
I mean, that's what I was like in the 80s. That doesn't happen now
What gas station do you go to you don't see that here? There's no lollipops in New York. There's a lot in Cali
Cali as I believe that there are whores out there. Everyone just wants
everyone wants one study
I
Want to punch you what's exciting?
Oh, the truck stop the truck stops our
Yeah, but isn't that like
Well, hold on. I think sake you should at least offer an apology. I know he's good now. He's calm
I think you should say, you know, he didn't mean what he said about the n-word and all that
To himself
Well, no, he was saying it. I think you know on YouTube and you're not really allowed to
Okay thing that is I didn't know that was a thing is still in America a lot lizards. Are you serious? Are you old truckers?
I don't know about this shit
It's a lot Lizard. That's the funniest shit on earth. Thank you guys are crazy
They just called horse at a truck stop to me lot Lizards who comes up with this shit, I agree
if you go on YouTube and you type that in, bro, there's like a shitload of people recording, exposing these lot lizards, like you could be in your car and just chillin' it, stop sayin' it, it's too funny, you could be in your car and chillin' it, and then they come to you, they're like, hey, you know what, I picture, I picture lizards coming out of like the woods in the parking lot, like out of the bushes, like all lizarding up to the truck, oh my god.
They'll be like with the little part like little winners with the little person little lipstick on in the
Like this it'll be like this cuz I don't know if you heard about
Are you know, do you know the metaglasses where you can record everything on your glasses?
Yes, yes. All right, so the guys exposed in all these all these bitches, right?
They'll come up to him and they'll be like, hey, um, do you want us or do you want me to clean up in the inside?
I could clean it up for you.
Real nice.
So they're insinuating that they're going to clean the car for you.
But it's it's cold.
It's cold for do you want me to suck your cock and fuck?
And then if you are waiting, you know, if you catch on like, of course, I want you to clean.
How much next thing you know, you're fucking the dumb bitch.
Hey, I get it, man. I get it. I catch on. I catch on.
Uh, psyche, I think, I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe he didn't say the N word. I don't know.
He did. I don't know. Maybe he didn't actually. I don't know what the fuck.
Well, after a lot of lizards, I'm done. And more or no, I'm worth a lot. Lizards.
They're just hulkers, bro. They're hulkers that hide in the bushes.
the short definition.
I think Saik you should apologize. I'm sorry, but I think you should.
Who himself?
Just as a panel, like the chat, maybe there's somebody that's, you know, black and listen to it and heard him say that.
Peace panel!
Oh, okay. I hear you. Are you black? Is that why you're going at this award?
You could be black.
100% I'm gonna check out the truck stops tomorrow thing that is maybe look on some lizards
Like I heard there was a lot of lizards, baby
I need a cleaning
Psychic can you please never mind it's okay
Apologize to the black man on the panel the black people
He's gonna crash out. So I don't want to piss him off. So
Oh, that's right. He kicks you if you say oh hi forget about this. Yeah. Yeah, right
Hi author. Hey psyche get the fuck out of here
He loves to hate you is what it is he doesn't hate you he loves to hate you
I think you should
Because you know why I think like sweet peas somebody must have recorded him saying that word
Be the
You know you said this and
And then you know
The bill is he doesn't mean it. You don't have to like go, you know, persecute the man. He didn't mean it
Now you got to make him say sorry. He knows he didn't mean it. You know, he didn't mean it
We've all said that
That is a good
You know, like why highlight it so much and make such a big deal
Unless it was really evil and like, you know, make me
Man, he's just fucking around.
Actually, he was pissed.
I like, we're out of them.
They were calling him it or something.
And he was like, fuck you.
He just said it out of like, not a big deal.
He knows it would trigger Sam.
And that's all.
Correct.
Zach.
Hey, you know what I mean?
That's all good.
No.
My brother.
Yo, so what should I get?
breakfast bro. I ain't make breakfast today. I was too lazy to make anything last night.
Hello, bacon and cheese always wins bacon and cheese is always a winner. I love do you do you
prefer bacon and cheese or sausage, I can cheese.
Bacon bacon, but I'm a friend of soldiers that 100% does that's the go-to
You do the salt pepper mayo ketchup. No, no, I do. It's called the big baby
I already have my deli accustomed to it
I get a bacon egg and cheese on a hero bacon and cheese on a hero with tomatoes
With tomato on and they're like you want tomato on a bacon and shoot tomato. I'm like yes tomato
Salt and pepper
Ketchup mayo and hot sauce. Oh, dude. I love Frank's hot sauce on my kid. The big babies
Maybe some avocado in there, so you know, you really want to go crazy
You know what I do sometimes I
I
Cooked that I cooked the potato and I throw it in there, too
Well potatoes the best, you know what I got tonight I went to Wendy's and I got two baconators
I had one in front of me right now. It's gotta catch it up. Yeah, that's what I'm having for breakfast baconator
Has has you know the tomato lettuce or it doesn't know the baconators are straight up meat and bacon and male
Oh, you're right. You're right. Keep it real. There's no lettuce or nothing. That's right
Who's the baconator?
Chad, he did not say the n-word, stop.
Freeway to shit your pants first thing in the morning.
Well, I mean, you get to cleanse your cleanse your system, right?
So I mean, the other day I ordered a turkey club for breakfast. It was amazing.
The turkey club is turkey with bacon and cheese and lettuce and tomato and mayo.
That was so fucking good.
Wait, hold on now if I leave panel, would you leave too? I
Would not leave
Why would I leave? I mean something I could have
Cuz he's gonna leave you one self
No, I don't I'm not gonna stay here by myself
So if you're gonna go I'll go to and then we'll just see what happens
You know I'm saying yeah
You got to go you got to go let's go bro fuck this it's been I mean how many it's been long enough. We had a good show
there and I
Mean what you want?
No, I mean, I want I'm gonna stick around for a minute. Let's see if people, you know come by
Depends do you want people to come by ginger?
Sam Sam is testing us by the way. He's low psyche. He sucks like he's cocked
Comes up here on some dumb shit
Well now I got to get to my baconator my man, so decide what's happening anyone popping up or what?
Yeah, somebody gonna join and stick around with McQueen
Canada wetters live
Bo let the man get some rest let psyche get some rest he had a long one
All right, I guess so many past I
Right brother. I mean I tried
And you succeeded
All right, brother. Make sure to accomplish bro. Thank you, man
Have a good day. I'm sure see you looking half hour or some shit. Yeah, not tonight
Thank you
Thank you. Thank you
What the fuck was that gay shit
Oh, who's that
No, no, no, these are slaps. Oh, I'm so uh gay shit. No, I can't leave
Oh, what the what the fuck was that shit?
Motherfucker he fell for the old I'm not gonna leave trick. Haha. Now it's just me motherfuckers
Drop the link hit the link you pussies Arthur you fell for it again dick
What a dick thing that is you saw him he fell for the oldest trick in the book
Oh, I'm gonna go to shut the fuck up now. It's just me
Alexander McQueen
Ola hello who wants to hear a joke?
Think that is what an idiot he fell for the oldest trick in the book. My man won't want these people have a learn
Exactly axe drop that link
Drop it, Gossiper!
Everyone's shopping on the link. Like, someone please join and save us from Alex.
Ha! 30 links just dropped.
Someone join and save them from Alex!
Yo, Benny Bread, my man.
What a good kid, man.
My man, Benny Bread, or Lulz.
Supermodel.
Look at thing that is loving it in the chat. He's loving it.
He's enjoying the night. He's just laughing it up. He's at a comedy club. Just laughing like ha ha
I want an idiot the oldest trick in the book my man
Where you coming up you come
Thing that is has been a member he's got a little member emoji next to his name
Which means he's been a member for a month or two
So it's basically he could have four or five hours a month, I don't know, not bad, not bad.
Look at Arthur, you know Arthur's punching potato chips right now.
Like Alex, the two were dropping together.
What a dick.
The fucking first night you met me, loser.
I want to punch you, come on, baby.
Smootches kisses
Uh, I think she's rushing I want to punch you dawg dawg
I don't think that is a
I'm Canadian a
I want to punch you dawg
It's crazy
Benny Brady, Brad O Bradley, whoever Benny was up here and
Psyche is just in a coma from coming. He choked over like 10 times in the past
20 minutes. He's in a calm coma
So unfortunately, it's me for the rest of the night
Look at the eyebrows. Look at that brows my man
look at the team members laughing my ass off i'm getting ready for work and yep russian
da i know
some russians ivanayakanovic i am ivanayakanovic da i know baby
i can speak russian ivana okay sister i'm your bratan
Remember
But that that means brother in Russian for you little non-russian speaking people
And a dry they say you're whining too much you're crying too much you're doing too much. I don't know
Hit the link. I don't know what's gonna happen. I don't know where psyche is
I think he's in a a cum coma because his hero Benny was here
don't know I don't know so I got no answers for you people tonight you have
to figure it out on your own tonight my friend
okay I just told you karaoke Queen he's in a
That's it. So he's gonna be sleeping for a month my friend. Okay, that's a nice coming
Ivana you just jealous cuz nobody no man ever slept for a month of a coming over you. Don't be jelly, baby
Ivana's jelly
That's some good pussy right there Brad Bradley whatever Benny Benny
That wasn't off mental pussy for psych for a year
Benny coming up tonight with the haircut that's gonna take psyche into 2027. Okay
don't tell me that uh karaoke queen is not oh my god my little flexible chubby mama
Ivana punch you dog dog everything is good with enough vodka says Ivana i know you russians
Arte you fucked up my man you fell for the old Alex's leaving trick
When you gonna learn my boy
Jesus
I guess psyche's out. Oh, my name is thing that is
Either that or you're sucking cock or maybe the cops came back
You freaks will the fuck is calling cops on psyche?
Thing loves us russians though russian envy
No comment why the psyche always leave his streams because he's been on uh
What's your name lovely lady?
You know the guy is on street 24-7 he needs a break
Yeah, no knock he never came back exactly
So he's in the big house right now they got psyche and shackles in the big house because he's a monster
Yelling about Bito and Alexander on the internet. He deserves the electric chair. I
Bet you swat team scheme helicopters. They probably took the cats
But this guy yells
No, that's funny, that's funny to me man
I think that is thing that is always trying to test the brother
Thing that is surrounded by the ladies. Look at them lovely lady peace sign
Ten hours straight giving up peace signs
Okay, I'll take that thing so you gotta
At this point in the game, I don't know if you're talking to me or the character, correct
So I keep having to go back to Ocha and I didn't see your name to just now. I wanna punch you
Thing that is man, you never hit the link tonight
16 years
So you must be dying for new cock same cock 16 years, that's crazy
Did you think
Wait, I gotta look back
I'm thinking thing, but oh, yeah with your jacket. That's right. You in the parking lot
Yes thing
My bad, I just threw jackets on you see like this pussy didn't hit the link all night
See how funny that can happen
Don don't go talk with Alex don
If don comes up I'm out I don't talk to no one thing don
That's your mom thing that is she tells you what to do. She's part of the happers, bro. She has half her tendencies
Michael Dolan get your ass up here man, honey, someone normal
Hit the link Dolan hit the link
Michael Dolan's a special one my friends. Let me tell you
Michael Dolan has never been on this panel by the way
Maybe in the chat once or twice, but never been on the pad
Psyche when you meet this guy, you're gonna lose your mind my friend
Thongy
Thing that is just cheating on beater with Ivana punch you in the chat
Your beater you watching this?
Karaoke Queen
She says que me oigo muy caliente. I sound hot
She knows who I am so Nat why you making me blush
You saw that you sound hot, baby
Let me see those
What is she she's in London UK some shit
Come to New York net
Yes, they're all pussies no one hits the link
Just me and my crew look at the picture you don't want that at 5 a.m. Pull out
Psyche keep it down. We don't want to get another phone call. Like what the fuck?
I'm in the back says Canada
Canada Canada drive I
Can't help you Canada. Hopefully Psyche will snap out of his cum coma
In the back, in the back, I'm in the motherfucking back.
Canada ones up.
But what anyway, to talk to me, bro, come on, Canada,
think about it.
I'm in the back.
I'm up here alone.
You want to come chitchat with me, Queens?
Don't you tell me?
I don't know.
What do you think thing that is?
I'm buying it.
Do I talk politics?
What do I talk about?
Oh my God, I'm going to have to tell myself to hold it down.
Psych is either AFK or sleep.
I'm going to go with both.
Thing that is, he's both.
He's not AFK.
He's under his fucking covies.
Oh, another.
That's my theory, just, you know, being released under the covies.
I'm 43.
My mom still tell me what to do.
I'm alive if anyone wants to come up.
Unfortunately, I'm stuck here, Canada.
Have you ever noticed?
I am,
cybersecurity.
And you don't leave a man behind
when you're up alone on his panel.
You can't just disappear, like, hello.
Poor guy might not have a clue.
And then there'll just be a black screen for 12 hours.
I'm taking one for the team tonight as well
No, I can't think that is no
It happens all the time
Well, it's not happening tonight my friend my little Greek friend
Was your stupid Greek name again to Connie's or some shit?
I think that Christopher John. Oh John. Wait, wait Johnny Johnny
I'm a dick.
Johnny, I hear gyros, my name is Johnny.
Johnny, yes, Johnny, not Johnny, Johnny.
You must have got all the pussy with that name.
Hi, I'm Johnny, that's us, fuck me.
That's crazy, Johnny.
I ain't meant Johnny, I fuck Johnny tonight.
Oh, oh, I like Johnny.
Know my man
But did you really take advantage of it to the fullest brother? I
Was still take advantage of that honestly. I would have fucked page by now like Yanni
When you meeting up with me page page and Yanni
Yanni you hold it on the chart
I'm gonna hold it up here while I go to the bathroom myself.
I gotta tell myself to hold it down.
You're my queen, you got it?
I got it, son.
Alright.
Okay
So what you're not gonna be typing in a chat anymore, and I'm still gonna be up here alone. Thanks, Yanni
Hello, I'm just kidding. I'm having my baconator as well my man. Mmm yum yum
Sorry for what bro
Even though we're here. So what are you talking about? Sorry. I'm gone after eating
This guy's funny, Yanni's funny tonight. I'll stay with you for a smoke. Nice. Thank you
Thank you, buddy. Appreciate it, man
You know never leave a team member behind
What do you think, Yanni? He's gonna keep this panel up or he's gonna erase it like the rest of fucking every night?
He makes it up cuz Benny was here, man. So we might have a chance tonight, Yanni
You might have a chance to actually, you know make some content for the man and I get erased
It's gone, most likely, probably, yeah.
Well, it'll never be gone in my heart, Yanni.
I'll always remember it, okay?
He can't take that from us.
He can't take our memory, Yanni.
I'll always remember our fun fun times on these panels.
So I had a beat it for me, by the way.
That bitch let me up, my man.
The bitch doesn't let me up anymore.
I didn't poem bomb her, by the way.
I didn't have a poem bomb beat in my life.
Fuckin' beat her.
Sanky! Sanky, Alex the Cucaracha!
I know Paige, I know Paige.
Pedro Onis, man
My ambassador of Kwan my page my ambassador of of sage and knowledge
My lobster my lobster girl my Canadian lobster
What would I do with Anna? What would I I don't even know I don't say
beats, as you call her, beats. She upgraded me from Cougaracha to Chihuahua, I think.
But I'm not going to go to Cougaracha, but I was, you know, that makes me laugh.
But she upgraded me. I got upgraded. Seiki.
Lobster.
I fucking hate lobster. I wouldn't touch that shit for a million, you know, for a million dollars, but a page said, hey, have some lobster.
I'm gonna have some fucking lobster.
Nah, I think that is. I don't buy my friends. Then fuck her.
But if it's like that, she should be paying me on your box to grace her with my presence.
That's a live page because we you make us listen to your fucking readings and we don't want to listen to your readings
So you do make us do things. Okay, so if I gotta eat lobster
For my pageronis
I don't know I didn't have to eat some fucking lobster I guess
Hey, do that or tell her fuck you bitch. I'm never eating lobster and go shit die
Can't do that, right
Give me a stupid lobster, man. Jesus. Fuck.
Just have a toilet bowl ready because I'm gonna throw my brains out.
I'm gonna fucking be throwing my brains out for the next two days.
Lobster girl.
Lobster girl, it's a joke. It's a joke. I love your readings.
I love your fucking readings.
No one gets my sense of humor.
Psyche gets it a little bit. He's starting to get it
No, I
Will make fun of him like that like no one's to hear a stupid reading psych and it would take it serious
Like you asked to hear him like I'm just kidding. So I love your fucking readings
Like I have a weird sense of humor
Eventually you'll get it, you know, and you'll understand me better
Paige are you still having a meltdown are you listening to what I'm saying that I was just kidding
Good question. Where is siking are you gonna yell at him now because of me
Don't turn it to be the part two.
Psyche!
Alexander says he doesn't like my readings, Psyche!
I was just kidding.
Love your readings.
I beg for your readings.
I yearn. I need.
It's just a joke.
Oh yeah, Paige.
His hero Benny was here.
So he...
He was really excited his blood pressure rose and he dropped and he's in a coma psyche
He's in a banny cold at the moment the guys in heaven
I ain't gonna yell y'all for you I
Get it. I'm laughing too. Oh, is that a poem? Oh my god. She wrote a poem
ain't gonna yell y'all for you I get it I'm laughing too don't worry about it
that was a poem
see how the creative energy just oozes out when you're pissed now you're writing
poems baby interesting interesting
Albertans haiku, haiku, Albertans haiku.
Stop being weird, think that is, I don't think page, I don't know.
You're not gonna fuck thing that is ever, right?
So, that's out the window.
Albertans haiku, he's still trying to flirt you.
Albertan, Haiku, am I even saying, Haiku? Haiku, Albertan. What does that fuck does that mean?
Alberta, loser? Like Alberta, Canada, right? Albertan has to mean Alberta. Haiku has to mean loser or something. What the fuck's Haiku mean?
And don't tell me Albertan's not Alberta. Come on, what does that shit mean? Don't make me look it up on AI.
What does that mean? I enjoyed fucking you last night?
I hope it's not high school.
I don't even know one poem, you know, I learned here in New York. We don't really do poems here, but
There was a nice Valentine's Day poem. I heard once
And I am a Burton, cause I live in Alberta, so I was just using a reference of such.
Holy Nerd Talk Batman.
Oh, you gotta come to the projects page and talk to the, like nah nigga fuck that, I am
a Burton.
So I was just referencing such
Don't look like you like you're a fucking alien like what this bitch just say oh fuck
I'm a comedian guys remember
remember
Nah, he's the only reservation I go to is Mojican Sun, the Indian Reservation Casino
Reservation, come to the reserve
And I don't talk like that either I'm not all talked out like the project people like yo nigga fuck
Oh, that's your son like what nigga? That's not me
But that shit you just said is also crazy, you know that as such shit
I'm right in the middle, you know
One way or the other that's too much for me. I got to keep it in the middle
Howdy Jim well, hi there Billy Bob. Well, see you in the golf course over bug golly gee willikers. It's either that or
My nigga now I'm saying fuck that yo son. We rollin up on this motherfucker. Yeah, yo fuck that
What do you say something I can't do either or I gotta be in the middle
Thing that is have fun
Be safe good shit. Love you, man. Oh
Fuck it's Paige Aronis in the chat and me up here. I'm just I
Just close my eyes get to us into the ocean
I go up, but the horse is asleep.
I know, it's like Destiny's keeping a support page, right?
We want to be together, but the universe is not allowing it.
But yeah, we're still together.
Like almost the universe can't stop it.
If you call together talking in the chat or being on panel,
I feel your magnetism. You're pulling me in. I feel like a
Very pagey
That's how you spell pagey. I was trying to figure it out. Stop the n shit. Stop gond
Don't even start spelling that shit here. We go a page. Do me a favor and kick gone
He's starting to spell the n-word in the chat
Page mrs. Mod
You don't do it, I'll be back
All right, cool page. Have a great day. Before you go, can you erase Gantt?
Thank you.
Gossiper
Gond
In the chat
Oh my page love you
Have a good day get that baby on the cheese boss
Where do you think he is black or G? Oh, I'm black or G. Oh, thank you. Oh, he's sleeping, bro
Thank you listening we are black or G wants to come open. Oh, I'm black or G. Oh
The groovy gruely Jimmy. Oh, Alex has got ranch. Oh
No way AI song sucks like a ho ho
Got the link for this dick. It's too early to listen to Alex
So go back to bed old man or go to work or do whatever you gotta do
No one said listen you're listening cuz you want to motherfucker
Hmm black RG loves me he loves me bro this guy wishes he can send some men to my house
Oh, I know you hate me more black RG
Wants me so bad. It's like acid in his mouth my friends
Oh, oh, oh, oh black RG. Oh, that voice is the best
Even sake me funny tonight with the boys on black or G. Ho ho. Oh, he did a black or G impression, bro
Ho ho
He did it man finally sake you did a black or G impression was the bus
while Alex was hitting on Benny.
I wasn't hitting on Benny.
I was trying to make a love happen,
but what do you mean, hit on Benny?
I told him he's a super model.
But if that's hitting on Benny, that's crazy.
I know time when I see my man,
just cause you're some fat, ugly fuck,
that kid, you know?
I run a modeling agency, my man.
That kid will make me 20 million in two years, bro with just all his stupid jawline and eyebrows
Kind of like me
Yeah, bro
You know Calvin Klein runs to these kids like fucking water
He'll be the next one on Times Square and fucking Speedo's like I'm banding way ten million dollar contract and the rest is history
And then psychic a marium
Just to make you legs do to never are you are you mind black rg? I'm not on mushrooms or acid that you can try to mind
Fuck me
Pussy pussy pussy pussy 24 7 I make that shit calm
If I see a dick, I'll cut that shit right off. Well, I can't even have three sums
That's how like, you know
I'm not homophobic. Like, you know, I was thinking my boy is gay. That's cool. Gay is gay. Tranny's Tranny
but I can't like
Fuck a girl with another guy. I just my demand in me
I don't want to see another cock be around to touch it, you know share pussy with it like
I don't know
You're gay if you can do that actually in my book at least a little gay like we ran a train on that bitch
Wow
Look at the little raccoon black or G
Black or RG
How black are you bro? It's black black or the blackest is there a blackest RG? Ah
Blackest RG
There has to be one man. I know it. I know there's a black or
There's always a bit a more black or one right black black or black is the black some is the blacks and Mosul's
the king black
So black you can't stand the fact Oh, huh
There was a movie
called the menace to society, right?
And there was a scene where the black kids got pulled over
and the cop was black.
And he was racist against his own blackness.
And he put a gun to the kid's head and was like,
I hate you little n-words.
And the black cop, it was a really crazy scene.
Menace to society.
And then they made a spoof about it.
Like, don't sip your juice while you're in the hood,
which was like a spoof movie about menace to society.
And they reenacted that scene.
Bunny is shit on earth, my man.
The cop pulled the kids over.
He put the gun to the head and he was like,
I hate you little n-words.
He's like, I hate everything about black.
I hate my pants because they're black.
I hate black pepper.
I
Man hates black pepper, bro
If I find out black RG is not a white guy, I don't know what I'm gonna do with that news. I
Always thought it was home. Just some white dick
Mmm
Not that it matters, bro black RG could have fucking stripes like a fucking zebra
I don't know, kind of like Jackie Robinson, remember 42, Brooklyn Dodgers, the first black
man to break the barrier in baseball, the color barrier, it was all white people in
baseball until Jackie fucking Robinson and some black guy comes along, greatest player
ever.
Like nah, we're not playing with him boycott boycott boycott. He was like, I'm Jackie Robinson like what all they do is play baseball
I'm the best like what did I do?
haters galore
Hey, hey, hey, hey
So he gets on the Brooklyn Dodgers
I'm gonna he gets on the Brooklyn Dodgers black RG listen to this and then uh, they're all white except him
And one night the team is having a meeting because they want him off the team and
They're literally having a meeting like how do we get this n-word off this team? They just hated him
And he was better than all of them, but besides being you know different color
True story by the way go watch the movie 42 Jackie Robinson. It's a true story
The fucking coach comes in and catches them having this stupid meeting in the middle of the night about how to get rid of Robinson
The coach looks at them and says you fucking morons
If he can help us win he's staying I
Don't give a fuck if he has stripes like a zebra
Robinson is staying. Oh and wrap your head around the pillow
Tonight think about this when you had is the pillow my friend
There's a million more just like him and they're coming
So I will concentrate more on your fucking job or they're gonna run you around the fucking ballpark
And look at baseball now
But the point of the story is not that he broke the color barrier to me the point is that
What the coach said to them he looked at a bunch of white guys and
Said I don't give a fuck if he has stripes like a zebra
If he can help us win he's staying
Okay, okay
BlackRG, you want to tell HokieKokie who this idiot is? Tell him.
Since I never seen that name before.
This is the idiot that will fucking ban you from here. That's who it is, HokieKokie.
Nice to meet you.
Psyche, ho ho, Black Archie, ho ho ho, did you hear Janet, ho ho, Gruy, Jamie, ho ho.
He's one of the funniest ones up here, I love, I love me some Archie, he's some dude who
loves us as a comp and has power ratios and pretend it's not mental illness, thank you
Black Archie, explain to the man who the fuck I am, okay hokey pokey?
Take notes black or G. Just explain to you who the fuck I am
Now shut the fuck up before I fucking ban your stupid ass, oh
Black or G
Pretty much sums it up. Oh
Basically what he's saying Hokey Pokey is Black Archie loves me I'm the man and just you know
watch your mouth and you make it you know you might survive
In other words you're in the devils then I'm the devil watch your fucking mouth and the story
But welcome you definitely welcome welcome to the family
Ronys
Ronys come back
That pretty much sums it up says black or G. Oh, he's a guy that cops us. Oh, he's a larper
What are you black or G and what are you
Don't get me I get me starting my man
Well, I would like to thank psyche for the emotional rollercoaster. He put me through tonight. Okay
My man was crying then he was laughing then he was yelling
Then cops were there
Then he was laughing again
Then Banny came on then he was in heaven. I mean tonight was like a
Basically like a trip to Disneyland from hell
Store all the coaster remotions the whole night
Up and down
Pretty cool
Actually
Hello ride man. Thank you
You definitely
You never disappoint bro
Remember
Chibi Chibi am I I'm even alright as a Chibi Chibi or Chai by Chai 97
First pronunciation was correct. Thank you Alex chibi-chibi 97
Now second question chibi-chibi is that hello kitty
It looks like hello kitty, but there's something off about it, right?
Is it like an evil hello kitty or something or?
Maybe it's not even hello kitty
I think you forgot the H.
Hello Kitty with a big old bag of grass. Nice.
So it's Hello Kitty holding a bag of weed hilarious. I never zoomed into it so I can't see it just
Chibi-chibi. Oh now I'm connecting the dots. Chibi-chibi, right? Isn't Chibi-chibi-chibi?
So you're a fan of the ganja, basically. A super fan.
Grass. Who the hell calls it grass? Oh my god.
There's the cold weed grass in like the 70s and 80s. Let me get a bag of grass, man.
People used to sell oregano in like high school and college and pretend it was weed to make money
Big old bag of grass that's got to be a country a country
Just checking in any life activity anything anyone come in Roger Roger
This acts and the McQueen coming in from cold psyche
Awakens the cold if there is any life form
Anybody
Anything anyone reaching this message I am out here. I will be out here
every day at midnight
I have food, medicine, shelter
if there was anyone reading this transmission
what do you want me to sing you a song?
Anybody, there's got to be somebody out there.
There's no way I'm the only one that survived this nuclear war. There's no way. Who's out there?
Anybody reading this transmission? Come in.
I can provide food, shelter, medicine, security. Anybody reading this?
I will be at Times Square tomorrow, every day, midnight.
I'm Sandy McQueen.
oh my god i think i got a transmission from beta someone named beta
i just i got a transmission all this says is sake sake
beta if you're out there can you read copy beta
ah hokey pokey we got a transmission hokey cocky hokey cocky i'm reading a
Are there any survivors?
It is what it is to do what it do, you know what I'm saying this that in the third come on stop playing with me
Easy talking about alex talk. You know who's up in this bitch come on
Ha, ha, baby. I'm always watching
All right my man
You know what's saying stop playing with McQueen. I told them stop playing McQueen easy. They didn't they don't want to stop playing McQueen
You know, now they crying and shit. Oh, why me Queen? Why me Queen?
Fuckess
I don't know about links so don't talk about links
I'm just monitoring now Chad and panel
I'm like a peregrine falcon my man just under on the perch just waiting a pounds on that ass
He man she man my man me and he man rekindled
Cause we hated each other. Me and him. I actually, I never hated each other. I gotta take that back.
I always loved he, man. And then I was a, a vile creature. I was a gremlin. I don't know what I did to the person,
but I understand. That means she's a good person or he, whatever.
You know, like, yeah, cause yeah, vile and gremlin, you bite your ass, my friend.
But, uh, you know, we became the love or friends once again,
can rekindle love anyone can okay if he man can forgive me for my atrocities against humanity
and the youtube world anyone can come back because i never thought that i never honestly
i'm like you know there's some people that hate you and you're just like this person will hate me
Love you too, so it basically means that he measures awesome and that has actually a heart
I don't hate yeah, you just call it how it is you hate evil shit and when I portray evil shit
I don't blame you for calling me evil. I get it
But thank you for seeing past that and seeing that you know, that's not really me
pretty crazy
okay this likes me now what are you talking about quack quick quick quack
if i can forget he meant she meant being easy were moral enemies and our brothers
he meant she meant you know bro we can all come back
That's what God says. Turn the other cheek. Forgive. Forgive your brother. Forgive.
You have to. Easy. You cannot move forward without forgiving. You can't. You just cannot.
If you can't forgive the people that betrayed you or hurt you, stab you in the back,
you're not going to move forward. And you got to forgive yourself as well.
Forgiveness is the key to everything, brother.
It's a no, isn't that the prayer, right?
Our Father, Hail Mary, forgive those that trespass against us,
like as we forgive them.
That's it. That's the key to life, bro.
Forgive me, Father, like I forgive the people that trespass against me.
Okay? If you can't do that.
Just go just say just pack your bags and go hang out with the devil man
How city?
Say he come back. I don't know about that
No, he's in a coma bro the motherfucker had a superstar up here tonight. He's in heaven
He could care less about me you anybody at the moment
The last thing he's thinking about is this panel, bro
I'm just stuck up here at the moment, but you know, I'm not Benny, right? Yeah, Benny, bro. Oh
My god, he was so happy. That was so cool that happened too because he was so upset earlier in the night and
then that happened
Awesome, but he's snoring
Probably for the first time in like months that he's probably having a good night sleep right now like he got his Benny
He's happy
You know what I'm trying to say?
When he made his night made his year
Awesome, and he's a good kid man. I believe why shit works out
Someone up there was watching Apple Psyche, man. He was hurting and someone was like Benny an angel brought Benny to him
That doesn't happen Benny never comes up to psyches like what are the chances of that?
Ah quack quack and Arthur two chums two peas and a pod
Best friends. I remember when you guys hated each other
I hate Easy, I hate Arthur, I'm not looking at him.
They're like two high school girls that are more shopping for pantyholes.
I got Arthur good earlier with the old let's leave together trick. It was me and Arthur and
He was like, yeah, psyche must be sleeping. I'm like, yeah, he must be
He's like, I'm gonna jump. I don't want to leave you here alone. And I'm like, oh, that's so nice of you
What though? I'm like, let's drop together then fuck it. Let's just go, you know, psyche will end it and I let him drop first
And I've been up here ever since alone like a king
Arthur fell for the old let's drop together trick like a loser
Uh, Arthur, I'm a comedian dick by the way. See people take that personally like oh alexandre said I'm a loser
That's comedy and I wish you could join
Unfortunately, I don't have that power at the moment
Just yell call them
call ghosts or something
Wake up a psyche, bro. Just let leave him alone. Honestly, let the guy get some rest
If I got a drop to make you lose as happy I will
Penny was up here
So guys sleeping happily for once in like a month
There was cops at his house easy. Did you see that cops went to psyche's house cops went to psyche's house tonight easy
Did you see that?
They went to the script, bro
Asked me why on live panel. He was like someone's on my door. Yep, and it was the police
Redondo Beach police went to psyche's house on panel check this out for real for real
You know what they said to him easy. They said we got a call. We were on panel
He was like hold on someone's on my door and he was like who is it and we thought it was like another pizza
They said to him, we got a call. You're making too much noise
Do not make us come back. You understand? We we don't want to get another call. They told him
So redondo, California beach police went to psyche cells like they were his dad or mommy and said shut the fuck up
Like you're making too much noise in your in the in your own house easy
Go watch it. It's on this panel my man
Benny bread was there for it. Thank you, Benny
Yo, is that insane or is that insane?
Is that a law you can go to people's houses and tell them to be quiet like please be quiet like what?
I mean, I get it. If you're having a Puerto Rican party and your neighbors, you know, call the cops like too much noise but psyche in his apartment yelling at us on panel gets a police call and they told him easy, you know, they told them do not make us come back.
They threatened him.
Don't don't make there be a second call. They told psyche.
Like don't have someone else called now one like yo, he's making too much noise again because you'll go to jail
Inspector inspector. What are we gonna do with that? I?
Know what happened with you, bro, and you know what psyche stood up for himself
He was like, you know who my uncle is or his grandfather
You know, and he threw that in their face and you hear some rookie asshole saying
Let not there be another call. That's what they said. You're making too much noise. Keep it down and
Don't make us come back
Imagine that imagine and when PD knocked on my door right now
Like I paid three grand a month and they were like, yeah, your neighbor said, oh, you're making too much noise
Don't make us come back
I don't know what to do with that man. I don't know what to do with that
I get it if you're having a Puerto Rican party and you're waking up the whole block. I get that like yo
That's just crazy enough with the fireworks and the fucking speakers on the lawn at 4 a.m
That I get brother, but psycharone's in his room with his little cats
Knock knock police keep it down
Mmm
Shut up, Arthur
Yeah, easy who the fuck called that on him
It could be psyche said once that the his neighbors were complaining and they heard him say the name Christine
It could have been Christine
honestly
Psyche said that he has a neighbor behind his house that complains about him yelling
When he's like, oh drunk like this. So this is a backstory. So it's part of that guy
Behind Psyche's house. There's some neighbor that hates Psyche and he complains about him yelling when he does this and
He even said one time that he knows the people that he talks about like he mentioned Christine
Saki told us on panel one like my name was crazy. He knows the people are here, you know Arthur Christine like he listens to me
So I had to be that guy
Because like he was screaming like that tonight
But I don't get I
Just don't get it. Is that allowed to tell someone to stop yelling like in your home. I
Guess so man. I don't know
Fuck for cops, but it was like their dad like stop yelling. Don't make us come back. What the fuck? Oh
Shit
That's no freedom
They can't do that easy, right? I mean, I guess they can in Redondo Beach. It would be so quiet
Okay, I try to put myself in their shoes easy
So if my neighbors were yelling so loud at 3 a.m
That I can hear them through the walls and I call 911
No, it's complaint. I get it. They will come and say listen what's going on and someone dying like keep it down
You can call again, I guess
Oh, someone's yelling. I don't know, bro
But I guess you can all do that in like inner cities, you know, like California, New York
You can't do that in the country like you get killed
So you're telling me you can't yell anymore, bro
You I should be in the electric chair then
If you if you get fucking cops cold hold on you for yelling on YouTube
Oh my god, specifically at your house, like so I paid 9 grand a month. I'll yell all I want
I'll yell all I fucking want my friend
Tell that motherfucker to get earplugs or move. I mean, I don't know. What's the law here?
Arthur, shut the hell up. Like it's fucking. Oh, Tom.
In regards of noise and quiet hours. Yes.
That's crazy. So yeah, actually, so he's in violation of like noise codes and shit.
Disturbing the peace. Your neighbors are calling a disturbance.
Don't make us. But the way they said it, though, do not make us come back.
You can hear him on live.
He was like, don't make there be a second call, bro.
Do not let there be another second call.
Basically saying, if we come back again,
you're going to jail for yelling in your own house
at a computer?
Well, I guess that's why you can have money
and have a nice house, not lifting next to losers
that cold cops on you.
Thank God I live in a nice place. I can scream my brains out old fucking day. No one's calling cops
Like this guy's going crazy. That's insane
No, it's complaints are for Puerto Rican parties, bro in the middle of 5 a.m. I went doom doom doom music blasting
You got a move, I don't know man
You can't live next to people that coke ops on you if you can't even yell in your home and like not be put private ties
I
Don't know
No, it's ordinance generally strict loud unnecessary noise or substantial areas. Yeah, but that's like party shit psyche yelling
About sweepy and beta like I hate you guys cops at the door
Cops at the door because you're yelling about you too
That's all I'm saying. I mean how loud was he yelling fuck?
If I can take it his neighbor and he's in my ear, you know, I'm on the line with him his neighbor a house away can't take it like hello
Close your fucking window. So what the fuck you telling me psyche's yelling through the whole neighborhood to the point
They got a co-cop son of him
Like this guy just keeps yelling
Alexander for 24 hours somebody somebody told him in jail
Hmm
10 p.m. To 7 a.m. Can you hold on for being too long plus apartment complex may have rules?
But he lives in a private house. Doesn't he not a complex? I thought of this he meant a hundred percent
Like you can't just you know when you live in a complex with people there's rules
But according I thought he lives in a little private house
It's some neighbor behind them.
It's a house behind them that's calling it in.
So there's some guy that lives behind his house
and can hear Psyche's every word when he starts yelling.
He said it on panel recently.
I just don't know if that's enough to send cops
and say don't make us come back,
because some asshole be-
Oh, he's too loud or he's yelling.
No, I'm on my own properties is my house till I lose it a fucking put on music and shut the fuck up. I don't know
If I live in redond, whatever if I live anywhere and have my own home
I'm assuming I can do as I please
I mean, Jesus, so there is no freedom.
I own a four-five million dollar home.
I can't even yell.
He lives in a complex.
They own the complex.
You guys know everything.
I don't know.
I thought he lives on top of his sister's fucking house or some shit.
Doesn't matter where you live bro the point is what the fuck cops at his door
But yelling on YouTube like it can't it couldn't be that loud like I'll push your people
Is there fucking like insulation in the walls like these people can hear psyche screaming like a 911 was emergency
There's some guy screaming. He keeps saying beta
That's fucking funny to me bro, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Where he man and how teens can't be after 11. That's like fucking
What were two shit? What are you talking about?
Thank you, brother appreciate that
Alexander answer my question
I've had cops tell me to go home because I was out past 10 p.m.
What?
Freedom is an illusion
NY sheriff's run NYC
freedom's an illusion
No, you can go in a park and run. It's not it's an illusion when you're in a cell or handcuffs like oh shit
It's a misillusion. I don't I don't know what you mean by that. Hey, man. It's an illusion
You're free, but yet not free free, but not free
illusion J1 colon
No one can call him dick the guy sleep and Benny was here. He's fucking in a coma
You're lucky we psyche
By Monday my man, hopefully wake up tomorrow this guy's in a Benny coma right now
You know how he is Benny. He's dreaming of Benny
Before his haircut after his haircut tonight
He's probably watching the whole the live just he probably has many on pause like rewinding every little second like oh, oh, Benny
I'm telling you when I see in psyche for days
Benny Benny Benny Benny the guys are super model both I was Benny man. Come on
J1 if J1 so super wanna tell the same shit, but J1's not a supermodel. He's getting on J1
J1 could be a supermodel for like McDonald's or some shit
Oh no, no
He, man, he appeared like a few months ago, which was actually like
the, you know, like the trailer to today.
Exactly. He appeared real quick a few months ago, and then just like
gave him a little dabble of Benny, a little taste and disappeared.
And then like, it was even double crush, like, oh, Benny, Benny, Benny.
And he appeared today.
And God bless Benny because man, we needed it today psyche was not in a good mood today
So I don't know who sent Benny what angel from heaven sent Benny today to put a smile on psyche's face because he needed it
You need it man, I don't know who keeps fucking with this fucking asshole, but it's a fuck with psyche
He's snoring. I can feel him, honestly. That guy's finally sleeping for the first time in Comfy.
Benny!
Tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut.
So funny to see him so star-shocked. He's like Benny. He doesn't even know what to say. Honestly. It's like he's so he gets star-shocked
I think I can do it. I can do
Alex what are you plans for what are your plans for the weekend?
Same thing I plan every weekend J1
To try to take over the world
The pinky and the brain the pinky and the brain one is
Yo
Dang it out of coffee grounds need to grind on some odd just one coffee is up
I know that's torture when you just want it, and you, ah.
That's what teleportation should come into play.
Someone has to have been teleporting.
Just like teleport coffee in my hand or teleport me to the storm back.
I don't like it, J.
One, I didn't like it at all.
I wasn't happy.
The pinky, the pinky and the brain, the pinky and the brain, the Alex and J1, the Alex and
J1, one is a genius, the other's insane, Alex, Alex and J1, one, one, one.
What are we going to do today, Alex?
Yeah, teleportation exists that I in my heart he meant and you know, they're keeping that shit from us
That's what the elites the aliens the whole
Teleportation that's why they're so interested in quantum physics and all that shit if all they're saying is true about
Adams and all that shit. So teleportation is real
You know
You collapse time and read and atoms and quantum and this and that
Time doesn't exist
time dilation
Speed, you know the fast you go the slow you age all that shit combined
Teleportation
I don't know about in the human form, but you can, I've heard, I've read about teleportation
projects between China and the USA.
They use like kids, like gifted children, and they make them teleport things like paper
Butterflies, like teleportation is real, there is documented evidence from the NSA of teleportation.
Now, can a human teleport to another place?
The remote viewing, they call it, I don't know.
But who's got time for that shit right when you wake up every day like I get to work and fucking pay my car insurance
so
It's crazy
Yeah, I've heard things she meant there's something called jump rooms, you know, they just
Yeah, what the monarch butterflies the monarch ones those like orange beautiful ones
Do you look that up?
They migrate to Mexico or something every year like they all like
Go to a certain place. I don't know the nature is out of control
And
They're never happened in my area before but that's because times are changing he man
Things are happening. Exactly the world's changing
It was fucking negative 16 degrees like two weeks ago
Yesterday was almost 70 degrees
That's not normal the climate change so sudden
Something's up
It went from fucking Antarctic winter to spring overnight.
Yeah, so the monarchs, the orange and black ones,
they have a purpose. Every year they migrate to a certain place in the jungle in Mexico,
Like every monorak on the earth just goes there and like
That's too much shit. I don't know. What are you gonna do? Believe in butterflies aliens fucking
No conspiracy theories. What happened? I ran getting bombed. I mean look even looked at that shit
Such as though happening war three
way too early, exactly. Nature's off-balance, hey man, that's what it means.
What they're saying is true, like nature's off-balance, global warming,
the polar caps melting, extreme winter and then extreme summers,
Like usually it like takes a little while when it goes from negative 10
To 70, you know, you have like a month till like get the temperature risen
It went from like two degrees to 90 in a day. Like what is this shit? I swear to God
I was fucking I had six layers on the next day. I was in shorts
And it's still happening back and forth. It just keeps bouncing like cold hot cold hot extreme
It's not normal
Lived in my whole life. This has never happened
So either we're fucking the player up or CIA is doing something or something something's up
I feel like I say a muley on a rant in the garage
I say, if you're out there, baby, hit the link.
You ever look at a butterfly though, he man, and realize that shit was like a caterpillar once?
Butterflies are little worms, they're worms, then they turn into a cocoon and then to that butterfly.
What the fuck is that? Who made that shit? Talking about a process, right? A worm, a worm, a caterpillar,
Transforms, and now it's this beautiful flying thing and you're telling me that's not a fucking God
That she's just a coincidence
No fucking way, that's a coincidence, bro something made that
An extremely powerful God made that
Coincidence can't make that stupid shit up. What are you crazy?
Turn the catapult into a butterfly
The big bang theory that's my favorite one it must have been the big bang theory
Two gases collided in space and here we are shut the fuck up an evolution a monkey turned into this shut the fuck up
That's not the window, too
The answer is there is a God a creator an architect that designed all the shit. I
Know it's scary, baby. I you rather believe in evolution
You rather believe in the Big Bang theory than face the facts that there is a fucking God
And you're going to hell my friends or heaven
Depending on how you play this game
Exactly, he means like a watch, a watchmaker.
You will look at a watch, the intricate parts, the ticking tick tick or the little parts that make it work.
That's you. There is a watchmaker out there. It's called God.
We are His creations.
Just look at the body. The veins, the system, the brain, how it all coincides.
Hello? Oh, we were just monkeys. Shut the fuck up.
I'm gonna have a lollipop now a great lollipop. Okay, it's now I'm excited
oh wow i've never been pregnant and imagine that if i was pregnant i would definitely believe in god after that like oh my god
i live in creature inside of me it's too much everything is too much perfect to work and coincide to not be designed
there's no way everything is that you know
Everything is perfect the elbow the joints to hand this the system the nervous system of this
It's like you with the sign you can need a kidney for this to clean there a dick and there's a woman won't always like you know
You want a drawing board one day and God was just drawing you out like hmm?
I'm gonna make this work. Oh cool. Let's give him a kidney a heart the hardest the motor. Well, he's gonna need a brain
How do we connect the brain to the toes?
Well, we're giving them some veins, right?
We're giving them some veins over here.
Get the electrical signals going.
How are they gonna multiply, sir?
Well, we got this bitch over here.
See this thing that hangs?
The dick goes in this hole.
You know, the little white stuff comes out
and then went where? And then they multiply, bro.
Jesus.
Did you miss fucking the pop quiz on Monday, my man?
God don't play
And then we have all these other human beings on the planet elephants giraffes
The reproductive system that alone should tell you there's a god
The reproductive system. How does that work? Oh, that was a coin kid ink. Thanks big bank theory. Wow
When those gases collided a billion years ago, they were really smart gases like the reproductive system
What?
What
There's a God baby son, he's the son look at the son every day and just be like thank you God. Don't fuck are you
Jesus fuck
No, it's a hell of a ride. Just be grateful and enjoy don't spend time
Trying to figure out what he is. This is gonna be a best advice. I'll ever give you
Don't waste your life
Trying to figure out if the moon and sun are real now because you're not gonna figure it out
Just enjoy your life
So you're a beautiful kid
Enjoy your life
every species on earth every animal with its own little defenses the colors the this the that
it's too much to be coincidence something made us i know it's fucking scary man i've been trying
to grapple with it myself but we did not just appear out of nowhere because two fucking gases collided
Have a great day, he man.
Thank you for engaging.
I have to have to hop along and get ready for the day. Thank you for this early morning conversation. I appreciate the topic and communication.
That kind of rhymes. Have a great day.